<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Business on Ideas on Stage</title>
    <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/tags/business/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Business on Ideas on Stage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© Ideas on Stage 2015 - </copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.ideasonstage.com/tags/business/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Why should I hire an external event coordinator? An experienced event manager&#39;s point of view</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2020/02/25/2020-02-25-why-should-i-hire-an-external-event-coordinator-an-experienced-event-manager-s-point-of-view/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2020/02/25/2020-02-25-why-should-i-hire-an-external-event-coordinator-an-experienced-event-manager-s-point-of-view/</guid>
      <description>A lot of people think that organizing an event is within everyone’s reach. But is it really true? If you want to organize one for your company, a lot is at stake, including brand reputation as well as the satisfaction of your customers or guests. If you don’t want to take any chances and make a positive impression, it’s important to set up a team dedicated to your project.
If you are the organizer in the hot seat, you are likely asking yourself many questions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet Camille, your new contact</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/10/15/2019-10-15-meet-camille-your-new-contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/10/15/2019-10-15-meet-camille-your-new-contact/</guid>
      <description>A funny thing happened when I was describing my “dream job” to a friend. I imagined a company whose mission would be to help people become great presenters, and had a culture that was both supporting and nurturing while remaining professional and attentive to clients’ needs. My friend said: “I know that company!”
A few weeks later after a relaxing summer vacation between positions, I found myself in the company of all my new colleagues, some whom I met for the very first time, at our annual Fall team meeting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The leadership Triangle</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/09/09/2019-09-09-the-leadership-triangle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/09/09/2019-09-09-the-leadership-triangle/</guid>
      <description>There is one key objective at the heart of all presenting. Persuading the human mind.
Today there is a war on for attention and space, with the human mind as object of the conquest. In 2019, emotions rule the stage and calm reasoned logic seems to have gone out of fashion. Individually and collectively, most of us are getting our information from sound bites, news summaries, and short burst headlines provided by our iPhone feed; while opinions change from one glance at the screen to the next.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>“Others Too”: Zoom&#39;s Terrible Communication Misstep</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/07/16/2019-07-16-others-too-zoom-s-terrible-communication-misstep/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/07/16/2019-07-16-others-too-zoom-s-terrible-communication-misstep/</guid>
      <description>You may have heard about it, a basic security problem was found in Zoom for Mac, that allowed attackers to turn the camera on remotely. Zoom is an application used to organize videoconferences on the web. It works well and has been widely adopted by corporations and individuals seeking to provide a quality service to employees working remotely or on different sites.
The security problem itself was easy to correct, and, at the time of this article, should have been fixed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Elon Musk running out of credibility?</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/04/30/2019-04-30-is-elon-musk-running-out-of-credibility/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/04/30/2019-04-30-is-elon-musk-running-out-of-credibility/</guid>
      <description>Gizmodo wrote this rather funny piece about Elon Musk’s latest rash of announcements, such as fully autonomous cars and a million robotaxis by 2020. Now, Gizmodo is not exactly known as a staple of great journalism, but sometimes they have a knack to hit the nail on the head. In this case, the fact that for several years Elon Musk repeatedly promised—and failed to deliver—full autonomous driving. Honestly, s eeing how hard it is to achieve full autonomy, and how many problems are left with Tesla’s current autopilot system, it is hard to believe these new promises will actually materialize.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Barbara Minto’s pyramid principle outdated?</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/04/16/2019-04-16-is-barbara-minto-s-pyramid-principle-outdated/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/04/16/2019-04-16-is-barbara-minto-s-pyramid-principle-outdated/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks ago someone spoke a name that I hadn’t heard in a long, very long time: Barbara Minto. She’s the author of the Pyramid Principle, a book that was long considered, and sometimes still is, the gold standard of presentation structuring in the consulting industry. But it was back in the eighties. So I’ll dare to ask the question: is the pyramid principle outdated?
If you’re not familiar with the pyramid principle, it is a method to lay out the information in a presentation in the most efficient way possible, based on how people with little time, especially executives, absorb information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to starve the presentation vultures (part 1)</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/02/05/2019-02-05-how-to-starve-the-presentation-vultures-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/02/05/2019-02-05-how-to-starve-the-presentation-vultures-1/</guid>
      <description>Maybe you feel that your last presentation was a complete failure. You didn’t manage to shake off your nerves. You became confused. The client or your boss criticized you. Maybe you’ve been caught in a downward spiral for some time, each criticism making you lose confidence, and making the next presentation worse. I have good news for you: no matter what your situation is, this vicious circle can be broken, and you gain the necessary confidence to enjoy presenting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to steal the show</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/01/29/2019-01-29-how-to-steal-the-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/01/29/2019-01-29-how-to-steal-the-show/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks ago, Ideas on Stage had the privilege of organizing a sales presentation training for Krauthammer at Dolce La Hulpe, close to Brussels in Belgium. For us, delivering a training for dozens of senior people at Krauthammer, one of the world’s most respected sales and management training companies, felt like designing something for Jonathan Ive, Apple’s legendary designer: a bit intimidating but incredibly exciting.
The training met with great success, and it was fantastic to work with such talented people, but what I will remember most are two presentations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Business Can Learn From TED</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2018/04/10/2018-04-10-what-business-can-learn-from-ted/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2018/04/10/2018-04-10-what-business-can-learn-from-ted/</guid>
      <description>Today marks the start of TED2018, the latest edition of the world&amp;rsquo;s best-known modern conference. Participants in Vancouver will be treated to high-quality talks from well-prepared speakers, and will leave feeling energized and inspired.
Back in the office, you and your colleagues will no doubt be subjected to low-quality presentations from poorly-prepared speakers, and you will leave feeling bored and uninspired.
Business presentations are not TED talks. A board meeting is not a stage with a round red carpet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Women on Stage Workshop Returns Dec 7</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/10/30/2017-10-30-women-on-stage-workshop-december-7-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/10/30/2017-10-30-women-on-stage-workshop-december-7-2017/</guid>
      <description>This December 7th in an elegant boardroom along the Champs-Elysée something powerful will take place: the beloved Women on Stage workshop will return by popular demand led by Marion Chapsal, Chief Learning Officer and Speaking Coach. Spaces are limited to allow space for each voice and leader to present and receive personalized feedback.
 Marion Chapsal
  For over 20 years, Marion&amp;rsquo;s work has helped leaders to strengthen their executive presence, enhance their presentation and communication skills, and promote gender-balanced leadership in everything she does.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can Women Pitch As Well As Men?</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/09/01/2017-09-01-can-women-pitch-as-well-as-men/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/09/01/2017-09-01-can-women-pitch-as-well-as-men/</guid>
      <description>It’s a simple fact that most successful startups are run by men. Why? Firstly, there are more men than women who decide - or dare - to start companies. Secondly, men are more successful at raising funds than women, and even those women who do raise funds end up raising less, on average, than their male counterparts. Having spent two years playing in the Silicon Valley arena myself, I’ve seen this truth first hand both in California and now in France.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
