<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PowerPoint on Ideas on Stage</title>
    <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/tags/powerpoint/</link>
    <description>Recent content in PowerPoint on Ideas on Stage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© Ideas on Stage 2015 - </copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.ideasonstage.com/tags/powerpoint/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to disable all animations in a PowerPoint presentation</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2020/07/07/2020-07-07-how-to-skip-all-animations-in-a-presentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2020/07/07/2020-07-07-how-to-skip-all-animations-in-a-presentation/</guid>
      <description>Do animations in a presentation make you feel seasick? Animations in PowerPoint are great, until they aren&amp;rsquo;t. A small dose of animation is fine, but presentations with too many animations can be cumbersome to watch in presenter mode.
Luckily, PowerPoint offers a simple functionality to disable all animations in one go. In the ribbon, go to the &amp;ldquo;Slide Show&amp;rdquo; tab, then click on &amp;ldquo;Set up Slide Show&amp;rdquo;. Then simply tick the box &amp;ldquo;show without animation&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three most annoying problems with business presentations, according to PowerPoint expert Dave Paradi</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/12/10/2019-12-10-three-most-annoying-problems-presentations-powerpoint/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/12/10/2019-12-10-three-most-annoying-problems-presentations-powerpoint/</guid>
      <description>Dave Paradi, an expert on PowerPoint presentations, has published the results of the annoying PowerPoint survey. We are not going to discuss the full results here, but what is clear is that the top 3 hasn’t changed much in many years. You could probably guess them just by asking yourself “what do I hate about PowerPoint presentations?” The top three problems are:
The speaker reads the slides to us
The text is too small</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cliché slides</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/11/05/2019-11-05-cliche-slides/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/11/05/2019-11-05-cliche-slides/</guid>
      <description>You’ve probably all seen these slides: they use a picture which is “cliché,” like two shaking hands. Using a few of these clichés is fine, because they are often the clearest way to illustrate the idea of the slide; it’s nice to be creative, but clarity of the message comes first.
But some presentations seem to overflow with these clichés, using them on every slide. So I asked myself the question: why are some presentations nearly cliché-free, while other presentations are full of them?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Check If Your Presentation Remote Works Without Anyone Noticing</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/10/08/2019-10-08-how-to-check-if-your-presentation-remote-works-without-anyone-noticing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/10/08/2019-10-08-how-to-check-if-your-presentation-remote-works-without-anyone-noticing/</guid>
      <description>It’s your turn to present. You’ve launched your presentation and enter the stage. But how do you know if your presentation remote is working? If you start clicking back and forth between your first and second slide to see if it is working, everyone will notice what you’re doing, and you will not make a great first impression.
Luckily, someone shared a simple tip on twitter. Just duplicate your first slide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Prezi failed at revolutionizing presentations</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/05/28/2019-05-28-why-prezi-failed-at-revolutionizing-presentations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/05/28/2019-05-28-why-prezi-failed-at-revolutionizing-presentations/</guid>
      <description>In 2009, the year when TED decided to launch its TEDx license program, Prezi was born out of the desire to overcome the limitations of tools like PowerPoint and Keynote. With its dramatic zooming and panning effects, it certainly did catch the eye of audiences worldwide when it was introduced. But its over-reliance on movement effects quickly became a visual nuisance, making the audience feel as if they had been on a boat caught in a category 10 hurricane.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
