<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Corporate-events on Ideas on Stage | Deliver amazing presentations</title>
    <link>https://flamboyant-mirzakhani-73a1c6.netlify.com/corporate-events/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Corporate-events on Ideas on Stage | Deliver amazing presentations</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Ideas on Stage</copyright>
    
	<atom:link href="https://flamboyant-mirzakhani-73a1c6.netlify.com/corporate-events/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Event Design</title>
      <link>https://flamboyant-mirzakhani-73a1c6.netlify.com/corporate-events/event-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://flamboyant-mirzakhani-73a1c6.netlify.com/corporate-events/event-design/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Good enough&amp;rdquo; is not good enough. Storify your event and turn it into a unique moment people will love and talk about. Turn a traditional corporate meeting into a powerful opportunity to engage the media, partners, employees, clients or suppliers.
Our Event Design team has made an impact with luxury firms, large pharmaceutical companies, industry leaders, public conferences and more.
Traditional conferences could achieve so much more with a little more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Master of Ceremonies</title>
      <link>https://flamboyant-mirzakhani-73a1c6.netlify.com/corporate-events/master-of-ceremonies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://flamboyant-mirzakhani-73a1c6.netlify.com/corporate-events/master-of-ceremonies/</guid>
      <description>A Master of Ceremonies for your event Our Master of Ceremonies will go beyond the traditional animator. They are entertainers, storytellers, showrunners, but it&amp;rsquo;s only the surface. They will immerse themselves in your event&amp;rsquo;s specific culture and add another dimension with their thought-provoking questions.
We have acted as Master of Ceremonies for numerous events for well-known companies such as Airbus, Microsoft, EDF and Pierre Fabre, as well as industry congresses and charity events, including COP21 and the World Social Forum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inspiring Keynotes</title>
      <link>https://flamboyant-mirzakhani-73a1c6.netlify.com/corporate-events/keynotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://flamboyant-mirzakhani-73a1c6.netlify.com/corporate-events/keynotes/</guid>
      <description>An inspiring keynote or workshop to wow your audience or motivate your team Whether you&amp;rsquo;re organising a conference, a team off-site event or a leadership retreat, your participants will love our entertaining, thought-provoking keynote presentations delivered by one of our experienced professional speakers.
Our speakers have delivered highly-appreciated keynote presentations at major conferences, leading companies and government agencies, as part of events and as off-site presentation workshops for company departments.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>