<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ideas on Stage | Deliver amazing presentations</title>
    <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ideas on Stage | Deliver amazing presentations</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© Ideas on Stage</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.ideasonstage.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Event Design</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/corporate-events/event-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/corporate-events/event-design/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Good enough&amp;rdquo; is not good enough. Storify your event and turn it into a unique moment people will love and talk about. Turn a traditional corporate meeting into a powerful opportunity to engage the media, partners, employees, clients or suppliers.
Our Event Design team has made an impact with luxury firms, large pharmaceutical companies, industry leaders, public conferences and more.
Traditional conferences could achieve so much more with a little more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PowerPoint Presentation Creation</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/presentation-creation-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/presentation-creation-service/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TEDx Coaching</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/tedx/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/tedx/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Business Presentation Revolution</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/training-workshops/business-presentation-revolution/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/training-workshops/business-presentation-revolution/</guid>
      <description>Train your teams to give TED-quality business presentations Presentations are everywhere in business, and most of them fail to reach their objectives - if they even have clear objectives. The Business Presentation Revolution tears up the conventional wisdom and provides trainees a simple new method for producing great presentations that hit the mark every time.
The Business Presentation Revolution, accompanied by the book of the same name, is based on our exclusive Presentation SCORE Method.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Master of Ceremonies</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/corporate-events/master-of-ceremonies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/corporate-events/master-of-ceremonies/</guid>
      <description>A Master of Ceremonies for your event Our Master of Ceremonies will go beyond the traditional animator. They are entertainers, storytellers, showrunners, but it&amp;rsquo;s only the surface. They will immerse themselves in your event&amp;rsquo;s specific culture and add another dimension with their thought-provoking questions.
We have acted as Master of Ceremonies for numerous events for well-known companies such as Airbus, Microsoft, EDF and Pierre Fabre, as well as industry congresses and charity events, including COP21 and the World Social Forum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public Speaking Coaching</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/public-speaking-coaching/public-speaking-coaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/public-speaking-coaching/public-speaking-coaching/</guid>
      <description>Lead from the stage Our exclusive Senior Team dedicated to the coaching of C-Level Executives will help you build your communication skills and move to the next stage of your career.
We help many Senior Executives from leading companies to master the arts of leading from the stage, speaking to the media, and inspiring their organisations. Our role is to build competence, confidence and comfort, and make you enjoy the challenge of leadership communication in all situations, from the boardroom to the auditorium.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Storytelling &amp; Copywriting</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/presentation-creation-agency/story-copywriting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/presentation-creation-agency/story-copywriting/</guid>
      <description>Why do we remember stories, yet forget yesterday’s presentation? Your document or presentation was received, but will it be read? Will it be remembered? And most importantly, will it be acted upon? Or, did you just waste your time &amp;hellip;
Each year companies create millions of presentations and documents. Yet most of them are boring, hard to understand and lack a clear purpose. The information is there, but it doesn’t stick; and so, it is quickly forgotten.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Women on Stage</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/training-workshops/women-on-stage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/training-workshops/women-on-stage/</guid>
      <description>What’s so unique for women in their challenge to speak up and be heard? Women, when they are speaking at the workplace, almost never get it “Just Right”. Some have advised women to be more assertive and to take on masculine attitudes. Others have suggested they should stick with their roles and act their more feminine attributes. In both cases, it doesn’t work. To quote the famous leading organization Catalyst for women and business, “women are damned if they do, doomed if they don’t”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inspiring Keynotes</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/corporate-events/keynotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/corporate-events/keynotes/</guid>
      <description>An inspiring keynote or workshop to wow your audience or motivate your team Whether you&amp;rsquo;re organising a conference, a team off-site event or a leadership retreat, your participants will love our entertaining, thought-provoking keynote presentations delivered by one of our experienced professional speakers.
Our speakers have delivered highly-appreciated keynote presentations at major conferences, leading companies and government agencies, as part of events and as off-site presentation workshops for company departments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Media Training</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/public-speaking-coaching/media-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/public-speaking-coaching/media-training/</guid>
      <description>Show the world the best version of yourself You come from make-up into a warm studio under hot lights, you take a seat opposite a journalist you hardly know, and after a brief greeting you are thrust via technology in front of a million pairs of eyes. Just as that thought hits your mind you’re being fired your first question, by someone who might not pull their punches. It suddenly feels even hotter under the lights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presentation Strategy</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/presentation-creation-agency/presentation-strategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/presentation-creation-agency/presentation-strategy/</guid>
      <description>Get a powerful presentation to sell your value and convince your audience, be they clients, partners or the media We will help you shape your communication strategy and turn it into a great story illustrated by amazing visuals. We can help you inspire and motivate your employees from the stage, launch high visibility products or services, win highly competitive sales, build a great corporate presentation and much more.
Our Strategic Presentations team combines Senior Executives with years of hands-on business experience, master storytellers and visual designers specialized in presentations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presentation Zen for Business</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/training-workshops/presentation-zen-for-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/training-workshops/presentation-zen-for-business/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Startup Pitch</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/training-workshops/pitch-for-startups/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/training-workshops/pitch-for-startups/</guid>
      <description>Everything comes down to the pitch As a startup you spend a lot of time testing, developing and improving your product and idea, but are you able to pitch effectively in front of an angel investor, venture capitalist or even to your clients?
Pitching is critical to the success of any startup, because no matter how great your idea, product or service, you still have to convince investors, clients and/or bankers to trust you with their money.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gender-Balanced Leadership</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/training-workshops/gender-balanced-leadership/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/training-workshops/gender-balanced-leadership/</guid>
      <description>Overcome gender bias and information silos in your company, and boost your performance. Diversity and inclusion are hot subjects for companies these days and for good reason: research is showing that diversity in teams makes them more creative, while diverse companies financially outperform their homogeneous counterparts by up to 35%. How do we create a hospitable space and foster empathy and collaboration to drive higher performance?
At Ideas on Stage, our programs produce concrete results that lead to shifts in thinking and actions, resulting in higher engagement and greater fulfillment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reboot your company</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/training-workshops/pitch-for-corporations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/training-workshops/pitch-for-corporations/</guid>
      <description>Everyone has an idea to pitch Many large corporations look at startups and wonder how they could be as agile, as creative and as innovative as these fast-moving entrepreneurs. Can you get long-time employees to think differently and adopt a startup mindset? Our answer is most definitely: Yes, we can!
Reboot Your Company is a half-day workshop, ideal for department meetings or team events, built using our many years of experience working with hundreds of startups, as well as our many blue-chip clients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TEDx Saclay – Worth all the Applause</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/12/01/8.-tedxsaclay/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/12/01/8.-tedxsaclay/</guid>
      <description>For the third year running, Ideas on Stage was very happy to partner with the TEDx Saclay conference, which took place this November 30, 2017 in the brand-new CentraleSupélec amphitheater at the Plateau de Saclay on the powerful theme of “Serving the Living”.
TEDx Saclay Keeping standards typically high, this year’s event boasted a rich program of speakers including a few notably prestigious guests such as Cédric Villani &amp;ndash; renowned mathematician and member of the French National Assembly &amp;ndash; as well as artists, scientists, students, entrepreneurs and even a Guinness World Record gamer (Kayane).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Women on Stage Workshop Returns Dec 7</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/10/30/7.-women-on-stage-workshop-returns-dec-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/10/30/7.-women-on-stage-workshop-returns-dec-7/</guid>
      <description>This December 7th in an elegant boardroom along the Champs-Elysée something powerful will take place: the beloved Women on Stage workshop will return by popular demand led by Marion Chapsal, Chief Learning Officer and Speaking Coach. Spaces are limited to allow space for each voice and leader to present and receive personalized feedback.
 Marion Chapsal
  For over 20 years, Marion&amp;rsquo;s work has helped leaders to strengthen their executive presence, enhance their presentation and communication skills, and promote gender-balanced leadership in everything she does.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EDF InnovDay UNITEP 2017</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/10/06/6.-supporting-edf-innovday-unitep-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/10/06/6.-supporting-edf-innovday-unitep-2017/</guid>
      <description>Innovation is at the heart of what keeps large companies competitive. This is why EDF (Electricity of France) UNITEP organized a challenge to promote and reward internal innovative projects.
For the fourth year in a row, Ideas on Stage collaborated with EDF to coach said Innovators. We helped each group build a strong and original three-minute presentation on their innovation.
True to our methodology, we worked on developing the four elements of an impactful presentation: message, story, visuals and speaking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Helping Startups Pitch for Social Good</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/10/04/5.-helping-startups-pitch-for-social-good-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/10/04/5.-helping-startups-pitch-for-social-good-news/</guid>
      <description>The Sport Social Business Lab, aka SSBL, is an incubator specialized in sport startups for the social good. It is part of the INCO network.
Sport startups are no different from other startups: without a good pitch, they don&amp;rsquo;t stand a chance to attract investors and grow. This is why the SSBL asked Ideas on Stage to animate a three-hour pitch workshop.
As an avid sportsman who has been active in the Startup ecosystem since 2010, cofounder Pierre Morsa was uniquely qualified to deliver this workshop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taking Female Leadership by the Reins</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/09/04/4.-taking-female-leadership-by-the-reins/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/09/04/4.-taking-female-leadership-by-the-reins/</guid>
      <description>This September, something special will take place at Wisteria Acres in British Columbia, and it’s not just time with the horses. From Friday September 29th through Sunday evening on the 1st of October, Marion Chapsal and her co-facilitator Evelyn McKelvie will guide eight willing and ready women on a journey to find &amp;ndash; or fine-tune &amp;ndash; their public voice and take the stage alongside, you guessed it, horses. They call this workshop and retreat &amp;ldquo;The Heroine&amp;rsquo;s Journey&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can Women Pitch As Well As Men?</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/09/01/2.-can-women-pitch-as-well-as-men/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/09/01/2.-can-women-pitch-as-well-as-men/</guid>
      <description>It’s a simple fact that most successful startups are run by men. Why? Firstly, there are more men than women who decide - or dare - to start companies. Secondly, men are more successful at raising funds than women, and even those women who do raise funds end up raising less, on average, than their male counterparts. Having spent two years playing in the Silicon Valley arena myself, I’ve seen this truth first hand both in California and now in France.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lost in Transition?</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/08/31/1.lost-in-transition/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/08/31/1.lost-in-transition/</guid>
      <description>This summer Ideas on Stage partnered up with the fine people at Set’Event to help a handful of such thoughtful and committed citizens to give impactful keynote presentations at the 15th annual ACIDD event, which took place August 28-29 in Bordeaux. This year’s theme? “Lost in Transition: the time of possibilities”.
This annual event is dedicated to exploring the skills and solutions necessary to live well in our emerging digital age across all sectors, from sustainable energy to food and agriculture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who teaches the Preachers?</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/08/29/3.-who-teaches-the-preachers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/08/29/3.-who-teaches-the-preachers/</guid>
      <description>It’s not only business leaders, salespeople and entrepreneurs who need to inspire their audiences. For thousands of years, many of the most talented speakers could be found not in a shop or office but in a place of worship.
Ask people which public speaker they most admire, and many will point to Rev. Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr.. He spoke powerfully and inspired his audiences, and of the well-known speakers of the last century he was certainly among the best.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/pierre-morsa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/pierre-morsa/</guid>
      <description>The best time to quit your consulting job and create a startup with zero Customers is when you are 40, at the top, with two young kids and a loan to reimburse for a Parisian apartment. Just close your eyes. Take a deep breath. Count to 10. And jump into the unknown.
Several years later, here I am, as the co-founding Partner and Creative Director of Ideas on Stage and enjoying every moment of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cookies</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/cookies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/cookies/</guid>
      <description>To make this site work properly, we sometimes place small data files called cookies on your device. Most big websites do this too.
What are cookies? A cookie is a small text file that a website saves on your computer or mobile device when you visit the site. It enables the website to remember your actions and preferences (such as login, language, font size and other display preferences) over a period of time, so you don’t have to keep re-entering them whenever you come back to the site or browse from one page to another.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/phil-waknell/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/phil-waknell/</guid>
      <description>Phil Waknell is one of Europe’s leading experts in the new art of presenting, and speaks regularly at major corporations and conferences about better business communication. He teaches business presenting at HEC Paris Executive Education, Europe’s leading executive business school, and is the author of The Business Presentation Revolution.
Phil has helped hundreds of entrepreneurs and TED(x) speakers to prepare and deliver high-impact presentations, as well as coaching leaders at many of Europe’s top companies, delivering seminars and workshops around the world, and acting as Master of Ceremonies for major international events.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/michael-rickwood/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/michael-rickwood/</guid>
      <description>Initially a classically trained actor with 12 years of experience on stage and screen, Michael swapped his passion for acting in favour of business communication and design. Before joining Ideas on Stage, in parallel to his acting career, Michael spent many years creating and delivering original presentation training courses for some of France’s biggest companies.
Today, apart from training and coaching executives from all sectors and industries and helping them develop content, Michael also coaches speakers at hugely successful TEDx and WikiStage conferences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/marion-chapsal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/marion-chapsal/</guid>
      <description>Marion Chapsal coaches leaders in executive presence, presentation skills and gender-balanced leadership.
Her clients know her as fun, caring and remarkably creative. One may even say she&amp;rsquo;s the Mary Poppins of executive coaching; turning work into play while delivering high-quality results.
For Women on Stage, she has created the Heroines’ Journey. Partnered with Equine coach Evelyn McKelvie in Vancouver, the two have designed unique leadership retreats for women executives to find a voice of their own, craft their #TEDlike talks and own their presence on stage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/joe-ross/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/joe-ross/</guid>
      <description>Joe is a highly experienced writer, communicator, and campaign strategy designer; he has taught business writing and communication at Ecole Polytechnique as well in several business schools. Having a wealth of experience in the public sector and business, he has served in the capacity of Chief of Policy and Senior Advisor to prominent institutions, foundations, and governments including The Tallberg Foundation in Stockholm; PlaNet Finance in Paris; and the City of San Diego, California.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/vanessa-querville/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/vanessa-querville/</guid>
      <description>After graduating in History from Paris Sorbonne and Trinity College in Dublin, Vanessa Querville worked as a publisher and book designer before joining the startup world and running the Microsoft Accelerator in Paris. There, she was in charge of recruitment, operations, helping startups with their pitches, and acting as a bridge between startups and Microsoft clients. She joined Ideas on Stage in 2015 as Chief Pitch Officer, helping fast-growing companies with killer pitches, and helping established companies to pitch just as well as tech startups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/rose-bloomfield/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/rose-bloomfield/</guid>
      <description>Born in Los Angeles, California, Rose Bloomfield grew up performing on stage and in front of the camera. Her first big role was interviewing film creatives as a Disney host, talent like Jerry Bruckheimer, Anne Hathaway and Nicolas Cage, which paved the unexpected road to her next large project as a principle on the socio-cultural F.X. documentary series, “Black. White.”
Following the project and before earning a degree in Cultural Anthropology at the University of California, Santa Cruz, Rose had been a hired speaker at over a dozen colleges across the United States on the topic of empathy and intercultural communication.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/ricardo-bonis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/ricardo-bonis/</guid>
      <description>Ricardo is the founder and manager of Ideas on Stage Spain, located in Barcelona. Combining more than 15 years of experience in executive roles in the telco industry and his experience teaching at the Escuela Politécnica de Ingeniería of the University of Oviedo, Ricardo knows first hand the challenging business environment and the importance of great presentation skills to thrive in it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/laura-diaz-de-entresotos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/laura-diaz-de-entresotos/</guid>
      <description>Laura is an experienced coach and communicator. Before joining Ideas on Stage, she worked as psychology therapist for more than 13 years. She earned a PhD in Psychology from University of Oviedo and EuroPsy certification. Her experience on therapy and coaching, as well as her ability to connect, are her foundations to help other people feel comfortable, gain confidence and perform to their best on stage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/edoardo-sala/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/edoardo-sala/</guid>
      <description>After his diploma in classical studies Edoardo followed his passion for the arts and the theatre.
He graduated at the Drama Centre London, one of the most prestigious Academies of Dramatic Art in Great Britain and worked for many years as a professional actor.
He then brought his knowledge of verbal, non-verbal communication and public speaking skills to the corporate world.
After an extensive experience as a Sales and Marketing Manager in the International luxury market he completed the Executive MBA at the MIP school of management of the Politecnico of Milan, where he focused on General and Innovation Management, Luxury Marketing, Digital and Social Media Marketing finding a balance between his artistical background and his managerial experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/dirk-haun/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/dirk-haun/</guid>
      <description>Coming from a background in software development and technology, Dirk has made it his mission to help people express and present their ideas. He is the co-organizer and speaker liaison at TEDxStuttgart and the author of “Presenting for Geeks”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/patricia-lane/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/patricia-lane/</guid>
      <description>Patricia Lane, a dual French &amp;amp; American national, holds advanced degrees in Political Science targeting the US-Europe-Asia triangle.
An intercultural communications specialist, she leads the Franco-American Quill, which provides creative copywriting, executive training, and cross-cultural strategic consulting. She has worked for clients such as Airbus, Groupe Bel, Aventis, McDonald’s Europe, Dalkia and Linkfluence, has taught at INALCO, and is a member of the SFT, IABC and Communication et Entreprise. Passionate about photography, she is rarely seen without her Nikon slung over her shoulder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/roberto-lalli/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/roberto-lalli/</guid>
      <description>Specialising in value-based leadership and marketing through storytelling, and speaking fluent German, Italian and English, Roberto coaches and trains executives around Europe to broaden their charismatic leadership skills and their storytelling expertise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/</guid>
      <description> We have assembled a multidisciplinary group of Presentation Experts from all around the world. Our backgrounds range from former business consultants to trained actors. </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>