<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>TEDx on Ideas on Stage</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/tedx/</link>
    <description>Recent content in TEDx on Ideas on Stage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© Ideas on Stage</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/tedx/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Top 5 TEDx Talks in number of views</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2020/03/30/2020-03-30-the-top-5-tedx-talks-in-number-of-views/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2020/03/30/2020-03-30-the-top-5-tedx-talks-in-number-of-views/</guid>
      <description>We worked with a lot of TEDx events over the years, and some of the talks have accumulated hundreds of thousands views, some even getting above the 1 million mark. Here are the top 5 talks of events we participated to, in number of views.
In fifth place we have Jean-Gabriel Causse, speaking at TEDx Dunkerque, with nearly 600,000 views. Color me shocked, but his is talk about the power of colors is full of interesting details.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If you want to be brief and to the point, prepare</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2020/02/04/2020-02-04-if-you-want-to-be-brief-and-to-the-point-prepare/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2020/02/04/2020-02-04-if-you-want-to-be-brief-and-to-the-point-prepare/</guid>
      <description>A few months ago I recorded an episode for our video channel “The Business Presentation Revolution.” Initially, my content was too long to fit in the 3 to 4 minutes running time that we had planned. Looking at my script, I realized that many sentences could be simplified, some details omitted, and the structure streamlined.
After several dry runs and rewrites, we finally managed to get the video down to 3 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life after TED: How to show up in the Post-TED world</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2020/01/07/2020-01-07-life-after-ted-how-to-show-up-in-the-post-ted-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2020/01/07/2020-01-07-life-after-ted-how-to-show-up-in-the-post-ted-world/</guid>
      <description>You know that mental image you have of what you think you should be like on stage? Yes, that one based upon a mash-up of some of your favorite TED speakers whom you are certain you’ll never be as good as. Well, forget it!
Welcome to the Post-TED style of authenticity centered presentation.
In my last article, Wash that TED right out of your head: New Post-TED presentation, we explored some of the foundational reasons which many are experiencing, and what I call, “TED-like style Fatigue”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Put your most nervous speakers early in the program</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2019/07/09/2019-07-09-put-your-most-nervous-speakers-early-in-the-program/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2019/07/09/2019-07-09-put-your-most-nervous-speakers-early-in-the-program/</guid>
      <description>One of the most stressful moments when speaking at an event is actually not during your presentation, but the hours before your presentation. To some speakers, the wait can be so stressful that they completely lose their presence. As mother nature didn&amp;rsquo;t give humans an appropriate instinctive response to face the stress of a presentation, they adopt one of the basic survival techniques for protection: they fight the public, they flee, or they &amp;ldquo;play dead&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Prezi failed at revolutionizing presentations</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2019/05/28/2019-05-28-why-prezi-failed-at-revolutionizing-presentations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2019/05/28/2019-05-28-why-prezi-failed-at-revolutionizing-presentations/</guid>
      <description>In 2009, the year when TED decided to launch its TEDx license program, Prezi was born out of the desire to overcome the limitations of tools like PowerPoint and Keynote. With its dramatic zooming and panning effects, it certainly did catch the eye of audiences worldwide when it was introduced. But its over-reliance on movement effects quickly became a visual nuisance, making the audience feel as if they had been on a boat caught in a category 10 hurricane.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 7 deadly sins of slide design</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2019/04/23/2019-04-23-the-7-deadly-sins-of-slide-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2019/04/23/2019-04-23-the-7-deadly-sins-of-slide-design/</guid>
      <description>This is a quick list of seven common problems that we see with slides created by non specialists. However they are relatively easy to spot, and you don’t have to be a graphic designer to avoid them. Read on and your next slides will look much better!
 Too much content. The goal is not to cover every single inch with content. It’s not because you have some space left at the bottom of the slide that you should put something there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The triple stakes of great presentations</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2019/03/05/2019-03-05-triple-stakes-of-great-presentations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2019/03/05/2019-03-05-triple-stakes-of-great-presentations/</guid>
      <description>The best presentations have three stakes, three reasons &amp;ldquo;why&amp;rdquo; they are important:
 The first stake is about you: why is the topic important for you? This is the reason you, and not somebody else, is on stage to deliver the presentation. The second stake is about your audience: why is it important for them? This is the reason why your audience is there to listen to you instead of doing something else.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 warning signs someone is not ready to speak at your TEDx event</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2019/02/26/2019-02-26-5-warning-signs-someone-is-not-ready-for-ted/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2019/02/26/2019-02-26-5-warning-signs-someone-is-not-ready-for-ted/</guid>
      <description>“Don’t worry, I’m experienced, I speak at conferences all the time!” How many times have we heard that sentence from speakers who never did a TEDx style talk, yet think that, because of experience, they can just wing it? For us, it’s not reassuring. Quite the opposite, it’s a clear warning sign that the speaker doesn’t really know what is expected of him. Here are five warning signs that give you clues that your speaker may not be ready to give a TEDx style talk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Business Can Learn From TED</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2018/04/10/2018-04-10-what-business-can-learn-from-ted/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2018/04/10/2018-04-10-what-business-can-learn-from-ted/</guid>
      <description>Today marks the start of TED2018, the latest edition of the world&amp;rsquo;s best-known modern conference. Participants in Vancouver will be treated to high-quality talks from well-prepared speakers, and will leave feeling energized and inspired.
Back in the office, you and your colleagues will no doubt be subjected to low-quality presentations from poorly-prepared speakers, and you will leave feeling bored and uninspired.
Business presentations are not TED talks. A board meeting is not a stage with a round red carpet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TEDx Saclay – Worth all the Applause</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2017/12/01/2017-12-01-tedxsaclay/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2017/12/01/2017-12-01-tedxsaclay/</guid>
      <description>For the third year running, Ideas on Stage was very happy to partner with the TEDx Saclay conference, which took place this November 30, 2017 in the brand-new CentraleSupélec amphitheater at the Plateau de Saclay on the powerful theme of “Serving the Living”.
TEDx Saclay Keeping standards typically high, this year’s event boasted a rich program of speakers including a few notably prestigious guests such as Cédric Villani &amp;ndash; renowned mathematician and member of the French National Assembly &amp;ndash; as well as artists, scientists, students, entrepreneurs and even a Guinness World Record gamer (Kayane).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TEDX McGill 2016</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/project/tedx-mcgill-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/project/tedx-mcgill-2016/</guid>
      <description>Ideas on Stage, the global presentation specialists have been coaching TED speakers over the last six years with great results. This year we not only coached but also partnered with TedX McGill which occurred earlier this month.
   View this post on Instagram        Check out our amazing location for our conference !
A post shared by TEDxMcGill (@tedxmcgill2016) on Mar 9, 2016 at 6:00am PST</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>