<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Presentation on Ideas on Stage</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/presentation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Presentation on Ideas on Stage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© Ideas on Stage</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/presentation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title> The 3 Magic Ingredients of Great Presentations</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2020/01/29/2020-01-29-the_3_magic_ingredients_of_great_presentations/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2020/01/29/2020-01-29-the_3_magic_ingredients_of_great_presentations/</guid>
      <description>Is there a perfect recipe for a successful presentation? No. Partly it depends on the audience and the context: a boardroom presentation shouldn’t look like a TED talk, even if the subject is the same. And different presentations at the same event – a conference, a demo day, an Executive Committee meeting – should also look different from each other, because otherwise none of them will stand out.
So if there is no magic formula, are there at least some key ingredients we should always include?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game of Thrones and the importance of the storyline</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2019/05/21/2019-05-21-game-of-thrones-and-the-importance-of-the-storyline/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2019/05/21/2019-05-21-game-of-thrones-and-the-importance-of-the-storyline/</guid>
      <description>By now, the last episode of the cult show Game of Thrones has aired. I haven’t seen it, and I didn’t want to see it before writing this article. Whether it accurately follows the storyline of the books or not is a moot point, because said book hasn’t been written yet. And it shows. I won’t spoil anything, don’t worry. But everyone noticed that the screenwriting of the seasons that could rely on George R.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why would people care about your presentation?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2019/05/14/2019-05-14-why-would-people-care-about-your-presentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2019/05/14/2019-05-14-why-would-people-care-about-your-presentation/</guid>
      <description>Why would people care about your product?
Why would people care about your service?
Why would people care about your project?
Why would people care about your career?
Why would people care about your investment?
Why would people care about your discovery?
Why would people care about your research?
Why would people care about your videos?
Why would people care about your book?
Why would people care about your ideas?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I presented at CES and all I got was a bunch of ungrateful tweets</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2019/01/15/2019-01-14-i-presented-at-ces-and-all-i-got-was-a-bunch-of-ungrateful-tweets/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2019/01/15/2019-01-14-i-presented-at-ces-and-all-i-got-was-a-bunch-of-ungrateful-tweets/</guid>
      <description>My colleague Ricardo pointed me to a tweet from Rene Ritchie, who was attending the conferences at CES.
Dear almost everyone on stage at CES: Pay ungodly amounts of money — anything you have to — to get WWDC speaker training ASAP.
Or go to Juilliard or the Royal Shakespeare Company for a month. Whatever works for you.
&amp;mdash; Rene Ritchie (@reneritchie) January 8, 2019  This tweet says:
&amp;ldquo;Dear almost everyone on stage at CES: Pay ungodly amounts of money — anything you have to — to get WWDC speaker training ASAP.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Inform, Transform</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2019/01/07/2019-01-07-dont-inform-transform/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2019/01/07/2019-01-07-dont-inform-transform/</guid>
      <description>Too many presentations aim only to inform, yet this is one thing oral presentations are particularly bad at &amp;ndash; we forget most of what we hear within 30 seconds.
If you want people to remember information, give them a document and a coffee, and time to read. Then you can answer their questions, discuss, agree on the next steps, and leave.
This is what happens in meetings at companies like Amazon and LinkedIn, where not only do meetings never have slides - they never have presentations.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>