<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Corporate Communication on Ideas on Stage</title>
    <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/corporate-communication/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Corporate Communication on Ideas on Stage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© Ideas on Stage 2015 - </copyright><atom:link href="https://www.ideasonstage.com/corporate-communication/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Presentation Strategy</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/services/communication-consulting/communication-strategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/services/communication-consulting/communication-strategy/</guid>
      <description>Get a powerful presentation to sell your value and convince your audience, be they clients, partners or the media We will help you shape your communication strategy and turn it into a great story illustrated by amazing visuals. We can help you inspire and motivate your employees from the stage, launch high visibility products or services, win highly competitive sales, build a great corporate presentation and much more.
Our Strategic Presentations team combines Senior Executives with years of hands-on business experience, master storytellers and visual designers specialized in presentations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Storytelling &amp; Copywriting</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/services/communication-consulting/story-copywriting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/services/communication-consulting/story-copywriting/</guid>
      <description>Why do we remember stories, yet forget yesterday’s presentation? Your document or presentation was received, but will it be read? Will it be remembered? And most importantly, will it be acted upon? Or, did you just waste your time . . .
Each year companies create millions of presentations and documents. Yet most of them are boring, hard to understand and lack a clear purpose. The information is there, but it doesn’t stick; and so, it is quickly forgotten.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Audience Transformation Roadmap™</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/services/communication-consulting/audience-transformation-roadmap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/services/communication-consulting/audience-transformation-roadmap/</guid>
      <description>Most people use presentations to share information, which is a terrible waste of everybody’s time because we forget most of what we hear very quickly.
If you want to share information, give people a written document, and quiet time to read it – and then by all means discuss what you have all read. This is how Amazon runs their meetings, and it works because that’s how human brains work. Meetings that might have taken two hours end up taking 25-30 minutes, even with 10 minutes of quiet reading at the start.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
