<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Presentations on Presentation Creation | Public Speaking Coaching and Training | Ideas on Stage</title>
    <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/tags/presentations/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Presentations on Presentation Creation | Public Speaking Coaching and Training | Ideas on Stage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© Ideas on Stage</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.ideasonstage.com/tags/presentations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to steal the show</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/01/29/2019-01-29-how-to-steal-the-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/01/29/2019-01-29-how-to-steal-the-show/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks ago, Ideas on Stage had the privilege of organizing a sales presentation training for Krauthammer at Dolce La Hulpe, close to Brussels in Belgium. For us, delivering a training for dozens of senior people at Krauthammer, one of the world’s most respected sales and management training companies, felt like designing something for Jonathan Ive, Apple’s legendary designer: a bit intimidating but incredibly exciting.
The training met with great success, and it was fantastic to work with such talented people, but what I will remember most are two presentations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What presentation lessons can we learn from Apple’s profit warning?</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/01/08/2019-01-07-what-presentation-lessons-can-we-learn-from-apples-profit-warning/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/01/08/2019-01-07-what-presentation-lessons-can-we-learn-from-apples-profit-warning/</guid>
      <description>By now, you’ve probably heard that Apple was doomed. Last Wednesday they released a profit warning press release, followed by an interview with CEO Tim Cook.
I’m all too aware of Apple’s previous profit warning. Back in the nineties, after Steve Jobs returned to Apple and a Saudi prince (whose name I forget) bought a lot of Apple shares, I decided that I would be a smart investor and I bought Apple shares too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 presentation lessons from The Darkest Hour</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2018/02/16/2018-02-16-the-darkest-hour-presentation-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2018/02/16/2018-02-16-the-darkest-hour-presentation-lessons/</guid>
      <description>Have you seen Gary Oldman in his interpretation of Churchill in the latest biopic by Joe Wright? If you have not, please go. It’s jaw-dropping. His outstanding performance may very soon win him an Oscar. You will enjoy some of the finest acting and also benefit from precious presentation lessons from the Master Orator.
Here are 3 takeaways from the movie, which you can immediately apply for your next keynote, sales meeting or investor pitch.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>