<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Training &amp; Workshops on Ideas on Stage</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/presentations-training/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Training &amp; Workshops on Ideas on Stage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© Ideas on Stage</copyright>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/presentations-training/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Business Presentation Revolution Training</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/presentations-training/the-business-presentation-revolution/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/presentations-training/the-business-presentation-revolution/</guid>
      <description>Train your teams to give TED-quality business presentations Presentations are everywhere in business, and most of them fail to reach their objectives - if they even have clear objectives. The Business Presentation Revolution tears up the conventional wisdom and provides trainees a simple new method for producing great presentations that hit the mark every time.
The Business Presentation Revolution, accompanied by the book of the same name, is based on our exclusive Presentation SCORE Method.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presentation Zen for Business</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/presentations-training/presentation-zen-for-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/presentations-training/presentation-zen-for-business/</guid>
      <description>The approach that revolutionized presentations all over the world Garr Reynolds redefined the rules for business presentations in his best-selling book Presentation Zen. A leading author, designer, former manager at Apple and professor based in Japan, he began the Presentation Zen blog in 2005, and published the first edition of the Presentation Zen book in 2007, followed by the highly successful Presentation Zen Design and The Naked Presenter.
Garr’s approach takes lessons and principles from Japanese culture, particularly restraint, simplicity and naturalness, and applies them to typical presentations given in conferences and the workplace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reboot your company</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/presentations-training/pitch-for-corporations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/presentations-training/pitch-for-corporations/</guid>
      <description>Everyone has an idea to pitch Many large corporations look at startups and wonder how they could be as agile, as creative and as innovative as these fast-moving entrepreneurs. Can you get long-time employees to think differently and adopt a startup mindset? Our answer is most definitely: Yes, we can!
Reboot Your Company is a half-day workshop, ideal for department meetings or team events, built using our many years of experience working with hundreds of startups, as well as our many blue-chip clients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Startups on Stage</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/presentations-training/pitch-for-startups/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/presentations-training/pitch-for-startups/</guid>
      <description>Everything comes down to the pitch As a startup you spend a lot of time testing, developing and improving your product and idea, but are you able to pitch effectively in front of an angel investor, venture capitalist or even to your clients?
Pitching is critical to the success of any startup, because no matter how great your idea, product or service, you still have to convince investors, clients and/or bankers to trust you with their money.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virtual Meeting Revolution Webinars</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/presentations-training/webinars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/presentations-training/webinars/</guid>
      <description>Virtual Meeting Revolution - Free Webinar Series We’re all facing a complex, unprecedented situation, and those of us who aren’t used to working remotely may feel disconnected, isolated, or lost. Wouldn’t it be great if every team could use virtual meetings to keep a sense of community and connection?
Stop and think about that for a moment. Meetings? Most physical meetings are a waste of time and energy, and now that many of us are working from home, we’re finding that too many virtual meetings have the same problem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virtual Meetings Revolution Training</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/presentations-training/virtual-meetings-revolution/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/presentations-training/virtual-meetings-revolution/</guid>
      <description>Keep the Human Factor With all of this effort to stay safe and healthy, we don’t want to fall into isolation. Two big risks in remote work, as we well know, is feeling disconnected and demotivated. So how do we make our meetings a place of human connection even when we’re a screen apart?
Firstly, don’t cut all water-cooler talk. Consider starting your meeting with a quick round of check-ins: “How is everyone doing?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Women on Stage 2.0</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/presentations-training/women-on-stage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/presentations-training/women-on-stage/</guid>
      <description>Women on Stage 2.0 is a public speaking and professional development workshop dedicated to women leaders and executives who want to speak up, inspire and present with confidence.
To organize an internal workshop please contact us through the form below.
Click here to read full event details -- Authenticity. Confidence. Leadership. In this professional development training participants will learn the fundamentals of what makes a successful presentation while addressing the specific challenges women face when speaking up.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>