<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Training &amp; Workshops on Ideas on Stage</title>
    <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/presentations-training/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Training &amp; Workshops on Ideas on Stage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© Ideas on Stage 2015 - </copyright><atom:link href="https://www.ideasonstage.com/presentations-training/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Business Presentation Revolution Training</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/presentations-training/the-business-presentation-revolution/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/presentations-training/the-business-presentation-revolution/</guid>
      <description>Train your teams to give TED-quality business presentations Presentations are everywhere in business, and most of them fail to reach their objectives - if they even have clear objectives. The Business Presentation Revolution tears up the conventional wisdom and provides trainees a simple new method for producing great presentations that hit the mark every time.
The Business Presentation Revolution, accompanied by the book of the same name, is based on our exclusive Presentation SCORE Method.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reboot your company</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/presentations-training/pitch-for-corporations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/presentations-training/pitch-for-corporations/</guid>
      <description>Everyone has an idea to pitch Many large corporations look at startups and wonder how they could be as agile, as creative and as innovative as these fast-moving entrepreneurs. Can you get long-time employees to think differently and adopt a startup mindset? Our answer is most definitely: Yes, we can!
Reboot Your Company is a half-day workshop, ideal for department meetings or team events, built using our many years of experience working with hundreds of startups, as well as our many blue-chip clients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Startups on Stage</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/presentations-training/pitch-for-startups/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/presentations-training/pitch-for-startups/</guid>
      <description>Everything comes down to the pitch As a startup you spend a lot of time testing, developing and improving your product and idea, but are you able to pitch effectively in front of an angel investor, venture capitalist or even to your clients?
Pitching is critical to the success of any startup, because no matter how great your idea, product or service, you still have to convince investors, clients and/or bankers to trust you with their money.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
