<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tedx on Presentation Creation | Public Speaking Coaching and Training | Ideas on Stage</title>
    <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/tags/tedx/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tedx on Presentation Creation | Public Speaking Coaching and Training | Ideas on Stage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© Ideas on Stage</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.ideasonstage.com/tags/tedx/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The triple stakes of great presentations</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/03/05/2019-03-05-triple-stakes-of-great-presentations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/03/05/2019-03-05-triple-stakes-of-great-presentations/</guid>
      <description>The best presentations have three stakes, three reasons &amp;ldquo;why&amp;rdquo; they are important:
 The first stake is about you: why is the topic important for you? This is the reason you, and not somebody else, is on stage to deliver the presentation. The second stake is about your audience: why is it important for them? This is the reason why your audience is there to listen to you instead of doing something else.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 warning signs someone is not ready to speak at your TEDx event</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/02/26/2019-02-26-5-warning-signs-someone-is-not-ready-for-ted/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/02/26/2019-02-26-5-warning-signs-someone-is-not-ready-for-ted/</guid>
      <description>“Don’t worry, I’m experienced, I speak at conferences all the time!” How many times have we heard that sentence from speakers who never did a TEDx style talk, yet think that, because of experience, they can just wing it? For us, it’s not reassuring. Quite the opposite, it’s a clear warning sign that the speaker doesn’t really know what is expected of him. Here are five warning signs that give you clues that your speaker may not be ready to give a TEDx style talk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Business Can Learn From TED</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2018/04/10/2018-04-10-what-business-can-learn-from-ted/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2018/04/10/2018-04-10-what-business-can-learn-from-ted/</guid>
      <description>Today marks the start of TED2018, the latest edition of the world&amp;rsquo;s best-known modern conference. Participants in Vancouver will be treated to high-quality talks from well-prepared speakers, and will leave feeling energized and inspired.
Back in the office, you and your colleagues will no doubt be subjected to low-quality presentations from poorly-prepared speakers, and you will leave feeling bored and uninspired.
Business presentations are not TED talks. A board meeting is not a stage with a round red carpet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TEDx Saclay – Worth all the Applause</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/12/01/2017-12-01-tedxsaclay/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/12/01/2017-12-01-tedxsaclay/</guid>
      <description>For the third year running, Ideas on Stage was very happy to partner with the TEDx Saclay conference, which took place this November 30, 2017 in the brand-new CentraleSupélec amphitheater at the Plateau de Saclay on the powerful theme of “Serving the Living”.
TEDx Saclay Keeping standards typically high, this year’s event boasted a rich program of speakers including a few notably prestigious guests such as Cédric Villani &amp;ndash; renowned mathematician and member of the French National Assembly &amp;ndash; as well as artists, scientists, students, entrepreneurs and even a Guinness World Record gamer (Kayane).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>