<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tedx on Presentation Creation Agency | Public Speaking Coaching and Training | Ideas on Stage</title>
    <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/tags/tedx/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tedx on Presentation Creation Agency | Public Speaking Coaching and Training | Ideas on Stage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© Ideas on Stage</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.ideasonstage.com/tags/tedx/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What Business Can Learn From TED</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2018/04/10/2018-04-10-what-business-can-learn-from-ted/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2018/04/10/2018-04-10-what-business-can-learn-from-ted/</guid>
      <description>Today marks the start of TED2018, the latest edition of the world&amp;rsquo;s best-known modern conference. Participants in Vancouver will be treated to high-quality talks from well-prepared speakers, and will leave feeling energized and inspired.
Back in the office, you and your colleagues will no doubt be subjected to low-quality presentations from poorly-prepared speakers, and you will leave feeling bored and uninspired.
Business presentations are not TED talks. A board meeting is not a stage with a round red carpet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TEDx Saclay – Worth all the Applause</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/12/01/8.-tedxsaclay/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/12/01/8.-tedxsaclay/</guid>
      <description>For the third year running, Ideas on Stage was very happy to partner with the TEDx Saclay conference, which took place this November 30, 2017 in the brand-new CentraleSupélec amphitheater at the Plateau de Saclay on the powerful theme of “Serving the Living”.
TEDx Saclay Keeping standards typically high, this year’s event boasted a rich program of speakers including a few notably prestigious guests such as Cédric Villani &amp;ndash; renowned mathematician and member of the French National Assembly &amp;ndash; as well as artists, scientists, students, entrepreneurs and even a Guinness World Record gamer (Kayane).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>