<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Services on Ideas on Stage</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Services on Ideas on Stage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© Ideas on Stage</copyright>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Online Work Community</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/from-office-to-remote-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/from-office-to-remote-work/</guid>
      <description>This service will help you create an attractive remote-based work environment for your employees. We will create an online work community whose benefits will have long-lasting positive effects on the productivity and morale of your workforce.
Propelled into a remote work environment, managers and employees will instinctively try to replicate their traditional work environment. But they soon realize the differences: no face-to-face meetings, no informal talk at the coffee machine, impossibility to check what every employee does every single minute.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PowerPoint Presentation Design Agency</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/services/powerpoint-presentation-design-agency/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/services/powerpoint-presentation-design-agency/</guid>
      <description>From great idea to great presentation The core of Ideas on Stage’s mission is to help leaders to communicate effectively. In a world where most business presentations fail even to keep audiences awake, it is all the more important to be the exceptional presenter whom everyone remembers.
Whether your clients are preparing for a TED talk, an important sales pitch or a vital board meeting, our experienced specialists will take them through our pSCORE™ presentation generation method, proven in thousands of important presentations and taught at leading business schools like HEC Paris.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>