<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Our Guides on Ideas on Stage</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/guides/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Our Guides on Ideas on Stage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© Ideas on Stage</copyright>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/guides/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to deliver presentations remotely</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/how-to-deliver-presentations-remotely/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/how-to-deliver-presentations-remotely/</guid>
      <description>What you need to deliver great presentations remotely: gear, software, setup, animation. We wrote this guide based on ten years of experience delivering professional remote presentations to clients. Note: we don’t earn any money on the software or hardware we recommend in this article. We recommend them based on our experience, but there are many other solutions that might work well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The event organizer&#39;s guide</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/event-organizer-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/event-organizer-guide/</guid>
      <description>This guide will give you the keys to organize a successful business event. Each step of the organization process is explained. Eliminate unforeseen circumstances, omissions and last-minute panic and turn event management into a strategic asset for your company. Events come in all shapes and sizes, but the principles of organization are always the same. The key to a successful event is making sure it’s well planned and that it meets all of your targeted expectations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Women, a series of kakemonos celebrating women who changed the world</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/women/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/women/</guid>
      <description>We created a series of kakemonos to celebrate women who changed the world. You can freely download and print them for your own use. All images are public domain. If you want to print them, the recommended format is 80 cm x 200 cm (approx. 31.49 inches by 78.7 inches) or smaller keeping the same proportions (e.g. 40 cm x  100 cm). The color space is FOGRA 39 and the bleed is 1 mm on every side.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>