<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Paris on Ideas on Stage | Deliver amazing presentations</title>
    <link>https://flamboyant-mirzakhani-73a1c6.netlify.com/tags/paris/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Paris on Ideas on Stage | Deliver amazing presentations</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Ideas on Stage</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://flamboyant-mirzakhani-73a1c6.netlify.com/tags/paris/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Women on Stage Workshop Returns Dec 7</title>
      <link>https://flamboyant-mirzakhani-73a1c6.netlify.com/news/2017/10/30/7.-women-on-stage-workshop-returns-dec-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://flamboyant-mirzakhani-73a1c6.netlify.com/news/2017/10/30/7.-women-on-stage-workshop-returns-dec-7/</guid>
      <description>This December 7th in an elegant boardroom along the Champs-Elysée something powerful will take place: the beloved Women on Stage workshop will return by popular demand led by Marion Chapsal, Chief Learning Officer and Speaking Coach. Spaces are limited to allow space for each voice and leader to present and receive personalized feedback.
 Marion Chapsal
  For over 20 years, Marion&amp;rsquo;s work has helped leaders to strengthen their executive presence, enhance their presentation and communication skills, and promote gender-balanced leadership in everything she does.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EDF InnovDay UNITEP 2017</title>
      <link>https://flamboyant-mirzakhani-73a1c6.netlify.com/news/2017/10/06/6.-supporting-edf-innovday-unitep-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://flamboyant-mirzakhani-73a1c6.netlify.com/news/2017/10/06/6.-supporting-edf-innovday-unitep-2017/</guid>
      <description>Innovation is at the heart of what keeps large companies competitive. This is why EDF (Electricity of France) UNITEP organized a challenge to promote and reward internal innovative projects.
For the fourth year in a row, Ideas on Stage collaborated with EDF to coach said Innovators. We helped each group build a strong and original three-minute presentation on their innovation.
True to our methodology, we worked on developing the four elements of an impactful presentation: message, story, visuals and speaking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Helping Startups Pitch for Social Good</title>
      <link>https://flamboyant-mirzakhani-73a1c6.netlify.com/news/2017/10/04/5.-helping-startups-pitch-for-social-good-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://flamboyant-mirzakhani-73a1c6.netlify.com/news/2017/10/04/5.-helping-startups-pitch-for-social-good-news/</guid>
      <description>The Sport Social Business Lab, aka SSBL, is an incubator specialized in sport startups for the social good. It is part of the INCO network.
Sport startups are no different from other startups: without a good pitch, they don&amp;rsquo;t stand a chance to attract investors and grow. This is why the SSBL asked Ideas on Stage to animate a three-hour pitch workshop.
As an avid sportsman who has been active in the Startup ecosystem since 2010, cofounder Pierre Morsa was uniquely qualified to deliver this workshop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can Women Pitch As Well As Men?</title>
      <link>https://flamboyant-mirzakhani-73a1c6.netlify.com/news/2017/09/01/2.-can-women-pitch-as-well-as-men/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://flamboyant-mirzakhani-73a1c6.netlify.com/news/2017/09/01/2.-can-women-pitch-as-well-as-men/</guid>
      <description>It’s a simple fact that most successful startups are run by men. Why? Firstly, there are more men than women who decide - or dare - to start companies. Secondly, men are more successful at raising funds than women, and even those women who do raise funds end up raising less, on average, than their male counterparts. Having spent two years playing in the Silicon Valley arena myself, I’ve seen this truth first hand both in California and now in France.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>