<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Podcasts on Ideas on Stage</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/podcasts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Podcasts on Ideas on Stage</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© Ideas on Stage 2010 - </copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/podcasts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Jeremy Connell-Waite on How to Tell Better Stories - The Ideas on Stage Podcast</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2024/06/12/2024-06-12-jeremy_connell-waite_on_how_to_tell_better_stories_-_the_ideas_on_stage_podcast/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2024/06/12/2024-06-12-jeremy_connell-waite_on_how_to_tell_better_stories_-_the_ideas_on_stage_podcast/</guid>
      <description>In this episode of the Ideas on Stage podcast we spoke with Jeremy Connell-Waite.&#xA;Jeremy Connell-Waite is passionate about helping others to tell better stories, especially executives and future business leaders in the tech industry. He works as a Communications Designer at IBM where he builds narratives for clients around emerging technologies, write speeches for senior executives and lead a performance coaching program for consultants called Impact Storytelling.&#xA;In this episode we talked about how to tell better business stories.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phil Waknell on How to Captivate a Million Minds - The Ideas on Stage Podcast</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2024/05/15/2024-05-15-phil_waknell_on_how_to_captivate_a_million_minds_-_the_ideas_on_stage_podcast_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2024/05/15/2024-05-15-phil_waknell_on_how_to_captivate_a_million_minds_-_the_ideas_on_stage_podcast_1/</guid>
      <description>In this episode of the Ideas on Stage podcast we spoke with our very own Phil Waknell.&#xA;Phil Waknell is one of Europe’s leading experts in the new art of presenting, and speaks regularly at major corporations and conferences about better business communication. He teaches business presenting at HEC Paris Executive Education, Europe’s leading executive business school, and is the author of Business Presentation Revolution.&#xA;Phil has helped hundreds of entrepreneurs and TED(x) speakers to prepare and deliver high-impact presentations, as well as coaching leaders at many of Europe’s top companies, delivering seminars and workshops around the world, and acting as Master of Ceremonies for major international events.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jack Appleman on Business Writing - The Ideas on Stage Podcast</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2024/03/13/2024-03-13-jack_appleman_on_business_writing_-_the_ideas_on_stage_podcast/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2024/03/13/2024-03-13-jack_appleman_on_business_writing_-_the_ideas_on_stage_podcast/</guid>
      <description>In this episode of the Ideas on Stage podcast we spoke with Jack Appleman. Jack Appleman, prominent business writing coach, professor and author of 10 Steps to Successful Business Writing—2nd edition (2018, ATD Press), is driven by the belief that working professionals can dramatically improve their writing by following straightforward techniques. His writing training for organizations including Bayer, Wells Fargo and HBO have helped thousands of individuals achieve better results from their writing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nicole Lowenbraun on Adaptive Listening - The Ideas on Stage Podcast</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2024/02/14/2024-02-14-nicole_lowenbraun_on_adaptive_listening_-_the_ideas_on_stage_podcast/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2024/02/14/2024-02-14-nicole_lowenbraun_on_adaptive_listening_-_the_ideas_on_stage_podcast/</guid>
      <description>In this episode of the Ideas on Stage podcast we spoke with Nicole Lowenbraun.&#xA;Nicole offers a unique perspective on why what you say and how you say it matters, because she’s equal parts speech-language pathologist and business communication expert. Nicole has coached and written for thousands of clients, most of whom top the Fortune 100, with a focus on helping clients find their most authentic and powerful voice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matt Abrahams on Spontaneous Speaking - The Ideas on Stage Podcast</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2024/01/17/2024-01-17-matt_abrahams_on_spontaneous_speaking_-_the_ideas_on_stage_podcast/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2024/01/17/2024-01-17-matt_abrahams_on_spontaneous_speaking_-_the_ideas_on_stage_podcast/</guid>
      <description>In this episode of the Ideas on Stage podcast we spoke with Matt Abrahams. Matt Abrahams is a leading expert in communication with decades of experience as an educator, author, podcast host, and coach. As a Lecturer in Organizational Behavior at Stanford University’s Graduate School of Business, he teaches popular classes in strategic communication and effective virtual presenting. He received Stanford GSB’s Alumni Teaching Award in recognition of his teaching students around the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John Roussot on Personal Mastery and Professional Excellence - The Ideas on Stage Podcast</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2023/12/13/2023-12-13-john_roussot_on_personal_mastery_and_professional_excellence_-_the_ideas_on_stage_podcast/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2023/12/13/2023-12-13-john_roussot_on_personal_mastery_and_professional_excellence_-_the_ideas_on_stage_podcast/</guid>
      <description>In this episode of the Ideas on Stage podcast we spoke with John Roussot. John Roussot is the founder and CEO of FiiT4GROWTH, a renowned business coaching and online training platform that helps individuals and organisations unlock their full potential. He has more than twenty-two years of experience in coaching, mentoring and guiding people towards personal and professional success, establishing himself as a multi-award-winning business coach and leadership development trainer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seth Godin on How to Get Your Ideas to Spread – The Ideas on Stage Podcast</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2023/06/19/2023-06-19-seth_godin_on_how_to_get_your_ideas_to_spread_the_ideas_on_stage_podcast/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2023/06/19/2023-06-19-seth_godin_on_how_to_get_your_ideas_to_spread_the_ideas_on_stage_podcast/</guid>
      <description>In this episode of the Ideas on Stage podcast we spoke with the legendary Seth Godin. Seth Godin is the author of 20 books that have been bestsellers around the world and have been translated into more than 35 languages. He’s also the founder of the altMBA and The Akimbo Workshops, online seminars that have transformed the work of thousands of people.&#xA;He writes about the post-industrial revolution, the way ideas spread, marketing, quitting, leadership and most of all, changing everything.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
