<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Business Presentation Revolution on Ideas on Stage</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/revolution/</link>
    <description>Recent content in The Business Presentation Revolution on Ideas on Stage</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© Ideas on Stage 2010 - </copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/revolution/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>4 Tempos</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/revolution/episode-00010/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/revolution/episode-00010/</guid>
      <description>Rose: Hi, welcome to the Business Presentation Revolution podcast. I’ve just given the most, I mean most boring presentation of my life and I need to learn how to give a more interesting and captivating presentation.&#xA;Michael: So what happened?&#xA;Rose: I just gave the most boring presentation of my life.&#xA;Michael: How? What did people say?&#xA;Rose: Something about my voice. And they don’t care what I had to say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Once upon a business story</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/revolution/episode-00009/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/revolution/episode-00009/</guid>
      <description>Rose: What a great story.&#xA;Pierre: That was a classic.&#xA;Rose: Is there a way we can take the magic of storytelling in film and apply it to business?&#xA;Pierre: Let&amp;rsquo;s compare the ingredients of traditional storytelling and business storytelling.&#xA;Rose: Let&amp;rsquo;s roll.&#xA;Rose: We&amp;rsquo;re gonna take the five key ingredients of traditional storytelling, like in film, and apply it to business. We have: the setting, characters, conflict, resolution, and plot.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazing Events</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/revolution/episode-00008/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/revolution/episode-00008/</guid>
      <description>Rose: Most people think that a great event is one that fits everything into the agenda. The more the better. Well, we want to share that less is more, especially when it comes to presentations. Today I&amp;rsquo;m gonna have three tips for you on how to create an amazing business event by making it active.&#xA;Tip 1: Only use presentations when necessary. Michael: Hey Rose, what are you reading there?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Showtime Stress</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/revolution/episode-00007/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/revolution/episode-00007/</guid>
      <description>Transcript Rose: OK. Yes. Got it. Thanks. Bye.&#xA;Rose: Welcome to the Business Presentation Revolution. I&amp;rsquo;m super stressed today because I have a presentation at the end of the day that I&amp;rsquo;m not prepared for. So I&amp;rsquo;ve called my coach to help turn this stress into success.&#xA;Michael: Hey Rose, what&amp;rsquo;s up?&#xA;Rose: Michael, I have a presentation at the end of the day. I helped prepare it with my colleagues so I know the slides but I don&amp;rsquo;t know what to do.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gestures</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/revolution/episode-00006/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/revolution/episode-00006/</guid>
      <description>Transcript Welcome to The Business Presentation Revolution! I&amp;rsquo;m here with my colleague Michael Rickwood who&amp;rsquo;s going to be sharing with us what to do with our bodies while presenting.&#xA;So Michael, our clients regularly ask us: “What do I do with my body, my hands, my face while presenting?” What do you tell your clients?&#xA;Rose, what you&amp;rsquo;re talking about is gestures and we all need to use them on stage, but to be better at gestures it&amp;rsquo;s good to know about the four different types of gestures that we can use to be more effective communicators on stage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slide Success</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/revolution/episode-00005/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/revolution/episode-00005/</guid>
      <description>Powerful visuals come from powerful messages and clear visual ideas. But sometimes slides aren’t necessary. The days of ‘Death by PowerPoint®’ are over. Take 5 to discover the 3 simple steps to slide success that will help you achieve your objectives—and leave your audience wanting more—in our new episode of The Business Presentation Revolution podcast, with presentation experts Rose Bloomfield and Phil Waknell.&#xA;Transcript Rose: [00:00:00] Welcome to The Business Presentation Revolution: your colorful cocktail of presentation goodness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carts and Horses</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/revolution/episode-00004/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/revolution/episode-00004/</guid>
      <description>If you just found out you need to give a 15-minute presentation tomorrow, how would you prepare? Would you put the cart before the horse? Most people do. But fear not, the latest episode of the Business Presentation Revolution Podcast is here to help! Take just five minutes to learn about the simple change that will put the horse before the cart, and you in the driver’s seat. Join Rose as she discusses a foolproof process to prepare a presentation with Phil Waknell, Co-Founder and Chief Inspiration Officer at Ideas on Stage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your audience</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/revolution/episode-00003/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/revolution/episode-00003/</guid>
      <description>The secret ingredient in any presentation is Your Audience. Don’t forget to ask these essential questions to be sure you don’t fail before you’ve even started to speak.&#xA;Transcript Phil: [00:00:00] Welcome to The Business Presentation Revolution, your double espresso of presentation know-how.&#xA;Rose: [00:00:05] This episode is all about the magic ingredient in any presentation: Your Audience.&#xA;Phil: [00:00:12] So Rose, when I ask people what they hate most about presentations, one thing that comes up all the time is that they hate it when they&amp;rsquo;re receiving a standard presentation, which just doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem like it is suited to that audience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overcoming nerves</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/revolution/episode-00002/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/revolution/episode-00002/</guid>
      <description>Rose asks Phil how to overcome your fear before a big presentation, and turn it into positive energy on stage. Discover our Chief Inspiration Officer&amp;rsquo;s tips to find your inner zen before a big event.&#xA;Transcript Rose: Welcome to The Business Presentation Revolution, your calming cup of presentation tea. Phil, is everything okay?&#xA;Phil: I&amp;rsquo;m just really feeling kind of nervous. I just don&amp;rsquo;t think I&amp;rsquo;m properly prepared for today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transformation</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/revolution/episode-00001/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/revolution/episode-00001/</guid>
      <description>Presentations are for transformation, not information. Learn the golden simple question to ask yourself to make your presentation a success. Guest: Phil Waknell&#xA;Transcript Rose: [00:00:00] Welcome to The Business Presentation Revolution, your regular cup of presentation inspiration.&#xA;Phil: [00:00:07] Today we&amp;rsquo;ll be looking at why presentation should rhyme not with Information but with Transformation.&#xA;Rose: [00:00:16] So Phil, you said that presentations should rhyme with transformation instead of information. What do you mean by that?</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
