<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Body language on Ideas on Stage</title>
    <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/tags/body-language/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Body language on Ideas on Stage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© Ideas on Stage 2015 - </copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.ideasonstage.com/tags/body-language/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Use eye contact to stop moving around on stage</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/10/01/2019-10-01-use-eye-contact-to-stop-moving-around-on-stage/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/10/01/2019-10-01-use-eye-contact-to-stop-moving-around-on-stage/</guid>
      <description>Moving with purpose on stage is good. Moving around aimlessly is not. It’s what we call derivative actions, things that we do unconsciously that betray our stress, lack of confidence or lack of preparation. Luckily, it’s very easy to stop parasitic movements, but the solution sounds counterintuitive: use eye contact to &amp;ldquo;anchor&amp;rdquo; yourself on the ground.
Yes, that’s right. Making eye contact with your audience will stabilise your attention and will prevent your feet from moving you around the stage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Should I move on stage when speaking?</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/06/25/2019-06-25-should-i-move-on-stage-when-speaking/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/06/25/2019-06-25-should-i-move-on-stage-when-speaking/</guid>
      <description>Should we move on stage when speaking, to avoid looking static? Or should we stay put on our feet, avoiding any unnecessary movements? Strangely, if we ask different coaches, we&amp;rsquo;re likely to get different answers. I remember meeting several coaches who followed classical theatre training at &amp;ldquo;La Comédie Française&amp;rdquo;, and they would recommend that you don&amp;rsquo;t move on stage when you&amp;rsquo;re speaking. I also remember other coaches telling startup pitchers that they looked like dead trees devoid of any energy because they didn&amp;rsquo;t move enough.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The body language myth of crossing your arms</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/06/18/2019-06-18-the-body-language-myth-of-crossing-your-arms/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/06/18/2019-06-18-the-body-language-myth-of-crossing-your-arms/</guid>
      <description>The communication industry is full of myths that are repeated without any scientific backing. I recently watched this video by a former FBI body language specialist. He used his skills to help bust criminals. The first thing he does (at 1&#39;10&amp;quot;) is bust the myth that crossing your arms is a blocking behavior.
Bingo. I cannot agree more with this. Most people cross their arms because it&amp;rsquo;s a comfortable position, not because they have a mental block, period.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
