<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News on Presentation Creation | Public Speaking Coaching and Training | Ideas on Stage</title>
    <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in News on Presentation Creation | Public Speaking Coaching and Training | Ideas on Stage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© Ideas on Stage</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The triple stakes of great presentations</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/03/05/2019-03-05-triple-stakes-of-great-presentations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/03/05/2019-03-05-triple-stakes-of-great-presentations/</guid>
      <description>The best presentations have three stakes, three reasons &amp;ldquo;why&amp;rdquo; they are important:
 The first stake is about you: why is the topic important for you? This is the reason you, and not somebody else, is on stage to deliver the presentation. The second stake is about your audience: why is it important for them? This is the reason why your audience is there to listen to you instead of doing something else.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 warning signs someone is not ready to speak at your TEDx event</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/02/26/2019-02-26-5-warning-signs-someone-is-not-ready-for-ted/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/02/26/2019-02-26-5-warning-signs-someone-is-not-ready-for-ted/</guid>
      <description>“Don’t worry, I’m experienced, I speak at conferences all the time!” How many times have we heard that sentence from speakers who never did a TEDx style talk, yet think that, because of experience, they can just wing it? For us, it’s not reassuring. Quite the opposite, it’s a clear warning sign that the speaker doesn’t really know what is expected of him. Here are five warning signs that give you clues that your speaker may not be ready to give a TEDx style talk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don’t do an elevator pitch. Start a conversation.</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/02/19/2019-02-19-dont-do-an-elevator-pitch-start-a-conversation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/02/19/2019-02-19-dont-do-an-elevator-pitch-start-a-conversation/</guid>
      <description>If you’re a Startup founder, you’ve heard this all before. “Your elevator pitch should be able to convince anyone in 30 seconds in an elevator”. Hold on hold on hold on! Let’s pause for a few seconds. Imagine that the roles are reversed. You’re in the elevator, lost in your thoughts, minding your own business. There is one other person in it, who you don’t know, and that person is looking intensely at you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to starve the presentation vultures (part 2)</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/02/12/2019-02-12-how-to-starve-the-presentation-vultures-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/02/12/2019-02-12-how-to-starve-the-presentation-vultures-2/</guid>
      <description>Last week we saw how presentation vultures can destroy your confidence and ability to present in front of an audience. We saw that the best way to fend them off is to strengthen your vital space anchor. But how can you do that?
If your presentation has an objective, a clear message, it is much easier to use it as an anchor. Let’s imagine for example that the key message is that your presentation is about a new software service that offers necessary services to protect your IT systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to starve the presentation vultures (part 1)</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/02/05/2019-02-05-how-to-starve-the-presentation-vultures-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/02/05/2019-02-05-how-to-starve-the-presentation-vultures-1/</guid>
      <description>Maybe you feel that your last presentation was a complete failure. You didn’t manage to shake off your nerves. You became confused. The client or your boss criticized you. Maybe you’ve been caught in a downward spiral for some time, each criticism making you lose confidence, and making the next presentation worse. I have good news for you: no matter what your situation is, this vicious circle can be broken, and you gain the necessary confidence to enjoy presenting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to steal the show</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/01/29/2019-01-29-how-to-steal-the-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/01/29/2019-01-29-how-to-steal-the-show/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks ago, Ideas on Stage had the privilege of organizing a sales presentation training for Krauthammer at Dolce La Hulpe, close to Brussels in Belgium. For us, delivering a training for dozens of senior people at Krauthammer, one of the world’s most respected sales and management training companies, felt like designing something for Jonathan Ive, Apple’s legendary designer: a bit intimidating but incredibly exciting.
The training met with great success, and it was fantastic to work with such talented people, but what I will remember most are two presentations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Listen like a butterfly, talk like a bee</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/01/22/2019-01-22-listen-like-a-butterfly-talk-like-a-bee/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/01/22/2019-01-22-listen-like-a-butterfly-talk-like-a-bee/</guid>
      <description>I know, paraphrasing the motto of the great Muhammad Ali, “Float like a butterfly, sting like a bee”, doesn’t seem to make much sense. Yet my point is that in a debate it is extremely important to listen and move with a maximum of agility, and talk with a maximum of punch.
Take the example of the Gilets jaunes controversy in France. The government was completely taken by surprise by the popularity of the movement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I presented at CES and all I got was a bunch of ungrateful tweets</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/01/15/2019-01-14-i-presented-at-ces-and-all-i-got-was-a-bunch-of-ungrateful-tweets/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/01/15/2019-01-14-i-presented-at-ces-and-all-i-got-was-a-bunch-of-ungrateful-tweets/</guid>
      <description>My colleague Ricardo pointed me to a tweet from Rene Ritchie, who was attending the conferences at CES.
Dear almost everyone on stage at CES: Pay ungodly amounts of money — anything you have to — to get WWDC speaker training ASAP.
Or go to Juilliard or the Royal Shakespeare Company for a month. Whatever works for you.
&amp;mdash; Rene Ritchie (@reneritchie) January 8, 2019 
This tweet says:
&amp;ldquo;Dear almost everyone on stage at CES: Pay ungodly amounts of money — anything you have to — to get WWDC speaker training ASAP.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What presentation lessons can we learn from Apple’s profit warning?</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/01/08/2019-01-07-what-presentation-lessons-can-we-learn-from-apples-profit-warning/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/01/08/2019-01-07-what-presentation-lessons-can-we-learn-from-apples-profit-warning/</guid>
      <description>By now, you’ve probably heard that Apple was doomed. Last Wednesday they released a profit warning press release, followed by an interview with CEO Tim Cook.
I’m all too aware of Apple’s previous profit warning. Back in the nineties, after Steve Jobs returned to Apple and a Saudi prince (whose name I forget) bought a lot of Apple shares, I decided that I would be a smart investor and I bought Apple shares too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Inform, Transform</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/01/07/2019-01-07-dont-inform-transform/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/01/07/2019-01-07-dont-inform-transform/</guid>
      <description>Too many presentations aim only to inform, yet this is one thing oral presentations are particularly bad at &amp;ndash; we forget most of what we hear within 30 seconds.
If you want people to remember information, give them a document and a coffee, and time to read. Then you can answer their questions, discuss, agree on the next steps, and leave.
This is what happens in meetings at companies like Amazon and LinkedIn, where not only do meetings never have slides - they never have presentations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Speaking Lessons from President Macron</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2018/10/10/2018-10-10-5-speaking-lessons-from-president-macron/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2018/10/10/2018-10-10-5-speaking-lessons-from-president-macron/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday French President Emmanuel Macron took live, unscripted questions from an audience of 2000 tech entrepreneurs and investors at Station F, the undisputed hub of the French startup community. Ideas on Stage may not be a tech company, but we have helped thousands of start-ups with their pitches, and partner with many accelerators including Ashoka’s ShareIT.io, based at Station F. So we are very much part of the French Tech ecosystem, and very interested in how it is evolving under its new Director, our good friend Kat Borlongan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are you ready?</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2018/10/08/2018-10-08-are-you-ready/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2018/10/08/2018-10-08-are-you-ready/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s already October and you know what that means&amp;hellip; Firming up plans for next year. Pitching projects. Assigning budgets. And ultimately getting creative about how to expire old, ineffective systems and implement a smarter and better approach. Look around and catch the shift. It&amp;rsquo;s not time for just another step forward. It&amp;rsquo;s time to leap.
At Ideas on Stage we coach, train and design for international clients and companies large and small, from CAC 40 enterprises to startups and incubators.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Business Can Learn From TED</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2018/04/10/2018-04-10-what-business-can-learn-from-ted/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2018/04/10/2018-04-10-what-business-can-learn-from-ted/</guid>
      <description>Today marks the start of TED2018, the latest edition of the world&amp;rsquo;s best-known modern conference. Participants in Vancouver will be treated to high-quality talks from well-prepared speakers, and will leave feeling energized and inspired.
Back in the office, you and your colleagues will no doubt be subjected to low-quality presentations from poorly-prepared speakers, and you will leave feeling bored and uninspired.
Business presentations are not TED talks. A board meeting is not a stage with a round red carpet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7 Tips for Overcoming the Fear of Presenting</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2018/04/09/2018-04-10-7-tips-for-overcoming-the-fear-of-presenting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2018/04/09/2018-04-10-7-tips-for-overcoming-the-fear-of-presenting/</guid>
      <description>Fear doesn&amp;rsquo;t remove the danger. Embrace it and get on top of your presentations.
 &amp;ldquo;There is nothing to fear but fear itself&amp;rdquo; - a memorable line from President Franklin D. Roosevelt&amp;rsquo;s inaugural address in 1932 at the depths of the Great Depression. At the time he may not have realized it, but his words are among the most powerful pieces of advice for public speaking.
After all, what we all fear in presentations is succumbing to fear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 presentation lessons from The Darkest Hour</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2018/02/16/2018-02-16-the-darkest-hour-presentation-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2018/02/16/2018-02-16-the-darkest-hour-presentation-lessons/</guid>
      <description>Have you seen Gary Oldman in his interpretation of Churchill in the latest biopic by Joe Wright? If you have not, please go. It’s jaw-dropping. His outstanding performance may very soon win him an Oscar. You will enjoy some of the finest acting and also benefit from precious presentation lessons from the Master Orator.
Here are 3 takeaways from the movie, which you can immediately apply for your next keynote, sales meeting or investor pitch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New brand, new design</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2018/01/26/2018-01-26-new-brand-new-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2018/01/26/2018-01-26-new-brand-new-design/</guid>
      <description>I am not a naive man. I have reasonable doubts that Santa does not really exist. So instead of writing a letter that I knew he would not answer I thought it was time to refresh the Ideas on Stage Brand, which hasn’t changed since the creation of the company in 2010.
We started with the font. We really love Gotham, the masterpiece from Tobias Frere-Jones. Its iconic design is built on a strong lineage of geometric sans serif fonts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TEDx Saclay – Worth all the Applause</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/12/01/2017-12-01-tedxsaclay/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/12/01/2017-12-01-tedxsaclay/</guid>
      <description>For the third year running, Ideas on Stage was very happy to partner with the TEDx Saclay conference, which took place this November 30, 2017 in the brand-new CentraleSupélec amphitheater at the Plateau de Saclay on the powerful theme of “Serving the Living”.
TEDx Saclay Keeping standards typically high, this year’s event boasted a rich program of speakers including a few notably prestigious guests such as Cédric Villani &amp;ndash; renowned mathematician and member of the French National Assembly &amp;ndash; as well as artists, scientists, students, entrepreneurs and even a Guinness World Record gamer (Kayane).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Women on Stage Workshop Returns Dec 7</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/10/30/2017-10-30-women-on-stage-workshop-december-7-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/10/30/2017-10-30-women-on-stage-workshop-december-7-2017/</guid>
      <description>This December 7th in an elegant boardroom along the Champs-Elysée something powerful will take place: the beloved Women on Stage workshop will return by popular demand led by Marion Chapsal, Chief Learning Officer and Speaking Coach. Spaces are limited to allow space for each voice and leader to present and receive personalized feedback.
 Marion Chapsal
  For over 20 years, Marion&amp;rsquo;s work has helped leaders to strengthen their executive presence, enhance their presentation and communication skills, and promote gender-balanced leadership in everything she does.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EDF InnovDay UNITEP 2017</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/10/06/2017-10-06-edf-innovday-unitep-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/10/06/2017-10-06-edf-innovday-unitep-2017/</guid>
      <description>Innovation is at the heart of what keeps large companies competitive. This is why EDF (Electricity of France) UNITEP organized a challenge to promote and reward internal innovative projects.
For the fourth year in a row, Ideas on Stage collaborated with EDF to coach said Innovators. We helped each group build a strong and original three-minute presentation on their innovation.
True to our methodology, we worked on developing the four elements of an impactful presentation: message, story, visuals and speaking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Helping Startups Pitch for Social Good</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/10/04/2017-10-04-helping-startups-pitch-for-social-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/10/04/2017-10-04-helping-startups-pitch-for-social-good/</guid>
      <description>The Sport Social Business Lab, aka SSBL, is an incubator specialized in sport startups for the social good. It is part of the INCO network.
Sport startups are no different from other startups: without a good pitch, they don&amp;rsquo;t stand a chance to attract investors and grow. This is why the SSBL asked Ideas on Stage to animate a three-hour pitch workshop.
As an avid sportsman who has been active in the Startup ecosystem since 2010, cofounder Pierre Morsa was uniquely qualified to deliver this workshop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taking Female Leadership by the Reins</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/09/04/2017-09-04-taking-female-leadership-by-the-reins/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/09/04/2017-09-04-taking-female-leadership-by-the-reins/</guid>
      <description>This September, something special will take place at Wisteria Acres in British Columbia, and it’s not just time with the horses. From Friday September 29th through Sunday evening on the 1st of October, Marion Chapsal and her co-facilitator Evelyn McKelvie will guide eight willing and ready women on a journey to find &amp;ndash; or fine-tune &amp;ndash; their public voice and take the stage alongside, you guessed it, horses. They call this workshop and retreat &amp;ldquo;The Heroine&amp;rsquo;s Journey&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can Women Pitch As Well As Men?</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/09/01/2017-09-01-can-women-pitch-as-well-as-men/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/09/01/2017-09-01-can-women-pitch-as-well-as-men/</guid>
      <description>It’s a simple fact that most successful startups are run by men. Why? Firstly, there are more men than women who decide - or dare - to start companies. Secondly, men are more successful at raising funds than women, and even those women who do raise funds end up raising less, on average, than their male counterparts. Having spent two years playing in the Silicon Valley arena myself, I’ve seen this truth first hand both in California and now in France.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lost in Transition?</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/08/31/2017-08-31-lost-in-transition/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/08/31/2017-08-31-lost-in-transition/</guid>
      <description>This summer Ideas on Stage partnered up with the fine people at Set’Event to help a handful of such thoughtful and committed citizens to give impactful keynote presentations at the 15th annual ACIDD event, which took place August 28-29 in Bordeaux. This year’s theme? “Lost in Transition: the time of possibilities”.
This annual event is dedicated to exploring the skills and solutions necessary to live well in our emerging digital age across all sectors, from sustainable energy to food and agriculture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who teaches the Preachers?</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/08/29/2017-08-29-who-teaches-the-preachers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/08/29/2017-08-29-who-teaches-the-preachers/</guid>
      <description>It’s not only business leaders, salespeople and entrepreneurs who need to inspire their audiences. For thousands of years, many of the most talented speakers could be found not in a shop or office but in a place of worship.
Ask people which public speaker they most admire, and many will point to Rev. Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr.. He spoke powerfully and inspired his audiences, and of the well-known speakers of the last century he was certainly among the best.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>