<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Presentation and Public Speaking News on Ideas on Stage</title>
    <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Presentation and Public Speaking News on Ideas on Stage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© Ideas on Stage 2015 - </copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Why Public Speaking Is The Most Important Skill You Need Right Now </title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/11/29/2022-11-29-why_public_speaking_is_the_most_important_skill_you_need_right_now/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/11/29/2022-11-29-why_public_speaking_is_the_most_important_skill_you_need_right_now/</guid>
      <description>The most likely reason for any setbacks and disappointments in your business, role or career is a communication deficiency—or lack of communication skills.
If you can’t convey your ideas to others then you won’t be able to reach your true potential.
The number one factor holding people back in their lives, especially in business, is poor communication skills.
If your business isn&amp;rsquo;t growing, there’s a communication deficiency.
If you&amp;rsquo;re finding it hard to lead your team, there’s a communication deficiency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don’t Let ‘Authenticity’ Hold You Back</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/11/22/2022-11-22-don_t_let_authenticity_hold_you_back/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/11/22/2022-11-22-don_t_let_authenticity_hold_you_back/</guid>
      <description>When I start working with clients to help them improve their presentations they often push back and resist change.
I encourage business leaders to use a mix of logic and emotion, tell stories, include audience interactions and use eye contact and gestures.
A common concern is that the changes I suggest feel ‘fake’ and ‘inauthentic’. People say things like, ‘this is not me’ and ‘I don’t want to act like someone I’m not’.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Bring Boring Case Studies Alive – In 4 Easy Steps</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/11/15/2022-11-15-how_to_bring_boring_case_studies_alive_in_4_easy_steps/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/11/15/2022-11-15-how_to_bring_boring_case_studies_alive_in_4_easy_steps/</guid>
      <description>One of the worst things you can do when sharing examples, stories or case studies in a business presentation is to make them about yourself一instead of the client or the audience.
I’ve seen it so many times. I hear phrases like:
We’ve been the industry leader since 2010
We have 123 offices in 36 different countries
We have 7,500 clients across 80 industries We’re a pioneering company in our field</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Make Your Presentations More Interactive </title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/11/08/2022-11-08-how_to_make_your_presentations_more_interactive/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/11/08/2022-11-08-how_to_make_your_presentations_more_interactive/</guid>
      <description>There’s nothing more boring than a one-way lecture which makes an audience feel like they’re being talked at.
Unfortunately, too many business leaders deliver presentations which are more like one-sided lectures. They believe their job is to speak for 30 minutes while others listen.
These kinds of presentations, which don’t consider the needs of the audience, are tedious and unsuccessful.
How do we do things differently? In this article I’ll explore how to bring the audience into your presentations and make them feel involved.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Ways To Communicate Data More Effectively</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/11/01/2022-11-01-3_ways_to_communicate_data_more_effectively/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/11/01/2022-11-01-3_ways_to_communicate_data_more_effectively/</guid>
      <description>Data and numbers can be important to a business presentation一but they can be bone dry unless you bring them to life in interesting ways.
I often see business leaders struggle to communicate data effectively. When I ask them if they think they’re doing it well they usually say yes. But that’s rarely the case.
Too many presenters assume that their data is intrinsically meaningful.
“Here’s the data: take it, use it, understand it, remember it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leadership and Communication Tactics to Fuel Your Success</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/10/24/2022-10-19-leadership_and_communication_tactics_to_fuel_your_success/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/10/24/2022-10-19-leadership_and_communication_tactics_to_fuel_your_success/</guid>
      <description>Do others dismiss your ideas and proposals?
Do you struggle with creating and delivering simple, engaging, and persuasive presentations?
Have you heard about ‘storytelling’ but you’re not sure how to do it?
If so, this is the event you&amp;rsquo;ve been waiting for!
O﻿n 6th December 2022 I&amp;rsquo;m hosting a free, live web class in collaboration with the one and only Carmine Gallo, the bestselling author of Talk Like TED. You’ll learn strategies based on his new book, The Bezos Blueprint.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Persuasive Power of Analogies in Communication</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/10/18/2022-10-18-the_persuasive_power_of_analogies_in_communication/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/10/18/2022-10-18-the_persuasive_power_of_analogies_in_communication/</guid>
      <description>One of the hardest lessons to learn in communication is the art of keeping things simple.
The more we know about something, the easier it is to fall into the trap of making our ideas too complex and too technical.
It’s something I see business leaders doing all the time before they learn to improve their presentations. They wrongly assume that the audience will understand something just because they do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7 Ways To Lead Your Audience To The Next Step</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/10/11/2022-10-12-7_ways_to_lead_your_audience_to_the_next_step/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/10/11/2022-10-12-7_ways_to_lead_your_audience_to_the_next_step/</guid>
      <description>If there’s a common purpose to most business presentations it’s to persuade the audience to act upon your ideas in some way. The best way to persuade the audience to do what you want them to do is with a clear call to action.
If the call to action isn’t clear enough, the audience will fail to act. Your presentation will have been in vain.
For example, imagine you were giving a webinar or an introductory workshop on your area of expertise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What to do the minute you take the stage? C-SPARK</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/10/05/2022-10-05-what_to_do_the_minute_you_take_the_stage_c-spark/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/10/05/2022-10-05-what_to_do_the_minute_you_take_the_stage_c-spark/</guid>
      <description>Of the three million articles written about public speaking, isn’t it refreshing to read something useful in under three minutes? I think so, or at least that is what I would appreciate. So here are my three minutes’ worth for you.
It’s high time to get live presentations kicking again. But can we go back to them seamlessly like before? It can be a little daunting after such a long spell presenting virtually.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7 Memorable Ways to Open a Presentation (With Examples)</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/10/04/2022-10-04-7_memorable_ways_to_open_a_presentation_with_examples/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/10/04/2022-10-04-7_memorable_ways_to_open_a_presentation_with_examples/</guid>
      <description>The first words of a presentation are the most important. Your opening needs to grab the audience’s attention and hold it.
The philosopher Plato said: “The beginning is the most important part of the work.”
Sadly, most business leaders don’t think carefully enough about the way they open their presentations. Instead, they focus on the main body of their presentation and leave the opening to chance.
Or they make the common mistake of opening with a boring agenda slide or by introducing themselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>“Be Water my friend“</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/09/28/2022-09-28-be_water_my_friend/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/09/28/2022-09-28-be_water_my_friend/</guid>
      <description>How a famous Bruce Lee quote can help presenters conquer fear by surrendering the outcome.
So this got your attention! Drawing on a 70s Kung Fu star to get some presentation tips! For those who don’t know Bruce Lee, he was an icon of the 1970s whose movies including Enter the Dragon and Fist of Fury have inspired generations. He was both impressive and also rather eccentric. Crafting his own philosophy during his relatively short life, he was quoted saying some interesting things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6 Steps To Creating A Clear Presentation Storyline</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/09/27/2022-09-27-6_steps_to_creating_a_clear_presentation_storyline/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/09/27/2022-09-27-6_steps_to_creating_a_clear_presentation_storyline/</guid>
      <description>The greatest films, TV shows and novels are the ones with the best storylines. The same is true for presentations. A strong narrative can help you bring your presentation alive and make it memorable and successful. However, most business owners, leaders and professionals don’t pay enough attention to the way they structure their presentations. They fail to develop a clear storyline.
I’ve come across many presenters who simply improvise their presentation around some slides.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Take Control Of Your Fear of Public Speaking (Without Any “Woo Woo” Remedies) </title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/09/20/2022-09-15-how_to_take_control_of_your_fear_of_public_speaking_without_any_woo_woo_remedies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/09/20/2022-09-15-how_to_take_control_of_your_fear_of_public_speaking_without_any_woo_woo_remedies/</guid>
      <description>It’s almost pointless asking if you feel nervous before a presentation. It would be strange if you didn’t. The vast majority of people are afraid of public speaking. It’s perfectly normal to have a fear of public speaking, also known by its technical name of glossophobia.
Research shows that more than 75 percent of the population has some level of public speaking anxiety. So you’re in good company.
I’m a presentation coach and I feel nervous all the time before a presentation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What the hell is personal branding anyway?</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/09/20/2022-09-20-what_the_hell_is_personal_branding_anyway/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/09/20/2022-09-20-what_the_hell_is_personal_branding_anyway/</guid>
      <description>I ask this question in order to answer it because clarity leads to serenity. We are bombarded daily with new concepts and trends, and Personal Branding is another one, albeit a little vague for most of us. People are taking what ideas they think they know from Personal Branding and applying them with gusto. Others are doing it instinctively. One thing is for sure: it’s here to stay and remains a key tool to get ahead in the landscape of opportunity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Rehearsing Leads to More Confidence</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/09/13/2022-09-14-why_rehearsing_leads_to_more_confidence/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/09/13/2022-09-14-why_rehearsing_leads_to_more_confidence/</guid>
      <description>When you watch the best athletes their movement seems completely natural and effortless. The reason they look so at ease is because of the years of dedicated practice they’ve put in. No one is born with the ability to excel—it requires work.
The same is true for business presentations. It’s impossible to deliver a great speech without rehearsing it thoroughly. You can spot a presenter who hasn’t rehearsed adequately. The giveaways are that they might:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Audience Interaction</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/09/07/2022-08-31-big_audience_interaction/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/09/07/2022-08-31-big_audience_interaction/</guid>
      <description>As we emerge from a long period of working from home and online meetings, more and more organizations are bringing people back together. Some big firms are having difficulty forcing people back into the office, but one thing everyone seems to agree on is that Zoom is no substitute for face-to-face conferences or conventions.
Presenters are now having to face a problem they haven’t faced for some time: how to make presentations interactive in front of big audiences, without the benefit of online features like polls, chat or breakout rooms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do You Suffer From The Curse Of Knowledge? </title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/09/06/2022-09-07-do_you_suffer_from_the_curse_of_knowledge/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/09/06/2022-09-07-do_you_suffer_from_the_curse_of_knowledge/</guid>
      <description>There is a famous saying that ‘a little knowledge is a dangerous thing’. It warns against those who know something about a subject but not quite enough.
We should apply the same caution to those business owners and leaders who pitch their presentations above the audience’s heads. They forget how much they know about a subject and aim too high.
In Made to Stick by Chip Heath and Dan Heath, one of the best books I’ve ever read, they introduce the concept of the curse of knowledge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Idea Is Worthless Unless You Can Communicate It</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/08/30/2022-08-30-your_idea_is_worthless_unless_you_can_communicate_it/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/08/30/2022-08-30-your_idea_is_worthless_unless_you_can_communicate_it/</guid>
      <description>Right now there&amp;rsquo;s someone in the world having a great idea; their own lightbulb moment which could change the world.
Many entrepreneurs, business owners and leaders assume that their ideas are the most important thing. They believe that their idea, whether that be a product, service, project or business, is all that matters. They focus on creating and working on their concepts without giving sufficient thought to articulating them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Make Your Message Relevant To Your Audience</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/08/23/2022-08-16-how_to_make_your_message_relevant_to_your_audience/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/08/23/2022-08-16-how_to_make_your_message_relevant_to_your_audience/</guid>
      <description>When Paul McCartney headlined Glastonbury in 2022 he played a long set which included lots of newer material, plus songs from his solo and Wings albums. Many people loved it. But he was criticised for not giving the audience what they wanted — which was the hits.
No doubt Sir Paul had his reasons. He doesn’t just want to play Beatles songs all evening. But even someone of his experience and talent can get it wrong sometimes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Power of Storytelling in Presentations</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/08/16/2022-07-26-the_power_of_storytelling_in_presentations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/08/16/2022-07-26-the_power_of_storytelling_in_presentations/</guid>
      <description>If you truly want to connect with an audience one of the most powerful strategies is to share stories and real life experiences. Facts and figures are hard to remember but we love hearing anecdotes.
Many business owners, leaders and professionals make the mistake of only sharing information in their presentations. They include abstract concepts, facts and figures. As a result, their presentations remain dry, factual and boring. You don’t want to be a boring presenter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Present A Clear Message To Any Audience: The Rule of Three</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/08/09/2022-08-09-how-to-present-a-clear-message-to-any-audience-the-rule-of-three/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/08/09/2022-08-09-how-to-present-a-clear-message-to-any-audience-the-rule-of-three/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever had this experience: it becomes increasingly obvious to you during a presentation that the structure isn’t clear enough? You’re losing the audience (which might be clients, colleagues, the board, partners or investors).
If so, you are not alone. Most business leaders and professionals struggle with this.
Fortunately, there is one simple yet powerful communication technique that will help you: the Rule of Three.
The Rule of Three Three is the most powerful number in communication.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three Ways To Simplify Your Presentations</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/08/02/2022-08-02-three-ways-to-simplify-your-presentations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/08/02/2022-08-02-three-ways-to-simplify-your-presentations/</guid>
      <description>Many business owners, leaders and professionals give presentations that are too complex. The consequence is that the audience fails to grasp the message and will not take the desired action.
I believe that the more you say, the less your audience will remember. So you need to keep your presentations short, simple and to the point.
Keeping it simple is one of the five key factors behind any powerful presentation. If you are interested in learning more about the others, I have written about them here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Five Key Principles For Powerful Presentations</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/07/26/2022-07-26-the-five-key-principles-for-powerful-presentations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/07/26/2022-07-26-the-five-key-principles-for-powerful-presentations/</guid>
      <description>Most business leaders fail to follow set principles for creating and delivering their presentations. In not doing so they are making a fundamental mistake.
Some think it’s primarily about creating slides on PowerPoint. They think if they get a decent deck together then they are good to go.
If you are one of those people who spend most of your preparation time working on PowerPoint slides (or any other presentation tool), you’ve missed the point.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Being Confident At Public Speaking: The Three Things You Need To Know</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/07/19/2022-07-19-being-confident-at-public-speaking-the-three-things-you-need-to-know/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/07/19/2022-07-19-being-confident-at-public-speaking-the-three-things-you-need-to-know/</guid>
      <description>Many business leaders and professionals wrongly believe that being confident at public speaking comes naturally to some people. Perhaps they are born with confidence?
Or they think that to become more confident at presenting they simply need to improve their delivery skills and work on things like eye contact, body language and vocal delivery. These things are all important but there is so much more to it.
As a result, most untrained business leaders don’t feel confident presenting at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Hidden Cost Of Bad Presentations — How To Avoid Losing Business</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/06/28/2022-06-28-the-hidden-cost-of-bad-presentations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/06/28/2022-06-28-the-hidden-cost-of-bad-presentations/</guid>
      <description>A presentation is your opportunity to make a great first impression. It’s a bit like a first date — only the stakes are financial rather than romantic.
However, too many business leaders fail to consider the cost of delivering a bad presentation.
Many companies fall into the trap of making an invisible first impression. When presenting an idea for the first time — be it a product, a service or a project — the impression they make is invisible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public Speaking: A Proven Process to Build Your Confidence</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/06/09/2022-06-09-public-speaking-a-proven-process-to-build-your-confidence/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/06/09/2022-06-09-public-speaking-a-proven-process-to-build-your-confidence/</guid>
      <description>It’s easier than you think to improve your confidence when presenting or public speaking. The more prepared and structured your approach, the more confident you will be.
Most business leaders don’t follow any sort of organised process when preparing a presentation. Keen to get started, they launch into things and hope for the best. We’ve all seen the person who decides to wing it or who turns up with chaotic notes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why complex presentations don&#39;t work (and what to do instead)</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/05/31/2022-05-31-why-complex-presentations-don-t-work-and-what-to-do-instead/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/05/31/2022-05-31-why-complex-presentations-don-t-work-and-what-to-do-instead/</guid>
      <description>The most successful messages are the simplest. The best writing gets to the point. The greatest speeches are concise and direct.
However, too many business leaders fall into the trap of giving presentations which are overly complex and technical. They navigate their audience down side roads and off on tangents. Their visuals mirror this and are often confusing and convoluted.
Why does this happen? It is all done for the right reasons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Presentation Problems Every Business Leader Needs To Avoid</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/05/04/2022-05-04-5-presentation-problems-every-business-leader-needs-to-avoid/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/05/04/2022-05-04-5-presentation-problems-every-business-leader-needs-to-avoid/</guid>
      <description>Think about how technology has evolved over the last 20 years or so. Think about the tools we can use today to communicate our ideas to the world. Now, compare that with the tools we had a few years ago. Today in most industries we have more competition—not only from a business perspective but also from a communication perspective.
The tools we have today are designed to empower people—lots of people—to share their message with the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Soft Skills: The 2022 French Presidential Debate</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/04/21/2022-04-21-soft-skills-the-2022-french-presidential-debate/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/04/21/2022-04-21-soft-skills-the-2022-french-presidential-debate/</guid>
      <description>The 2022 French presidential election debate serves up a new dish, more palatable than the one served in 2017.
On Wednesday night, 20th of April 2022, two presidential candidates battled in Paris for the next five years in a crucial election here in France. For Emmanuel Macron and Marine Le Pen this was their second debate, the last being back in 2017. But last night’s debate was very different.
Now, from a policy point of view, many views were exchanged on the environment, security, the economy and the current international context amongst many others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Communication Battle Facing Us All</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/03/29/2022-03-29-the-communication-battle-facing-us-all/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/03/29/2022-03-29-the-communication-battle-facing-us-all/</guid>
      <description>Misinformation is the scourge of our time. It confuses and divides us and can do irreparable harm. What can we do to fight it?
For the majority of us today working in business, life is good. In the last 15 years or so, I have observed huge improvements in the way large companies and corporations respond and communicate with their customers and peers on issues that matter: climate change, DE&amp;amp;I and Digital transformation being the most important.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great Leaders Move Mountains</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/03/02/2022-03-08-great-leaders-move-mountains/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/03/02/2022-03-08-great-leaders-move-mountains/</guid>
      <description>Volodymyr Zelenskiy has reached the parts that other leaders haven’t reached in a long time.
After weeks of an army build-up on the borders of Ukraine from the Russian state, and on the eve of a massive Russian invasion, the President of Ukraine Volodymyr Zelenskiy, hopelessly outnumbered and outgunned, made a video statement to his people from the centre of Kyiv which inspired not only Ukrainians, but also the rest of the world to the core:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Interview with Jerry Weissman</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/01/18/2022-01-18-my-interview-with-jerry-weissman/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2022/01/18/2022-01-18-my-interview-with-jerry-weissman/</guid>
      <description>Michael Rickwood from Ideas on Stage on how he got to meet the man who started it all for the presentation world.
Once in a while we set ourselves some great tasks. Interviewing my presentation hero was a particularly appealing one. Over the years I have read many great books on business communication and have taken inspiration from authors from all facets of our industry: Nancy Duarte, Garr Reynolds, Patsy Rodenburg, Dan and Chip Heath, Guy Kawasaki, Simon Sinek, Dan Pink, Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It is always the Season for Giving</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2021/12/23/2021-12-23-it-is-always-the-season-for-giving/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2021/12/23/2021-12-23-it-is-always-the-season-for-giving/</guid>
      <description>We have recently completed coaching all the finalists for the latest installment of the INSEAD Venture Competition (IVC), an event where over one hundred teams of entrepreneurs pitch their start-up ideas for cash prizes. This is an internal competition where all MBA students are invited to participate.
More than the cash prizes, teams are mentored through the process by experts in launching businesses, investors, and management consultants. Teams gain world class advice and guidance towards launching their start-up businesses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boris Johnson’s Peppa Pig Moment</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2021/12/07/2021-12-07-boris-johnson-s-peppa-pig-moment/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2021/12/07/2021-12-07-boris-johnson-s-peppa-pig-moment/</guid>
      <description>Say what you like about Boris Johnson, his style connects with the mob. Our institutional leaders need to put aside their intellectual bias and start figuring out why it’s working.
Last month in London, Boris Johnson gave a speech at the Confederation of British Industry in South Shields in the North of England. He stumbled, got lost in his notes, and started talking about Peppa Pig. You might start reading this and assume where it’s going.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Words Matter: words breed inspiration, inspiration breeds hope, hope breeds action.</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2021/11/09/2021-11-09-word-matter/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2021/11/09/2021-11-09-word-matter/</guid>
      <description>Why a 13-year-old speech given by a former US president holds a blueprint solution for our modern problem.
In 2008, during his campaigning, Barack Obama gave a rallying speech in Wisconsin on the power of words and resistance to hope. “Don’t tell me words don’t matter! I have a dream, just words?! All men are created equal, just words?!” It’s true that speeches don’t solve all problems, but what is also true is if we cannot inspire the country to believe again then it doesn’t matter how many policies and plans we have.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pSCORE Stage 5: Connection</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2021/07/23/2021-07-22-pscore_stage_5_connection/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2021/07/23/2021-07-22-pscore_stage_5_connection/</guid>
      <description>Business Presentation Revolution covers the five stages of the Presentation SCORE Method, or pSCORE, giving you a simple, proven process to follow to prepare and deliver successful presentations every time.
In this extract from Business Presentation Revolution, author Phil Waknell outlines the fifth and final stage: Connection.
Having the fastest, best designed and most attractive car doesn’t guarantee you’ll win the race. The performance of the driver is just as important.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pSCORE Stage 4: Illustration</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2021/07/22/2021-07-22-pscore_stage_4_illustration/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2021/07/22/2021-07-22-pscore_stage_4_illustration/</guid>
      <description>Business Presentation Revolution covers the five stages of the Presentation SCORE Method, or pSCORE, giving you a simple, proven process to follow to prepare and deliver successful presentations every time.
In this extract from Business Presentation Revolution, author Phil Waknell outlines the fourth stage: Illustration.
Humans can only process one linguistic input at a time: this means that if you show your audience a slide while you’re speaking, they have to choose either to read or to listen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pSCORE Stage 3: Creation</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2021/07/21/2021-07-21-pscore_stage_3_creation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2021/07/21/2021-07-21-pscore_stage_3_creation/</guid>
      <description>Business Presentation Revolution outlines the five stages of the Presentation SCORE Method, or pSCORE, giving you a simple, proven process to follow to prepare and deliver successful presentations every time.
In this extract from Business Presentation Revolution, author Phil Waknell outlines the third stage: Creation.
In the first and second stages, you should already have studied your Audience, their Burning needs and the Context (ABC), set one or more objectives for transforming what your audience believes, feels and/or does, and found all the raw materials necessary to achieve those objectives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pSCORE Stage 2: Ideation</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2021/06/18/2021-06-18-pscore_stage_2_ideation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2021/06/18/2021-06-18-pscore_stage_2_ideation/</guid>
      <description>Business Presentation Revolution outlines the five stages of the Presentation SCORE Method, or pSCORE, giving you a simple, proven process to follow to prepare and deliver successful presentations every time.
In this extract from Business Presentation Revolution, author Phil Waknell outlines the second stage: Ideation.
The aim of the Ideation stage is to generate all the raw material you need so you are ready to begin creating your presentation. This means you need to find ideas, because ideas are the raw material of a successful presentation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pSCORE Stage 1: Foundation</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2021/06/10/2021-06-10-the_foundation_stage/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2021/06/10/2021-06-10-the_foundation_stage/</guid>
      <description>Business Presentation Revolution outlines the five stages of the Presentation SCORE Method, or pSCORE, giving you a simple, proven process to follow to prepare and deliver successful presentations every time.
In this extract from Business Presentation Revolution, author Phil Waknell outlines the vital first stage: Foundation.
If you build a house on sand, it will not be stable; likewise, if you start to prepare a presentation without understanding its context or its audience, you will be setting yourself up for failure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How do you prepare yourself before a big presentation?</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2021/06/02/2021-06-02-how_do_you_prepare_yourself_before_a_big_presentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2021/06/02/2021-06-02-how_do_you_prepare_yourself_before_a_big_presentation/</guid>
      <description>In this extract from Business Presentation Revolution, published on July 14th 2021, I answer the important question: how do you prepare yourself before a big presentation?
Before you take the stage, you need to be comfortable. Audiences don’t appreciate speakers who haven’t prepared properly, don’t know their presentation well enough, and are visibly worrying about what to say next.
There are several simple actions you can take before your presentation to maximize your own comfort and help you to deliver a better talk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The science of presenting</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2021/05/26/2021-05-25-the_science_of_presenting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2021/05/26/2021-05-25-the_science_of_presenting/</guid>
      <description>I’m not a motor mechanic. I don’t play with my car’s engine, hoping to make it run better, because I don’t understand how it works in detail. I leave that to experts who are professionally trained and experienced.
The human brain is far more complex than an engine, and we know far less about how it works. Trying to present without learning a little about how the brain works is like throwing a spanner into a car and hoping it will fix the brakes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What’s the right tone for Business Presentations?</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2021/05/25/2021-05-25-what_s_the_right_tone_for_business_presentations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2021/05/25/2021-05-25-what_s_the_right_tone_for_business_presentations/</guid>
      <description>TED has provided us all with a welcome relief from Death by PowerPoint. Shorter, more personal, more visual and more memorable, we now have thousands of talks to choose from providing us with a learning platform as awesome as Wikipedia. Business has benefited from it in miraculous ways. Garr Reynolds, author of Presentation Zen, once coined a great phrase: the ‘Ted-ification of business presentations’. Thanks in part to TED, but also to a certain extent to the original presentations of Steve Jobs, we all benefit from simpler, clearer, more original, more relevant and dare I say it more entertaining business presentations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aim not for perfect, but for personal.</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2021/05/20/2021-05-20-aim_not_for_perfect_but_for_personal-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2021/05/20/2021-05-20-aim_not_for_perfect_but_for_personal-/</guid>
      <description>There is no such thing as a perfect presentation. You should of course prepare and rehearse it enough so you know it well, and so your messages come from the heart, not the head. If you can focus on delivering not just the syllables of your words, but the meaning behind them, then you are ready to present. Do not overdo the rehearsals, though. Your audience does not expect absolute perfection, and if you can create a strong connection with them, they will accept your imperfections, and see you as more human.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do I really need slides?</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2021/05/18/2021-05-19-do_i_really_need_slides/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2021/05/18/2021-05-19-do_i_really_need_slides/</guid>
      <description>The success of PowerPoint in taking over corporate communication has led to one major problem: it is now the default way people present. If your boss asks you: “Have you prepared your presentation?” what she really means is: “Have you prepared your PowerPoint® slides?”
This means that presenters automatically assume that they will use PowerPoint® slides, and do not even consider that there may be other possibilities.
Ask yourself, for each point in your presentation: does my audience really need any visual aids?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sharknado is the same movie as Titanic, only with more sharks</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2021-05-18/sharknado-is-the-same-movie-as-titanic-only-with-more-sharks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2021-05-18/sharknado-is-the-same-movie-as-titanic-only-with-more-sharks/</guid>
      <description>Believe it or not, all American movies rely on the same formula; that formula is so sacred that scripts will get rejected if they stray from it. Whether it’s a psychological drama like American Beauty, a sci-fi movie like Star Wars or an action movie like Mission: Impossible, the same structure, plot points and character development techniques are used. I’ll just take one as an example: the hero, the main protagonist, is always an orphan, literally or figuratively, or experienced a personal drama; it is supposed to give the character more likeness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doctor Visual &amp; Mister Slide</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2021/05/12/2021-05-11-doctor_visual_mister_slide/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2021/05/12/2021-05-11-doctor_visual_mister_slide/</guid>
      <description>Slides can be an extremely powerful way of making your messages clearer and more memorable – yet all too often they are an obstacle to communication.
Humans can’t listen and read different things simultaneously: we can only process one linguistic input at a time. So if a slide features a lot of text and detail, it might make a useful reference document, but a terrible visual aid. On the other hand, if you keep your slides simple, with only a few words, they’ll be good visual aids but worthless as handouts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What are the few big things we need to change to fix presentations?</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2021/05/11/2021-05-11-what_are_the_few_big_things_we_need_to_change_to_fix_presentations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2021/05/11/2021-05-11-what_are_the_few_big_things_we_need_to_change_to_fix_presentations/</guid>
      <description>In 2021 we can watch more examples than ever to know how to give a good presentation. We see examples of it in TED, top company Keynotes and our favorite lecturers and leaders. Yet still there are things that need to be changed. I have tried to collect them into what I call the 5 negatives followed by our very own revolution solutions!
No foundations, people are still too last minute, whether its completing that 20,000-word dissertation at university written the night before or the finance report mixed together from excels and spreadsheets in the metro the same morning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Prepare your story before your slides</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2021/05/05/2021-05-04-prepare_your_story_before_your_slides/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2021/05/05/2021-05-04-prepare_your_story_before_your_slides/</guid>
      <description>As our recent LinkedIn poll showed clearly, the number one thing people hate about presentations is when the speaker reads slides to the audience.
Why does anyone still do this? If you show them all the text, they can read it far more quickly than you can say it, and they will wonder why you didn’t just give them a document to read instead.
If you are going to read your bullet-points, and then comment on them, be aware that while you are talking about point 1, they have finished reading all 6 points on your slide, and are switching off until you catch up with them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Don’t inform: Transform!</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2021/04/28/2021-04-28-don_t_inform_transform/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2021/04/28/2021-04-28-don_t_inform_transform/</guid>
      <description>What is your presentation’s primary objective? Many presenters treat their talk as if it were a dental appointment: their sole aim is to get through it as quickly and painlessly as possible, escape mostly unharmed, then drink something cool or strong, or perhaps both.
Other presenters might say their aim is to share information: for example, to explain sales targets, or business results.
It’s important to dig a little deeper, and when it comes to objectives, the most useful word is ‘why’.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Microsoft’s PowerPoint Presenter Coach taking my job? No.</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2021/04/27/2021-04-27-is-microsoft-s-powerpoint-presenter-coach-taking-my-job/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2021/04/27/2021-04-27-is-microsoft-s-powerpoint-presenter-coach-taking-my-job/</guid>
      <description>I have been a presentations coach for the best part of 15 years. Coach is one of my titles along with consultant, director, trainer and whatever else describes what I do, which is help people in all sectors and walks of life to give fantastic presentations in high stakes scenarios, or train them to be simpler, more natural, better prepared and highly impactful, whether on stage or on a digital platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seven Lessons From Apple&#39;s Spring-Loaded Event</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2021-04-21/seven-lessons-from-apple-spring-loaded-event/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2021-04-21/seven-lessons-from-apple-spring-loaded-event/</guid>
      <description>Apple’s Spring-loaded event was the talk of the internet town yesterday, and for a good reason: it was mind-blowingly great. Everything was perfect: the products, the speakers, the locations, the scenography, the production. How proud Apple employees must feel today after such a great event. I have identified seven elements that set Apple apart from its competitors.
Coaching. Get public speaking coaching. If you look at the video, the delivery of each speaker is impeccable: their diction, their voice, their posture, their body language.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whose Presentation Is It Anyway?</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2021/04/21/2021-04-21-whose_presentation_is_it_anyway/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2021/04/21/2021-04-21-whose_presentation_is_it_anyway/</guid>
      <description>When I visit companies to speak about presenting, I don’t give the same talk to every company. I don’t even give the same talk to every function in a company. They are all different, and while a standard talk would meet their needs, you should be more ambitious than just meeting their needs. You should aim to delight them.
A presentation is a gift. You could just give everyone a pair of socks for their birthday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 timeless principles from Presentation Zen</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2021-04-06/five-timeless-principles-of-presentation-zen/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2021-04-06/five-timeless-principles-of-presentation-zen/</guid>
      <description>When it was first published, Garr Reynolds’ first book Presentation Zen took the traditional world of presentations by storm. It brought the presentation revolution to a wider audience of enthusiasts. We propose to revisit five essential principles from the book that have stood the test of time and can still be considered as best presentation practices today.
Plan analog. There are many theories that try to explain how creativity works, but one thing is sure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Performance Buddy. Finally THE shortcut to presentation perfection.</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2021/04/01/2021-04-01-the.performance.buddy.finally.the.shortcut.to.presentation.perfection/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2021/04/01/2021-04-01-the.performance.buddy.finally.the.shortcut.to.presentation.perfection/</guid>
      <description>2021 already presents many challenges, not only for leaders and executives but for everyone in the white collar sphere who needs to communicate with their colleages, clients and partners.
With online talks raising the bar and audiences increasingly critical, leaders with confidence issues, performance anxiety and low self-esteem have to stay on point. The task of gaining confidence while battling nerves and getting out in one piece is exhausting. Coaching, meditation, rehearsal, visualisation and psychotherapy are all strategies that professionals have turned to over the years to conquer the fear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enough with Presenting On Zoom Already!</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2021/03/30/2021-03-30-enough-with-presenting-on-zoom-already.en-copy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2021/03/30/2021-03-30-enough-with-presenting-on-zoom-already.en-copy/</guid>
      <description>It’s March, 2021. The numbers continue to rise, vaccines are rolling out slowly (here in Europe anyway) and governments and communities remain at loggerheads about what to do going forward. There is a general expectation that this status quo will continue to the end of the year and businesses are continuing to either postpone large in-person gatherings or are adopting alternative ones using the tools we have at our disposal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ikigai of Your TED Presentation</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2021/03/16/2021-03-16-the-ikigai-of-your-ted-presentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2021/03/16/2021-03-16-the-ikigai-of-your-ted-presentation/</guid>
      <description>Ikigai is a Japanese concept that means “a reason for being.” Ikigai is the intersection between what you love, what you are good at, what you can be paid for and what the world needs.
If you ever want to speak at TED or TEDx event, you should find the ikigai of your presentation. It should be at the intersection of:
What you love, or in the context of a presentation, what you really care about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Biden’s Inauguration Speech: Reversing American Carnage</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2021/01/26/2021-01-26-biden-s-inauguration-speech-reversing-american-carnage/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2021/01/26/2021-01-26-biden-s-inauguration-speech-reversing-american-carnage/</guid>
      <description>I write this on the first full day of the 46th President of the United States Joseph Biden’s tenure in the White House. After 4 exhausting years for America and the wider world, the page has turned from the failings of an introspective, corrosive and divisive mandate into a bold, courageous and reactive new era, acknowledging first the gravity of America’s collective problems and seeking to solve them through consensus and action.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pro Tips for Zoom Meetings</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2020/12/14/2020-12-13-pro-tips_for_zoom_meetings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2020/12/14/2020-12-13-pro-tips_for_zoom_meetings/</guid>
      <description>Zoom has become one of those tools that most people use, but how many of us have actually followed a training course on how to use Zoom properly? Not so many.
At Ideas on Stage we have been using Zoom for years, so when the 2020 pandemic hit, we didn’t discover Zoom, but we did start to discover new features: some that we hadn’t needed before, and some that Zoom introduced as its usage exploded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Seven Deadly Sins of Online Presentations</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2020/12/04/2020-12-17-the_seven_deadly_sins_of_online_presentations/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2020/12/04/2020-12-17-the_seven_deadly_sins_of_online_presentations/</guid>
      <description>The COVID 19 pandemic has forced all of us to adjust and has pushed roughly 35% of the workforce to an exclusively online existence. While this is fortunate and frankly would have been impossible 15 years ago it doesn’t come without its challenges.
As we struggle to maintain our routines, stay connected with our co-workers we have to continue the regular meetings attendance, trainings and webinars and we often have to give them ourselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Master Q&amp;A Sessions</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2020/11/20/2020-12-21-how_to_master_q_a_sessions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2020/11/20/2020-12-21-how_to_master_q_a_sessions/</guid>
      <description>Many of us are starting to approach presentations in the right way, taking the time to fix our objectives, analyze the audience, study the context, put together some coherent arguments, good visuals and even find the time to rehearse.
Just as we are now spending longer to prepare our presentations properly, in a world of ever-increasing social media and ever-dwindling attention spans, our presentations are getting shorter in order to be more effective.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Violent Communication versus non-Violent Communication</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2020/11/12/2020-11-12-violent_communication_versus_non-violent_communication-_a_battle_still_rages_for_hearts_and_minds_in_the_city_built_on_speeches-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2020/11/12/2020-11-12-violent_communication_versus_non-violent_communication-_a_battle_still_rages_for_hearts_and_minds_in_the_city_built_on_speeches-/</guid>
      <description>A battle still rages for hearts and minds in the city built on speeches. Let the US election of 2020 be a lesson to all leaders of tomorrow.
I am a frequent visitor to Washington DC. Having a key client on Pennsylvania Avenue, I have had the pleasure of getting to know the city and its people, working the day and socializing the night, breathing the atmosphere and drinking its politics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unleash the Hans Rösling in You</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2020/10/20/2020-10-20-unleash-the-hans-ro%CC%88sling-in-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2020/10/20/2020-10-20-unleash-the-hans-ro%CC%88sling-in-you/</guid>
      <description>If you ever talked with me about my favorite TEDx talks, then I am sure I mentioned the late Hans Rösling, one of my all-time favorite TED speakers. On paper, he didn’t really start with an advantage; he spoke English with a strong foreign accent, and his key topic was statistics and demographics, something most of us associate with good sleep, not with great presentations.
Yet, Hans’ enthusiasm and passion on stage, combined with his unique way to use numbers to tell meaningful stories, meant that his presentations were always a high point of any TED conference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To learn or not to learn your speech by heart</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2020-10-06-should-i-learn-a-presentation-by-heart/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2020-10-06-should-i-learn-a-presentation-by-heart/</guid>
      <description>Some people think that to make a great TEDx presentation, they should learn their text by heart. Our collective experience as coaches shows that it’s a good solution only IF:
You like to know your speech word for word and it fits your personal style and you know how to do it properly. If you don’t meet one of these conditions, then it’s best to avoid learning your text by heart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don’t rush your start</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2020-09-01-dont-rush-your-start/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2020-09-01-dont-rush-your-start/</guid>
      <description>Many speakers tend to rush the start of their presentation. During conferences and events, they start to speak even before they put a foot on the stage, talking as they walk towards the center, or as soon as the master of ceremonies stops to speak. It makes them look as if they think they are suffering from the “imposter” syndrome, insecure and unsure that they should be speaking on stage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to disable all animations in a PowerPoint presentation</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2020/07/07/2020-07-07-how-to-skip-all-animations-in-a-presentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2020/07/07/2020-07-07-how-to-skip-all-animations-in-a-presentation/</guid>
      <description>Do animations in a presentation make you feel seasick? Animations in PowerPoint are great, until they aren&amp;rsquo;t. A small dose of animation is fine, but presentations with too many animations can be cumbersome to watch in presenter mode.
Luckily, PowerPoint offers a simple functionality to disable all animations in one go. In the ribbon, go to the &amp;ldquo;Slide Show&amp;rdquo; tab, then click on &amp;ldquo;Set up Slide Show&amp;rdquo;. Then simply tick the box &amp;ldquo;show without animation&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s end discrimination</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2020/06/05/2020-06-05-let-s-end-discrimination/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2020/06/05/2020-06-05-let-s-end-discrimination/</guid>
      <description>Recent events have shown that discrimination kills, and it has to stop. Many minorities, not just in America, but everywhere in the world, have to suffer injustice for no other reason than a difference of color, gender or belief. Our position at Ideas on Stage is simple: discrimination, in any form, is not acceptable and must be actively fought.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to facilitate virtual meetings</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2020/04/24/2020-04-24-how_to_facilitate_virtual_meetings/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2020/04/24/2020-04-24-how_to_facilitate_virtual_meetings/</guid>
      <description>A virtual meeting without a facilitator is like an orchestra without a conductor: the result is usually an unpleasant cacophony. Before, during and after the meeting, the facilitator’s role is key to ensure harmony, allow each participant to contribute, and achieve the meeting’s objectives.
The role will depend on the type of meeting. For a webinar, the facilitator will need to focus on sound quality, ensuring those not speaking have muted their microphones (or doing it for them), and handling the text chat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to use slides effectively in online meetings</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2020/04/10/2020-04-10-how_to_use_slides_effectively_in_online_meetings/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2020/04/10/2020-04-10-how_to_use_slides_effectively_in_online_meetings/</guid>
      <description>It’s no secret that most slide presentations are boring, ineffective wastes of time. PowerPoint isn’t the problem - it’s how people (mis)use it.
In fact most business meetings would do well to avoid slides - and presentations - altogether. Meetings should be for discussion, connection, decisions… not for information-sharing. Using a wonderfully-crafted PowerPoint deck to share information is like using an iPad Pro as a frisbee: sure, it’s well-designed and better than most other tablets, but it’s still the wrong tool for the job.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virtual Speaking Success: Effective communication in online meetings</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2020/04/06/2020-04-06-virtual_speaking_success_effective_communication_in_online_meetings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2020/04/06/2020-04-06-virtual_speaking_success_effective_communication_in_online_meetings/</guid>
      <description>As many of us are learning, it’s easy to arrange a virtual meeting, but not so easy to run one successfully. There is quite a steep learning curve.
One vital area to work on is speaking in virtual meetings. People often complain of video issues, microphone issues, poor vocal expression, monotonous speakers, and poor interactivity. Step 5 of our Virtual Meeting Revolution process is called Connection for a good reason: when speaking in an online meeting, you need to connect with the other participants, and you can’t connect if they are so bored they are not paying attention, or if they gave up trying to understand what you are saying.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 5 Virtual Meeting Revolutions</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2020/04/01/2020-04-01-the_5_virtual_meeting_revolutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2020/04/01/2020-04-01-the_5_virtual_meeting_revolutions/</guid>
      <description>What are you going to do today? For many typical office workers, the answer is: too many meetings, and not enough time to work. It’s rare that meetings and productivity coincide.
At the time of writing, many of us are required to work from home, so physical meetings have become virtual meetings, and they’re not always an improvement. Online meetings present their own set of challenges, principally because unless everyone has their camera switched on, one participant won’t know whether another is paying attention, or is checking Instagram, or has gone to walk his dog, aiming to return at the end of the meeting in time to say goodbye and pick up as few actions as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Top 5 TEDx Talks in number of views</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2020/03/30/2020-03-30-the-top-5-tedx-talks-in-number-of-views/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2020/03/30/2020-03-30-the-top-5-tedx-talks-in-number-of-views/</guid>
      <description>We worked with a lot of TEDx events over the years, and some of the talks have accumulated hundreds of thousands views, some even getting above the 1 million mark. Here are the top 5 talks of events we participated to, in number of views.
In fifth place we have Jean-Gabriel Causse, speaking at TEDx Dunkerque, with nearly 600,000 views. Color me shocked, but his is talk about the power of colors is full of interesting details.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How we deliver our services remotely</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2020/03/03/2020-03-03-how-we-deliver-our-services-remotely/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2020/03/03/2020-03-03-how-we-deliver-our-services-remotely/</guid>
      <description>With the current health crisis looming, remote work may no longer be a choice, but a precautionary measure. How do we do it at Ideas on Stage?
From day one, Ideas on Stage was created as a digital company. In fact, for many years, we didn&amp;rsquo;t have a physical office. Even today, we strongly encourage our employees to work remotely and limit their travel to what&amp;rsquo;s necessary. We can deliver 90% of our services at distance to our clients, whether it&amp;rsquo;s the creation of a presentation, coaching or training.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why should I hire an external event coordinator? An experienced event manager&#39;s point of view</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2020/02/25/2020-02-25-why-should-i-hire-an-external-event-coordinator-an-experienced-event-manager-s-point-of-view/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2020/02/25/2020-02-25-why-should-i-hire-an-external-event-coordinator-an-experienced-event-manager-s-point-of-view/</guid>
      <description>A lot of people think that organizing an event is within everyone’s reach. But is it really true? If you want to organize one for your company, a lot is at stake, including brand reputation as well as the satisfaction of your customers or guests. If you don’t want to take any chances and make a positive impression, it’s important to set up a team dedicated to your project.
If you are the organizer in the hot seat, you are likely asking yourself many questions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If you want to be brief and to the point, prepare</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2020/02/04/2020-02-04-if-you-want-to-be-brief-and-to-the-point-prepare/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2020/02/04/2020-02-04-if-you-want-to-be-brief-and-to-the-point-prepare/</guid>
      <description>A few months ago I recorded an episode for our video channel “The Business Presentation Revolution.” Initially, my content was too long to fit in the 3 to 4 minutes running time that we had planned. Looking at my script, I realized that many sentences could be simplified, some details omitted, and the structure streamlined.
After several dry runs and rewrites, we finally managed to get the video down to 3 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The 3 Magic Ingredients of Great Presentations</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2020/01/29/2020-01-29-the_3_magic_ingredients_of_great_presentations/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2020/01/29/2020-01-29-the_3_magic_ingredients_of_great_presentations/</guid>
      <description>Is there a perfect recipe for a successful presentation? No. Partly it depends on the audience and the context: a boardroom presentation shouldn’t look like a TED talk, even if the subject is the same. And different presentations at the same event – a conference, a demo day, an Executive Committee meeting – should also look different from each other, because otherwise none of them will stand out.
So if there is no magic formula, are there at least some key ingredients we should always include?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life after TED: How to show up in the Post-TED world</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2020/01/07/2020-01-07-life-after-ted-how-to-show-up-in-the-post-ted-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2020/01/07/2020-01-07-life-after-ted-how-to-show-up-in-the-post-ted-world/</guid>
      <description>You know that mental image you have of what you think you should be like on stage? Yes, that one based upon a mash-up of some of your favorite TED speakers whom you are certain you’ll never be as good as. Well, forget it!
Welcome to the Post-TED style of authenticity centered presentation.
In my last article, Wash that TED right out of your head: New Post-TED presentation, we explored some of the foundational reasons which many are experiencing, and what I call, “TED-like style Fatigue”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Should I stand behind the lectern?</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/12/17/2019-12-17-should-i-stand-behind-the-lectern/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/12/17/2019-12-17-should-i-stand-behind-the-lectern/</guid>
      <description>The lectern is a staple of traditional speeches. We see politicians use them all the time, as well as&amp;hellip; who else? Who, apart from politicians, still uses a lectern?
If I had to create a 0 to 10 presentation scale where 0 is totally informal and 10 is fully formal, I would say that running naked on stage is 0 and speaking from behind a lectern is 11. Yes, the lectern is really that formal, and in 99% of the cases, that&amp;rsquo;s not a good thing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three most annoying problems with business presentations, according to PowerPoint expert Dave Paradi</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/12/10/2019-12-10-three-most-annoying-problems-presentations-powerpoint/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/12/10/2019-12-10-three-most-annoying-problems-presentations-powerpoint/</guid>
      <description>Dave Paradi, an expert on PowerPoint presentations, has published the results of the annoying PowerPoint survey. We are not going to discuss the full results here, but what is clear is that the top 3 hasn’t changed much in many years. You could probably guess them just by asking yourself “what do I hate about PowerPoint presentations?” The top three problems are:
The speaker reads the slides to us
The text is too small</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The story behind the story</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/12/03/2019-12-03-the-story-behind-the-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/12/03/2019-12-03-the-story-behind-the-story/</guid>
      <description>First, a mandatory disclaimer: I like Sixties-Boomer music. If poor musical tastes offend you, don’t read this.
Last week, I was searching for an old song on YouTube, when suddenly I noticed a video from Joan Baez. I realized that, despite priding myself on my knowledge of 60s music, I never actually listened to one of her songs. So I clicked and listened to it. It was called Diamonds and Rust.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Being coached is the mark of true leaders</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/11/26/2019-11-26-being-coached-is-the-mark-of-true-leaders/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/11/26/2019-11-26-being-coached-is-the-mark-of-true-leaders/</guid>
      <description>Some leaders are afraid to let other people know that they took public speaking coaching. I want to explain why it’s a mistake, and why the best leaders are proud of being coached.
The Consulting Partner who hired me back in 1996, for a company that was then called Andersen Consulting, was an extremely charismatic person and an excellent orator. One advice he gave openly to his peers, and to us young consultants, was to get professional public speaking coaching to become better orators.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happens when two political parties use the same rhetoric?</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/11/19/2019-11-19-what-happens-when-two-political-parties-use-the-same-rhetoric/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/11/19/2019-11-19-what-happens-when-two-political-parties-use-the-same-rhetoric/</guid>
      <description>What happens when two parties position themselves in a similar manner on the same topic? Simple: the one which is the most credible wins. By “most credible,” I mean “the one that incarnates the rhetoric with the most authenticity.”
There is a mistake that has been made by many traditional parties. Some traditional parties saw new parties start to gain popularity by advocating extremist views. So they started to adopt a slightly watered down version of these views to attract voters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Establish a Connection First</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/11/12/2019-11-12-establish-a-connection-first/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/11/12/2019-11-12-establish-a-connection-first/</guid>
      <description>You’ve probably already seen those presenters who climb on stage and rush into their presentation, apparently oblivious to the fact that they have an audience in front of them. Once they’re done, they rush out of the stage, as if you didn’t exist.
To avoid looking like one of these presenters, try to establish a connection with the audience as soon as possible. Look and smile at them as you enter the stage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cliché slides</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/11/05/2019-11-05-cliche-slides/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/11/05/2019-11-05-cliche-slides/</guid>
      <description>You’ve probably all seen these slides: they use a picture which is “cliché,” like two shaking hands. Using a few of these clichés is fine, because they are often the clearest way to illustrate the idea of the slide; it’s nice to be creative, but clarity of the message comes first.
But some presentations seem to overflow with these clichés, using them on every slide. So I asked myself the question: why are some presentations nearly cliché-free, while other presentations are full of them?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wash that Ted right out of your head: new post-Ted presentation</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/10/29/2019-10-29-wash-that-ted-right-out-of-your-head-avoiding-bad-ted-presentations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/10/29/2019-10-29-wash-that-ted-right-out-of-your-head-avoiding-bad-ted-presentations/</guid>
      <description>The days of the expert or reliable narrator are over. We have entered the “Disinformation Age” where fake news, conspiracy stories, and meme warfare rule.
One of the most prominent casualties, at least from a presentation perspective, is the TED-like style, top down, subject matter expert: the teacher or preacher schooling their passively sitting and listening students.
We see trust move from the command and control leadership style and morph into something vastly flatter, decentralized/distributed, and perhaps even autonomously self-organizing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet Camille, your new contact</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/10/15/2019-10-15-meet-camille-your-new-contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/10/15/2019-10-15-meet-camille-your-new-contact/</guid>
      <description>A funny thing happened when I was describing my “dream job” to a friend. I imagined a company whose mission would be to help people become great presenters, and had a culture that was both supporting and nurturing while remaining professional and attentive to clients’ needs. My friend said: “I know that company!”
A few weeks later after a relaxing summer vacation between positions, I found myself in the company of all my new colleagues, some whom I met for the very first time, at our annual Fall team meeting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Check If Your Presentation Remote Works Without Anyone Noticing</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/10/08/2019-10-08-how-to-check-if-your-presentation-remote-works-without-anyone-noticing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/10/08/2019-10-08-how-to-check-if-your-presentation-remote-works-without-anyone-noticing/</guid>
      <description>It’s your turn to present. You’ve launched your presentation and enter the stage. But how do you know if your presentation remote is working? If you start clicking back and forth between your first and second slide to see if it is working, everyone will notice what you’re doing, and you will not make a great first impression.
Luckily, someone shared a simple tip on twitter. Just duplicate your first slide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use eye contact to stop moving around on stage</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/10/01/2019-10-01-use-eye-contact-to-stop-moving-around-on-stage/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/10/01/2019-10-01-use-eye-contact-to-stop-moving-around-on-stage/</guid>
      <description>Moving with purpose on stage is good. Moving around aimlessly is not. It’s what we call derivative actions, things that we do unconsciously that betray our stress, lack of confidence or lack of preparation. Luckily, it’s very easy to stop parasitic movements, but the solution sounds counterintuitive: use eye contact to &amp;ldquo;anchor&amp;rdquo; yourself on the ground.
Yes, that’s right. Making eye contact with your audience will stabilise your attention and will prevent your feet from moving you around the stage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>12 Tips for an Amazing Event: Don’t Just Sit There, DO Something</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/09/24/2019-09-24-to-make-an-amazing-event-don-t-just-sit-there-do-something/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/09/24/2019-09-24-to-make-an-amazing-event-don-t-just-sit-there-do-something/</guid>
      <description>What is it about designing events that I love so much? Suddenly I think of cookie dough, the small crunchy granules of sugar blended with butter, the heavenly flavour of vanilla extract and the sublime melt of dark chocolate chips. Even before I bake the cookies, the main event in this case, the ingredients themselves have satisfied.
Designing events are similar because I love what goes into making them delicious–I mean, shine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The adult and the spoiled kid</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/09/17/2019-09-17-the-adult-and-the-spoilt-kid/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/09/17/2019-09-17-the-adult-and-the-spoilt-kid/</guid>
      <description>Some adults behave like bad, spoiled kids. They whine, they threaten, they become petty if they don’t get their way. They don’t hesitate to lie, or even worse, use the emotional card to play the victim, make you look bad and make you submit to their will.
These people are easy to recognize, but very difficult to deal with. Just think of the child rolling on the floor screaming. His parents will look bad whatever they do: scold him, do nothing, leave… they have zero good solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The leadership Triangle</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/09/09/2019-09-09-the-leadership-triangle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/09/09/2019-09-09-the-leadership-triangle/</guid>
      <description>There is one key objective at the heart of all presenting. Persuading the human mind.
Today there is a war on for attention and space, with the human mind as object of the conquest. In 2019, emotions rule the stage and calm reasoned logic seems to have gone out of fashion. Individually and collectively, most of us are getting our information from sound bites, news summaries, and short burst headlines provided by our iPhone feed; while opinions change from one glance at the screen to the next.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A student’s view of Ideas on Stage</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/09/02/2019-09-02-a-student-s-view-of-ideas-on-stage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/09/02/2019-09-02-a-student-s-view-of-ideas-on-stage/</guid>
      <description>Recently I had the chance to do an internship with Ideas on Stage, which has been by far one of my best experiences.
At first, I didn’t quite know what I had stepped into. It was a totally new place and I walked in full of curiosity.
You might know the famous saying “Behind every successful man there is a woman.” Well, within this week I understood that “behind every successful presentation there is Ideas on Stage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>“Others Too”: Zoom&#39;s Terrible Communication Misstep</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/07/16/2019-07-16-others-too-zoom-s-terrible-communication-misstep/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/07/16/2019-07-16-others-too-zoom-s-terrible-communication-misstep/</guid>
      <description>You may have heard about it, a basic security problem was found in Zoom for Mac, that allowed attackers to turn the camera on remotely. Zoom is an application used to organize videoconferences on the web. It works well and has been widely adopted by corporations and individuals seeking to provide a quality service to employees working remotely or on different sites.
The security problem itself was easy to correct, and, at the time of this article, should have been fixed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Put your most nervous speakers early in the program</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/07/09/2019-07-09-put-your-most-nervous-speakers-early-in-the-program/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/07/09/2019-07-09-put-your-most-nervous-speakers-early-in-the-program/</guid>
      <description>One of the most stressful moments when speaking at an event is actually not during your presentation, but the hours before your presentation. To some speakers, the wait can be so stressful that they completely lose their presence. As mother nature didn&amp;rsquo;t give humans an appropriate instinctive response to face the stress of a presentation, they adopt one of the basic survival techniques for protection: they fight the public, they flee, or they &amp;ldquo;play dead&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Start with the subject, not the context</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/07/02/2019-07-02-why-you-should-avoid-long-winded-introductions-in-your-presentations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/07/02/2019-07-02-why-you-should-avoid-long-winded-introductions-in-your-presentations/</guid>
      <description>You know these presenters who speak for 20 minutes before they finally understand what they are talking about? I had a colleague who was just like that. When I asked him why he couldn’t do a shorter introduction, he said that he felt that all the details he gave in his opening were indispensable to understand the presentation. In other words, he was taking the time to explain the context before talking about his subject.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Should I move on stage when speaking?</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/06/25/2019-06-25-should-i-move-on-stage-when-speaking/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/06/25/2019-06-25-should-i-move-on-stage-when-speaking/</guid>
      <description>Should we move on stage when speaking, to avoid looking static? Or should we stay put on our feet, avoiding any unnecessary movements? Strangely, if we ask different coaches, we&amp;rsquo;re likely to get different answers. I remember meeting several coaches who followed classical theatre training at &amp;ldquo;La Comédie Française&amp;rdquo;, and they would recommend that you don&amp;rsquo;t move on stage when you&amp;rsquo;re speaking. I also remember other coaches telling startup pitchers that they looked like dead trees devoid of any energy because they didn&amp;rsquo;t move enough.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The body language myth of crossing your arms</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/06/18/2019-06-18-the-body-language-myth-of-crossing-your-arms/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/06/18/2019-06-18-the-body-language-myth-of-crossing-your-arms/</guid>
      <description>The communication industry is full of myths that are repeated without any scientific backing. I recently watched this video by a former FBI body language specialist. He used his skills to help bust criminals. The first thing he does (at 1&#39;10&amp;quot;) is bust the myth that crossing your arms is a blocking behavior.
Bingo. I cannot agree more with this. Most people cross their arms because it&amp;rsquo;s a comfortable position, not because they have a mental block, period.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bonjour les Champs Élysées !</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/06/11/2019-06-11-bonjour-les-champs-elysees/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/06/11/2019-06-11-bonjour-les-champs-elysees/</guid>
      <description>Ideas on Stage now welcomes you in their Champs Élysées offices. Located in the heart of Paris, they offer the perfect atmosphere to make the best out of your public speaking coaching sessions. And above all, the coffee is very good (although we recommend to avoid it before speaking in public)!
What a change a few years can make. When we created the company, we rented a space in a shared office.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public Speaking Coaching With Virtual Reality in Paris</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/06/04/2019-06-04-public-speaking-coaching-with-virtual-reality-in-paris/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/06/04/2019-06-04-public-speaking-coaching-with-virtual-reality-in-paris/</guid>
      <description>I don’t think it’s exaggerated to say that the mentality in public speaking coaching and oratory coaching is fairly conservative. After all, many of the techniques that are taught today were developed by some guys in togas before year one of our calendar!
But the world has changed a lot since then, and recent technology advances have opened new exciting possibilities for public presentation training. One of these technologies is virtual reality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Prezi failed at revolutionizing presentations</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/05/28/2019-05-28-why-prezi-failed-at-revolutionizing-presentations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/05/28/2019-05-28-why-prezi-failed-at-revolutionizing-presentations/</guid>
      <description>In 2009, the year when TED decided to launch its TEDx license program, Prezi was born out of the desire to overcome the limitations of tools like PowerPoint and Keynote. With its dramatic zooming and panning effects, it certainly did catch the eye of audiences worldwide when it was introduced. But its over-reliance on movement effects quickly became a visual nuisance, making the audience feel as if they had been on a boat caught in a category 10 hurricane.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game of Thrones and the importance of the storyline</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/05/21/2019-05-21-game-of-thrones-and-the-importance-of-the-storyline/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/05/21/2019-05-21-game-of-thrones-and-the-importance-of-the-storyline/</guid>
      <description>By now, the last episode of the cult show Game of Thrones has aired. I haven’t seen it, and I didn’t want to see it before writing this article. Whether it accurately follows the storyline of the books or not is a moot point, because said book hasn’t been written yet. And it shows. I won’t spoil anything, don’t worry. But everyone noticed that the screenwriting of the seasons that could rely on George R.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A New Cure for Medical Conferences</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/05/16/2019-05-16-a-new-cure-for-medical-conferences/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/05/16/2019-05-16-a-new-cure-for-medical-conferences/</guid>
      <description>Most conferences are fairly boring. Even well-known tech conferences fail to engage their audiences all the time. But medical conferences can be among the worst. Check out this quick interview between Ideas on Stage, new partners with Doctors 2.0 &amp;amp; You, and Denise Silber to find out how to take medical (and other) events to the next level.
Our friend Ross Fisher, a paediatric surgeon based in the UK, has had enough of poor medical communication, and when he’s not operating, he spends time educating doctors about a better way to present.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Makes an Amazing, Culture-Shifting Event?</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/05/15/2019-05-15-what-makes-an-amazing-culture-shifting-event/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/05/15/2019-05-15-what-makes-an-amazing-culture-shifting-event/</guid>
      <description>Case study of Mövenpick Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts’ 2018 General Managers conference in Regensdorf, Switzerland.
__
The Story It was a cool September morning in Paris when my colleague and I sat down in a stylish hotel dining room to meet a Mr. Olivier Chavy, President of Mövenpick Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts.
Before 8:00am we jumped right into business: Olivier’s vision and objectives for the spring 2018 general managers conference. “We want people to leave with the sensation ‘wow, I am really proud to work for this company’,” emphasized Chavy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our upcoming events in London</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/05/14/2019-05-10-london-calling/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/05/14/2019-05-10-london-calling/</guid>
      <description>A big part of the way many companies sell is to create a presentation that shows the complex benefits of the solution they are offering.
But even great businesses — which are very good at what they do — often lack the ability to clearly share their message to their target audience using presentations.
There are many reasons why people and companies want to improve their presentations but at the heart of it what they really want is to win more deals, get more customers and sell more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why would people care about your presentation?</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/05/14/2019-05-14-why-would-people-care-about-your-presentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/05/14/2019-05-14-why-would-people-care-about-your-presentation/</guid>
      <description>Why would people care about your product?
Why would people care about your service?
Why would people care about your project?
Why would people care about your career?
Why would people care about your investment?
Why would people care about your discovery?
Why would people care about your research?
Why would people care about your videos?
Why would people care about your book?
Why would people care about your ideas?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Should you actually slow down your speech when you present?</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/05/07/2019-05-07-should-you-actually-slow-down-your-speech-when-you-present/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/05/07/2019-05-07-should-you-actually-slow-down-your-speech-when-you-present/</guid>
      <description>“You have to speak slower!”
This advice is a staple of oratory coaching. But I think it is sometimes given by coaches without thinking about the consequences, and that it can actually do more bad than good. Let me explain why.
The first reason is simply that not every speaker needs to speak slowly. Speaking slowly is done for several reasons, such as increasing the perceived gravitas (authority) or allowing the public to digest complex information more easily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Elon Musk running out of credibility?</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/04/30/2019-04-30-is-elon-musk-running-out-of-credibility/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/04/30/2019-04-30-is-elon-musk-running-out-of-credibility/</guid>
      <description>Gizmodo wrote this rather funny piece about Elon Musk’s latest rash of announcements, such as fully autonomous cars and a million robotaxis by 2020. Now, Gizmodo is not exactly known as a staple of great journalism, but sometimes they have a knack to hit the nail on the head. In this case, the fact that for several years Elon Musk repeatedly promised—and failed to deliver—full autonomous driving. Honestly, s eeing how hard it is to achieve full autonomy, and how many problems are left with Tesla’s current autopilot system, it is hard to believe these new promises will actually materialize.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 7 deadly sins of slide design</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/04/23/2019-04-23-the-7-deadly-sins-of-slide-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/04/23/2019-04-23-the-7-deadly-sins-of-slide-design/</guid>
      <description>This is a quick list of seven common problems that we see with slides created by non specialists. However they are relatively easy to spot, and you don’t have to be a graphic designer to avoid them. Read on and your next slides will look much better!
Too much content. The goal is not to cover every single inch with content. It’s not because you have some space left at the bottom of the slide that you should put something there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Barbara Minto’s pyramid principle outdated?</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/04/16/2019-04-16-is-barbara-minto-s-pyramid-principle-outdated/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/04/16/2019-04-16-is-barbara-minto-s-pyramid-principle-outdated/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks ago someone spoke a name that I hadn’t heard in a long, very long time: Barbara Minto. She’s the author of the Pyramid Principle, a book that was long considered, and sometimes still is, the gold standard of presentation structuring in the consulting industry. But it was back in the eighties. So I’ll dare to ask the question: is the pyramid principle outdated?
If you’re not familiar with the pyramid principle, it is a method to lay out the information in a presentation in the most efficient way possible, based on how people with little time, especially executives, absorb information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use your iPhone as backup for important presentations</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/04/09/2019-04-09-use-your-iphone-as-backup-for-important-presentations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/04/09/2019-04-09-use-your-iphone-as-backup-for-important-presentations/</guid>
      <description>Recently my computer, a MacBook Pro, needed to be repaired. I had to do without a laptop for several weeks. And of course, during those weeks I needed to present with slides. Luckily, with my iPhone and a couple of accessories I had everything I needed:
A (not too old) iPhone or iPad A lightning to HDMI adapter A lightning power cable and brick (using the HDMI adapter drains the battery fast).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The meatball sundae presentation effect</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/04/02/2019-04-02-the-meatball-sundae-presentation-e/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/04/02/2019-04-02-the-meatball-sundae-presentation-e/</guid>
      <description>Seth Godin coined the term “meatball sundae” several years ago in a book that explained that putting two great things together does not always create something better. And in the worst case, such as a meatball sundae, it can actually create something nobody wants.
The meatball sundae presentation effect can happen at two levels: at the event level, and at the individual presentation level.
Let’s take Apple’s latest keynote as an example of the meatball sundae effect at the event level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is there a drug to get rid of my fear of public speaking?</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/03/26/2019-03-26-is-there-a-drug-to-get-rid-of-my-fear-of-public-speaking/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/03/26/2019-03-26-is-there-a-drug-to-get-rid-of-my-fear-of-public-speaking/</guid>
      <description>It may sound weird, but this is a question we get asked from time to time: “Do you know a prescription drug that would help me reduce my stress on stage?”
We’re not talking about illegal drugs, but legal drugs sold in pharmacies. There are a lot of those designed by pharmaceutical companies to reduce stress, anxiety, blood pressure, cardiac rhythm, etc. We are not doctors, so we cannot say anything about them from a medical perspective.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In presentations, don’t do a flash back, do a flash present</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/03/19/2019-03-19-in-presentations-dont-do-a-flash/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/03/19/2019-03-19-in-presentations-dont-do-a-flash/</guid>
      <description>It’s a trick I learned when studying how movies and TV shows are written. You don’t do a flash back, you do a flash present. For presentations, that means that you don’t tell the story as something that is over; that makes the audience passive. Instead, you bring the scene from the past into the present, or you bring the audience to the past, and tell it as if it is happening right now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to Andrea Pacini, UK Presentation Director</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/03/12/2019-03-12-andrea-pacini-uk-presentation-director/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/03/12/2019-03-12-andrea-pacini-uk-presentation-director/</guid>
      <description>This March Andrea Pacini joined Ideas on Stage as UK Presentation Director, meaning that Ideas on Stage now has a direct presence in France, Spain, Italy and the United Kingdom - and we serve the rest of the world from these four locations.
We sat down with Andrea for a short interview.
Q: What is your background? A: I am Italian, and I studied in Italy and Ireland. I then did an internship in Cambridge, where I fell in love with the UK and decided to stay there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The triple stakes of great presentations</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/03/05/2019-03-05-triple-stakes-of-great-presentations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/03/05/2019-03-05-triple-stakes-of-great-presentations/</guid>
      <description>The best presentations have three stakes, three reasons &amp;ldquo;why&amp;rdquo; they are important:
The first stake is about you: why is the topic important for you? This is the reason you, and not somebody else, is on stage to deliver the presentation. The second stake is about your audience: why is it important for them? This is the reason why your audience is there to listen to you instead of doing something else.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 warning signs someone is not ready to speak at your TEDx event</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/02/26/2019-02-26-5-warning-signs-someone-is-not-ready-for-ted/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/02/26/2019-02-26-5-warning-signs-someone-is-not-ready-for-ted/</guid>
      <description>“Don’t worry, I’m experienced, I speak at conferences all the time!” How many times have we heard that sentence from speakers who never did a TEDx style talk, yet think that, because of experience, they can just wing it? For us, it’s not reassuring. Quite the opposite, it’s a clear warning sign that the speaker doesn’t really know what is expected of him. Here are five warning signs that give you clues that your speaker may not be ready to give a TEDx style talk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don’t do an elevator pitch. Start a conversation.</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/02/19/2019-02-19-dont-do-an-elevator-pitch-start-a-conversation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/02/19/2019-02-19-dont-do-an-elevator-pitch-start-a-conversation/</guid>
      <description>If you’re a Startup founder, you’ve heard this all before. “Your elevator pitch should be able to convince anyone in 30 seconds in an elevator”. Hold on hold on hold on! Let’s pause for a few seconds. Imagine that the roles are reversed. You’re in the elevator, lost in your thoughts, minding your own business. There is one other person in it, who you don’t know, and that person is looking intensely at you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to starve the presentation vultures (part 2)</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/02/12/2019-02-12-how-to-starve-the-presentation-vultures-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/02/12/2019-02-12-how-to-starve-the-presentation-vultures-2/</guid>
      <description>Last week we saw how presentation vultures can destroy your confidence and ability to present in front of an audience. We saw that the best way to fend them off is to strengthen your vital space anchor. But how can you do that?
If your presentation has an objective, a clear message, it is much easier to use it as an anchor. Let’s imagine for example that the key message is that your presentation is about a new software service that offers necessary services to protect your IT systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to starve the presentation vultures (part 1)</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/02/05/2019-02-05-how-to-starve-the-presentation-vultures-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/02/05/2019-02-05-how-to-starve-the-presentation-vultures-1/</guid>
      <description>Maybe you feel that your last presentation was a complete failure. You didn’t manage to shake off your nerves. You became confused. The client or your boss criticized you. Maybe you’ve been caught in a downward spiral for some time, each criticism making you lose confidence, and making the next presentation worse. I have good news for you: no matter what your situation is, this vicious circle can be broken, and you gain the necessary confidence to enjoy presenting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to steal the show</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/01/29/2019-01-29-how-to-steal-the-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/01/29/2019-01-29-how-to-steal-the-show/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks ago, Ideas on Stage had the privilege of organizing a sales presentation training for Krauthammer at Dolce La Hulpe, close to Brussels in Belgium. For us, delivering a training for dozens of senior people at Krauthammer, one of the world’s most respected sales and management training companies, felt like designing something for Jonathan Ive, Apple’s legendary designer: a bit intimidating but incredibly exciting.
The training met with great success, and it was fantastic to work with such talented people, but what I will remember most are two presentations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Listen like a butterfly, talk like a bee</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/01/22/2019-01-22-listen-like-a-butterfly-talk-like-a-bee/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/01/22/2019-01-22-listen-like-a-butterfly-talk-like-a-bee/</guid>
      <description>I know, paraphrasing the motto of the great Muhammad Ali, “Float like a butterfly, sting like a bee”, doesn’t seem to make much sense. Yet my point is that in a debate it is extremely important to listen and move with a maximum of agility, and talk with a maximum of punch.
Take the example of the Gilets jaunes controversy in France. The government was completely taken by surprise by the popularity of the movement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I presented at CES and all I got was a bunch of ungrateful tweets</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/01/15/2019-01-14-i-presented-at-ces-and-all-i-got-was-a-bunch-of-ungrateful-tweets/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/01/15/2019-01-14-i-presented-at-ces-and-all-i-got-was-a-bunch-of-ungrateful-tweets/</guid>
      <description>My colleague Ricardo pointed me to a tweet from Rene Ritchie, who was attending the conferences at CES.
Dear almost everyone on stage at CES: Pay ungodly amounts of money — anything you have to — to get WWDC speaker training ASAP.
Or go to Juilliard or the Royal Shakespeare Company for a month. Whatever works for you.
&amp;mdash; Rene Ritchie (@reneritchie) January 8, 2019 This tweet says:
&amp;ldquo;Dear almost everyone on stage at CES: Pay ungodly amounts of money — anything you have to — to get WWDC speaker training ASAP.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What presentation lessons can we learn from Apple’s profit warning?</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/01/08/2019-01-07-what-presentation-lessons-can-we-learn-from-apples-profit-warning/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/01/08/2019-01-07-what-presentation-lessons-can-we-learn-from-apples-profit-warning/</guid>
      <description>By now, you’ve probably heard that Apple was doomed. Last Wednesday they released a profit warning press release, followed by an interview with CEO Tim Cook.
I’m all too aware of Apple’s previous profit warning. Back in the nineties, after Steve Jobs returned to Apple and a Saudi prince (whose name I forget) bought a lot of Apple shares, I decided that I would be a smart investor and I bought Apple shares too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Inform, Transform</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/01/07/2019-01-07-dont-inform-transform/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/01/07/2019-01-07-dont-inform-transform/</guid>
      <description>Too many presentations aim only to inform, yet this is one thing oral presentations are particularly bad at &amp;ndash; we forget most of what we hear within 30 seconds.
If you want people to remember information, give them a document and a coffee, and time to read. Then you can answer their questions, discuss, agree on the next steps, and leave.
This is what happens in meetings at companies like Amazon and LinkedIn, where not only do meetings never have slides - they never have presentations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Speaking Lessons from President Macron</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2018/10/10/2018-10-10-5-speaking-lessons-from-president-macron/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2018/10/10/2018-10-10-5-speaking-lessons-from-president-macron/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday French President Emmanuel Macron took live, unscripted questions from an audience of 2000 tech entrepreneurs and investors at Station F, the undisputed hub of the French startup community. Ideas on Stage may not be a tech company, but we have helped thousands of start-ups with their pitches, and partner with many accelerators including Ashoka’s ShareIT.io, based at Station F. So we are very much part of the French Tech ecosystem, and very interested in how it is evolving under its new Director, our good friend Kat Borlongan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are you ready?</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2018/10/08/2018-10-08-are-you-ready/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2018/10/08/2018-10-08-are-you-ready/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s already October and you know what that means&amp;hellip; Firming up plans for next year. Pitching projects. Assigning budgets. And ultimately getting creative about how to expire old, ineffective systems and implement a smarter and better approach. Look around and catch the shift. It&amp;rsquo;s not time for just another step forward. It&amp;rsquo;s time to leap.
At Ideas on Stage we coach, train and design for international clients and companies large and small, from CAC 40 enterprises to startups and incubators.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Business Can Learn From TED</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2018/04/10/2018-04-10-what-business-can-learn-from-ted/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2018/04/10/2018-04-10-what-business-can-learn-from-ted/</guid>
      <description>Today marks the start of TED2018, the latest edition of the world&amp;rsquo;s best-known modern conference. Participants in Vancouver will be treated to high-quality talks from well-prepared speakers, and will leave feeling energized and inspired.
Back in the office, you and your colleagues will no doubt be subjected to low-quality presentations from poorly-prepared speakers, and you will leave feeling bored and uninspired.
Business presentations are not TED talks. A board meeting is not a stage with a round red carpet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7 Tips for Overcoming the Fear of Presenting</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2018/04/09/2018-04-10-7-tips-for-overcoming-the-fear-of-presenting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2018/04/09/2018-04-10-7-tips-for-overcoming-the-fear-of-presenting/</guid>
      <description>Fear doesn&amp;rsquo;t remove the danger. Embrace it and get on top of your presentations.
&amp;ldquo;There is nothing to fear but fear itself&amp;rdquo; - a memorable line from President Franklin D. Roosevelt&amp;rsquo;s inaugural address in 1932 at the depths of the Great Depression. At the time he may not have realized it, but his words are among the most powerful pieces of advice for public speaking.
After all, what we all fear in presentations is succumbing to fear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 presentation lessons from The Darkest Hour</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2018/02/16/2018-02-16-the-darkest-hour-presentation-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2018/02/16/2018-02-16-the-darkest-hour-presentation-lessons/</guid>
      <description>Have you seen Gary Oldman in his interpretation of Churchill in the latest biopic by Joe Wright? If you have not, please go. It’s jaw-dropping. His outstanding performance may very soon win him an Oscar. You will enjoy some of the finest acting and also benefit from precious presentation lessons from the Master Orator.
Here are 3 takeaways from the movie, which you can immediately apply for your next keynote, sales meeting or investor pitch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New brand, new design</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2018/01/26/2018-01-26-new-brand-new-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2018/01/26/2018-01-26-new-brand-new-design/</guid>
      <description>I am not a naive man. I have reasonable doubts that Santa does not really exist. So instead of writing a letter that I knew he would not answer I thought it was time to refresh the Ideas on Stage Brand, which hasn’t changed since the creation of the company in 2010.
We started with the font. We really love Gotham, the masterpiece from Tobias Frere-Jones. Its iconic design is built on a strong lineage of geometric sans serif fonts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TEDx Saclay – Worth all the Applause</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/12/01/2017-12-01-tedxsaclay/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/12/01/2017-12-01-tedxsaclay/</guid>
      <description>For the third year running, Ideas on Stage was very happy to partner with the TEDx Saclay conference, which took place this November 30, 2017 in the brand-new CentraleSupélec amphitheater at the Plateau de Saclay on the powerful theme of “Serving the Living”.
TEDx Saclay Keeping standards typically high, this year’s event boasted a rich program of speakers including a few notably prestigious guests such as Cédric Villani &amp;ndash; renowned mathematician and member of the French National Assembly &amp;ndash; as well as artists, scientists, students, entrepreneurs and even a Guinness World Record gamer (Kayane).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Women on Stage Workshop Returns Dec 7</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/10/30/2017-10-30-women-on-stage-workshop-december-7-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/10/30/2017-10-30-women-on-stage-workshop-december-7-2017/</guid>
      <description>This December 7th in an elegant boardroom along the Champs-Elysée something powerful will take place: the beloved Women on Stage workshop will return by popular demand led by Marion Chapsal, Chief Learning Officer and Speaking Coach. Spaces are limited to allow space for each voice and leader to present and receive personalized feedback.
Marion Chapsal
For over 20 years, Marion&amp;rsquo;s work has helped leaders to strengthen their executive presence, enhance their presentation and communication skills, and promote gender-balanced leadership in everything she does.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EDF InnovDay UNITEP 2017</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/10/06/2017-10-06-edf-innovday-unitep-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/10/06/2017-10-06-edf-innovday-unitep-2017/</guid>
      <description>Innovation is at the heart of what keeps large companies competitive. This is why EDF (Electricity of France) UNITEP organized a challenge to promote and reward internal innovative projects.
For the fourth year in a row, Ideas on Stage collaborated with EDF to coach said Innovators. We helped each group build a strong and original three-minute presentation on their innovation.
True to our methodology, we worked on developing the four elements of an impactful presentation: message, story, visuals and speaking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Helping Startups Pitch for Social Good</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/10/04/2017-10-04-helping-startups-pitch-for-social-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/10/04/2017-10-04-helping-startups-pitch-for-social-good/</guid>
      <description>The Sport Social Business Lab, aka SSBL, is an incubator specialized in sport startups for the social good. It is part of the INCO network.
Sport startups are no different from other startups: without a good pitch, they don&amp;rsquo;t stand a chance to attract investors and grow. This is why the SSBL asked Ideas on Stage to animate a three-hour pitch workshop.
As an avid sportsman who has been active in the Startup ecosystem since 2010, cofounder Pierre Morsa was uniquely qualified to deliver this workshop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taking Female Leadership by the Reins</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/09/04/2017-09-04-taking-female-leadership-by-the-reins/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/09/04/2017-09-04-taking-female-leadership-by-the-reins/</guid>
      <description>This September, something special will take place at Wisteria Acres in British Columbia, and it’s not just time with the horses. From Friday September 29th through Sunday evening on the 1st of October, Marion Chapsal and her co-facilitator Evelyn McKelvie will guide eight willing and ready women on a journey to find &amp;ndash; or fine-tune &amp;ndash; their public voice and take the stage alongside, you guessed it, horses. They call this workshop and retreat &amp;ldquo;The Heroine&amp;rsquo;s Journey&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can Women Pitch As Well As Men?</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/09/01/2017-09-01-can-women-pitch-as-well-as-men/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/09/01/2017-09-01-can-women-pitch-as-well-as-men/</guid>
      <description>It’s a simple fact that most successful startups are run by men. Why? Firstly, there are more men than women who decide - or dare - to start companies. Secondly, men are more successful at raising funds than women, and even those women who do raise funds end up raising less, on average, than their male counterparts. Having spent two years playing in the Silicon Valley arena myself, I’ve seen this truth first hand both in California and now in France.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lost in Transition?</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/08/31/2017-08-31-lost-in-transition/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/08/31/2017-08-31-lost-in-transition/</guid>
      <description>This summer Ideas on Stage partnered up with the fine people at Set’Event to help a handful of such thoughtful and committed citizens to give impactful keynote presentations at the 15th annual ACIDD event, which took place August 28-29 in Bordeaux. This year’s theme? “Lost in Transition: the time of possibilities”.
This annual event is dedicated to exploring the skills and solutions necessary to live well in our emerging digital age across all sectors, from sustainable energy to food and agriculture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who teaches the Preachers?</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/08/29/2017-08-29-who-teaches-the-preachers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/08/29/2017-08-29-who-teaches-the-preachers/</guid>
      <description>It’s not only business leaders, salespeople and entrepreneurs who need to inspire their audiences. For thousands of years, many of the most talented speakers could be found not in a shop or office but in a place of worship.
Ask people which public speaker they most admire, and many will point to Rev. Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr.. He spoke powerfully and inspired his audiences, and of the well-known speakers of the last century he was certainly among the best.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TEDX McGill 2016</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/project/tedx-mcgill-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/project/tedx-mcgill-2016/</guid>
      <description>Ideas on Stage, the global presentation specialists have been coaching TED speakers over the last six years with great results. This year we not only coached but also partnered with TedX McGill which occurred earlier this month.
The event theme was paradigm shift and took place at McGill University in Montreal. And as always the speakers were amazing and working on very different fields from gravitational waves to cyborg rights fondation or NGO activist.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
