<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Prise de parole en public on Ideas on Stage</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/prise-de-parole-en-public/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Prise de parole en public on Ideas on Stage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© Ideas on Stage</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/prise-de-parole-en-public/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The adult and the spoiled kid</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2019/09/17/2019-09-17-the-adult-and-the-spoilt-kid/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2019/09/17/2019-09-17-the-adult-and-the-spoilt-kid/</guid>
      <description>Some adults behave like bad, spoiled kids. They whine, they threaten, they become petty if they don’t get their way. They don’t hesitate to lie, or even worse, use the emotional card to play the victim, make you look bad and make you submit to their will.
These people are easy to recognize, but very difficult to deal with. Just think of the child rolling on the floor screaming. His parents will look bad whatever they do: scold him, do nothing, leave… they have zero good solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 7 deadly sins of slide design</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2019/04/23/2019-04-23-the-7-deadly-sins-of-slide-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2019/04/23/2019-04-23-the-7-deadly-sins-of-slide-design/</guid>
      <description>This is a quick list of seven common problems that we see with slides created by non specialists. However they are relatively easy to spot, and you don’t have to be a graphic designer to avoid them. Read on and your next slides will look much better!
 Too much content. The goal is not to cover every single inch with content. It’s not because you have some space left at the bottom of the slide that you should put something there.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>