<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Women on Ideas on Stage</title>
    <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/tags/women/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Women on Ideas on Stage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© Ideas on Stage 2015 - </copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.ideasonstage.com/tags/women/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Women on Stage Workshop Returns Dec 7</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/10/30/2017-10-30-women-on-stage-workshop-december-7-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/10/30/2017-10-30-women-on-stage-workshop-december-7-2017/</guid>
      <description>This December 7th in an elegant boardroom along the Champs-Elysée something powerful will take place: the beloved Women on Stage workshop will return by popular demand led by Marion Chapsal, Chief Learning Officer and Speaking Coach. Spaces are limited to allow space for each voice and leader to present and receive personalized feedback.
Marion Chapsal
For over 20 years, Marion&amp;rsquo;s work has helped leaders to strengthen their executive presence, enhance their presentation and communication skills, and promote gender-balanced leadership in everything she does.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taking Female Leadership by the Reins</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/09/04/2017-09-04-taking-female-leadership-by-the-reins/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/09/04/2017-09-04-taking-female-leadership-by-the-reins/</guid>
      <description>This September, something special will take place at Wisteria Acres in British Columbia, and it’s not just time with the horses. From Friday September 29th through Sunday evening on the 1st of October, Marion Chapsal and her co-facilitator Evelyn McKelvie will guide eight willing and ready women on a journey to find &amp;ndash; or fine-tune &amp;ndash; their public voice and take the stage alongside, you guessed it, horses. They call this workshop and retreat &amp;ldquo;The Heroine&amp;rsquo;s Journey&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can Women Pitch As Well As Men?</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/09/01/2017-09-01-can-women-pitch-as-well-as-men/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2017/09/01/2017-09-01-can-women-pitch-as-well-as-men/</guid>
      <description>It’s a simple fact that most successful startups are run by men. Why? Firstly, there are more men than women who decide - or dare - to start companies. Secondly, men are more successful at raising funds than women, and even those women who do raise funds end up raising less, on average, than their male counterparts. Having spent two years playing in the Silicon Valley arena myself, I’ve seen this truth first hand both in California and now in France.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
