<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Debate on </title>
    <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/tags/debate/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Debate on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© Ideas on Stage</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.ideasonstage.com/tags/debate/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Elon Musk running out of credibility?</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/04/30/2019-04-30-is-elon-musk-running-out-of-credibility/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/04/30/2019-04-30-is-elon-musk-running-out-of-credibility/</guid>
      <description>Gizmodo wrote this rather funny piece about Elon Musk’s latest rash of announcements, such as fully autonomous cars and a million robotaxis by 2020. Now, Gizmodo is not exactly known as a staple of great journalism, but sometimes they have a knack to hit the nail on the head. In this case, the fact that for several years Elon Musk repeatedly promised—and failed to deliver—full autonomous driving. Honestly, s eeing how hard it is to achieve full autonomy, and how many problems are left with Tesla’s current autopilot system, it is hard to believe these new promises will actually materialize.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 7 deadly sins of slide design</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/04/23/2019-04-23-the-7-deadly-sins-of-slide-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/04/23/2019-04-23-the-7-deadly-sins-of-slide-design/</guid>
      <description>This is a quick list of seven common problems that we see with slides created by non specialists. However they are relatively easy to spot, and you don’t have to be a graphic designer to avoid them. Read on and your next slides will look much better!
 Too much content. The goal is not to cover every single inch with content. It’s not because you have some space left at the bottom of the slide that you should put something there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Listen like a butterfly, talk like a bee</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/01/22/2019-01-22-listen-like-a-butterfly-talk-like-a-bee/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/01/22/2019-01-22-listen-like-a-butterfly-talk-like-a-bee/</guid>
      <description>I know, paraphrasing the motto of the great Muhammad Ali, “Float like a butterfly, sting like a bee”, doesn’t seem to make much sense. Yet my point is that in a debate it is extremely important to listen and move with a maximum of agility, and talk with a maximum of punch.
Take the example of the Gilets jaunes controversy in France. The government was completely taken by surprise by the popularity of the movement.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>