<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Public Speaking on Presentation Creation | Public Speaking Coaching and Training | Ideas on Stage</title>
    <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/tags/public-speaking/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Public Speaking on Presentation Creation | Public Speaking Coaching and Training | Ideas on Stage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© Ideas on Stage</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.ideasonstage.com/tags/public-speaking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The triple stakes of great presentations</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/03/05/2019-03-05-triple-stakes-of-great-presentations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/03/05/2019-03-05-triple-stakes-of-great-presentations/</guid>
      <description>The best presentations have three stakes, three reasons &amp;ldquo;why&amp;rdquo; they are important:
 The first stake is about you: why is the topic important for you? This is the reason you, and not somebody else, is on stage to deliver the presentation. The second stake is about your audience: why is it important for them? This is the reason why your audience is there to listen to you instead of doing something else.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 warning signs someone is not ready to speak at your TEDx event</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/02/26/2019-02-26-5-warning-signs-someone-is-not-ready-for-ted/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/02/26/2019-02-26-5-warning-signs-someone-is-not-ready-for-ted/</guid>
      <description>“Don’t worry, I’m experienced, I speak at conferences all the time!” How many times have we heard that sentence from speakers who never did a TEDx style talk, yet think that, because of experience, they can just wing it? For us, it’s not reassuring. Quite the opposite, it’s a clear warning sign that the speaker doesn’t really know what is expected of him. Here are five warning signs that give you clues that your speaker may not be ready to give a TEDx style talk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don’t do an elevator pitch. Start a conversation.</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/02/19/2019-02-19-dont-do-an-elevator-pitch-start-a-conversation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/02/19/2019-02-19-dont-do-an-elevator-pitch-start-a-conversation/</guid>
      <description>If you’re a Startup founder, you’ve heard this all before. “Your elevator pitch should be able to convince anyone in 30 seconds in an elevator”. Hold on hold on hold on! Let’s pause for a few seconds. Imagine that the roles are reversed. You’re in the elevator, lost in your thoughts, minding your own business. There is one other person in it, who you don’t know, and that person is looking intensely at you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to starve the presentation vultures (part 2)</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/02/12/2019-02-12-how-to-starve-the-presentation-vultures-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/02/12/2019-02-12-how-to-starve-the-presentation-vultures-2/</guid>
      <description>Last week we saw how presentation vultures can destroy your confidence and ability to present in front of an audience. We saw that the best way to fend them off is to strengthen your vital space anchor. But how can you do that?
If your presentation has an objective, a clear message, it is much easier to use it as an anchor. Let’s imagine for example that the key message is that your presentation is about a new software service that offers necessary services to protect your IT systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to starve the presentation vultures (part 1)</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/02/05/2019-02-05-how-to-starve-the-presentation-vultures-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/02/05/2019-02-05-how-to-starve-the-presentation-vultures-1/</guid>
      <description>Maybe you feel that your last presentation was a complete failure. You didn’t manage to shake off your nerves. You became confused. The client or your boss criticized you. Maybe you’ve been caught in a downward spiral for some time, each criticism making you lose confidence, and making the next presentation worse. I have good news for you: no matter what your situation is, this vicious circle can be broken, and you gain the necessary confidence to enjoy presenting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to steal the show</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/01/29/2019-01-29-how-to-steal-the-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/01/29/2019-01-29-how-to-steal-the-show/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks ago, Ideas on Stage had the privilege of organizing a sales presentation training for Krauthammer at Dolce La Hulpe, close to Brussels in Belgium. For us, delivering a training for dozens of senior people at Krauthammer, one of the world’s most respected sales and management training companies, felt like designing something for Jonathan Ive, Apple’s legendary designer: a bit intimidating but incredibly exciting.
The training met with great success, and it was fantastic to work with such talented people, but what I will remember most are two presentations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Listen like a butterfly, talk like a bee</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/01/22/2019-01-22-listen-like-a-butterfly-talk-like-a-bee/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/01/22/2019-01-22-listen-like-a-butterfly-talk-like-a-bee/</guid>
      <description>I know, paraphrasing the motto of the great Muhammad Ali, “Float like a butterfly, sting like a bee”, doesn’t seem to make much sense. Yet my point is that in a debate it is extremely important to listen and move with a maximum of agility, and talk with a maximum of punch.
Take the example of the Gilets jaunes controversy in France. The government was completely taken by surprise by the popularity of the movement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I presented at CES and all I got was a bunch of ungrateful tweets</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/01/15/2019-01-14-i-presented-at-ces-and-all-i-got-was-a-bunch-of-ungrateful-tweets/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2019/01/15/2019-01-14-i-presented-at-ces-and-all-i-got-was-a-bunch-of-ungrateful-tweets/</guid>
      <description>My colleague Ricardo pointed me to a tweet from Rene Ritchie, who was attending the conferences at CES.
Dear almost everyone on stage at CES: Pay ungodly amounts of money — anything you have to — to get WWDC speaker training ASAP.
Or go to Juilliard or the Royal Shakespeare Company for a month. Whatever works for you.
&amp;mdash; Rene Ritchie (@reneritchie) January 8, 2019 
This tweet says:
&amp;ldquo;Dear almost everyone on stage at CES: Pay ungodly amounts of money — anything you have to — to get WWDC speaker training ASAP.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>