<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Confident Presenter on Ideas on Stage</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/confident-presenter/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Confident Presenter on Ideas on Stage</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© Ideas on Stage 2010 - </copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/confident-presenter/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A Better Way To Think About Slide Design </title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2022/12/06/2022-12-06-a_better_way_to_think_about_slide_design/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2022/12/06/2022-12-06-a_better_way_to_think_about_slide_design/</guid>
      <description>The best things in life are often the simplest. Some of the best meals I‘ve ever eaten have been simple一just high quality ingredients presented in an uncomplicated way.&#xA;However, it can take a chef many years of training and experience to learn that lesson. The same is true in lots of other areas of life, not least art.&#xA;Look at Pablo Picasso’s famous set of drawing called The Bull from 1945.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Public Speaking Is The Most Important Skill You Need Right Now </title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2022/11/29/2022-11-29-why_public_speaking_is_the_most_important_skill_you_need_right_now/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2022/11/29/2022-11-29-why_public_speaking_is_the_most_important_skill_you_need_right_now/</guid>
      <description>The most likely reason for any setbacks and disappointments in your business, role or career is a communication deficiency—or lack of communication skills.&#xA;If you can’t convey your ideas to others then you won’t be able to reach your true potential.&#xA;The number one factor holding people back in their lives, especially in business, is poor communication skills.&#xA;If your business isn&amp;rsquo;t growing, there’s a communication deficiency.&#xA;If you&amp;rsquo;re finding it hard to lead your team, there’s a communication deficiency.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don’t Let ‘Authenticity’ Hold You Back</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2022/11/22/2022-11-22-don_t_let_authenticity_hold_you_back/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2022/11/22/2022-11-22-don_t_let_authenticity_hold_you_back/</guid>
      <description>When I start working with clients to help them improve their presentations they often push back and resist change.&#xA;I encourage business leaders to use a mix of logic and emotion, tell stories, include audience interactions and use eye contact and gestures.&#xA;A common concern is that the changes I suggest feel ‘fake’ and ‘inauthentic’. People say things like, ‘this is not me’ and ‘I don’t want to act like someone I’m not’.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Bring Boring Case Studies Alive – In 4 Easy Steps</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2022/11/15/2022-11-15-how_to_bring_boring_case_studies_alive_in_4_easy_steps/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2022/11/15/2022-11-15-how_to_bring_boring_case_studies_alive_in_4_easy_steps/</guid>
      <description>One of the worst things you can do when sharing examples, stories or case studies in a business presentation is to make them about yourself一instead of the client or the audience.&#xA;I’ve seen it so many times. I hear phrases like:&#xA;We’ve been the industry leader since 2010&#xA;We have 123 offices in 36 different countries&#xA;We have 7,500 clients across 80 industries We’re a pioneering company in our field</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Make Your Presentations More Interactive </title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2022/11/08/2022-11-08-how_to_make_your_presentations_more_interactive/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2022/11/08/2022-11-08-how_to_make_your_presentations_more_interactive/</guid>
      <description>There’s nothing more boring than a one-way lecture which makes an audience feel like they’re being talked at.&#xA;Unfortunately, too many business leaders deliver presentations which are more like one-sided lectures. They believe their job is to speak for 30 minutes while others listen.&#xA;These kinds of presentations, which don’t consider the needs of the audience, are tedious and unsuccessful.&#xA;How do we do things differently? In this article I’ll explore how to bring the audience into your presentations and make them feel involved.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 Ways To Communicate Data More Effectively</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2022/11/01/2022-11-01-3_ways_to_communicate_data_more_effectively/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2022/11/01/2022-11-01-3_ways_to_communicate_data_more_effectively/</guid>
      <description>Data and numbers can be important to a business presentation一but they can be bone dry unless you bring them to life in interesting ways.&#xA;I often see business leaders struggle to communicate data effectively. When I ask them if they think they’re doing it well they usually say yes. But that’s rarely the case.&#xA;Too many presenters assume that their data is intrinsically meaningful.&#xA;“Here’s the data: take it, use it, understand it, remember it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Persuasive Power of Analogies in Communication</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2022/10/18/2022-10-18-the_persuasive_power_of_analogies_in_communication/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2022/10/18/2022-10-18-the_persuasive_power_of_analogies_in_communication/</guid>
      <description>One of the hardest lessons to learn in communication is the art of keeping things simple.&#xA;The more we know about something, the easier it is to fall into the trap of making our ideas too complex and too technical.&#xA;It’s something I see business leaders doing all the time before they learn to improve their presentations. They wrongly assume that the audience will understand something just because they do.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Ways To Lead Your Audience To The Next Step</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2022/10/11/2022-10-12-7_ways_to_lead_your_audience_to_the_next_step/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2022/10/11/2022-10-12-7_ways_to_lead_your_audience_to_the_next_step/</guid>
      <description>If there’s a common purpose to most business presentations it’s to persuade the audience to act upon your ideas in some way. The best way to persuade the audience to do what you want them to do is with a clear call to action.&#xA;If the call to action isn’t clear enough, the audience will fail to act. Your presentation will have been in vain.&#xA;For example, imagine you were giving a webinar or an introductory workshop on your area of expertise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Memorable Ways to Open a Presentation (With Examples)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2022/10/04/2022-10-04-7_memorable_ways_to_open_a_presentation_with_examples/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2022/10/04/2022-10-04-7_memorable_ways_to_open_a_presentation_with_examples/</guid>
      <description>The first words of a presentation are the most important. Your opening needs to grab the audience’s attention and hold it.&#xA;The philosopher Plato said: “The beginning is the most important part of the work.”&#xA;Sadly, most business leaders don’t think carefully enough about the way they open their presentations. Instead, they focus on the main body of their presentation and leave the opening to chance.&#xA;Or they make the common mistake of opening with a boring agenda slide or by introducing themselves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 Steps To Creating A Clear Presentation Storyline</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2022/09/27/2022-09-27-6_steps_to_creating_a_clear_presentation_storyline/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2022/09/27/2022-09-27-6_steps_to_creating_a_clear_presentation_storyline/</guid>
      <description>The greatest films, TV shows and novels are the ones with the best storylines. The same is true for presentations. A strong narrative can help you bring your presentation alive and make it memorable and successful. However, most business owners, leaders and professionals don’t pay enough attention to the way they structure their presentations. They fail to develop a clear storyline.&#xA;I’ve come across many presenters who simply improvise their presentation around some slides.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Take Control Of Your Fear of Public Speaking (Without Any “Woo Woo” Remedies) </title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2022/09/20/2022-09-15-how_to_take_control_of_your_fear_of_public_speaking_without_any_woo_woo_remedies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2022/09/20/2022-09-15-how_to_take_control_of_your_fear_of_public_speaking_without_any_woo_woo_remedies/</guid>
      <description>It’s almost pointless asking if you feel nervous before a presentation. It would be strange if you didn’t. The vast majority of people are afraid of public speaking. It’s perfectly normal to have a fear of public speaking, also known by its technical name of glossophobia.&#xA;Research shows that more than 75 percent of the population has some level of public speaking anxiety. So you’re in good company.&#xA;I’m a presentation coach and I feel nervous all the time before a presentation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Rehearsing Leads to More Confidence</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2022/09/13/2022-09-14-why_rehearsing_leads_to_more_confidence/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2022/09/13/2022-09-14-why_rehearsing_leads_to_more_confidence/</guid>
      <description>When you watch the best athletes their movement seems completely natural and effortless. The reason they look so at ease is because of the years of dedicated practice they’ve put in. No one is born with the ability to excel—it requires work.&#xA;The same is true for business presentations. It’s impossible to deliver a great speech without rehearsing it thoroughly. You can spot a presenter who hasn’t rehearsed adequately. The giveaways are that they might:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do You Suffer From The Curse Of Knowledge? </title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2022/09/06/2022-09-07-do_you_suffer_from_the_curse_of_knowledge/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2022/09/06/2022-09-07-do_you_suffer_from_the_curse_of_knowledge/</guid>
      <description>There is a famous saying that ‘a little knowledge is a dangerous thing’. It warns against those who know something about a subject but not quite enough.&#xA;We should apply the same caution to those business owners and leaders who pitch their presentations above the audience’s heads. They forget how much they know about a subject and aim too high.&#xA;In Made to Stick by Chip Heath and Dan Heath, one of the best books I’ve ever read, they introduce the concept of the curse of knowledge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your Idea Is Worthless Unless You Can Communicate It</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2022/08/30/2022-08-30-your_idea_is_worthless_unless_you_can_communicate_it/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2022/08/30/2022-08-30-your_idea_is_worthless_unless_you_can_communicate_it/</guid>
      <description>Right now there&amp;rsquo;s someone in the world having a great idea; their own lightbulb moment which could change the world.&#xA;Many entrepreneurs, business owners and leaders assume that their ideas are the most important thing. They believe that their idea, whether that be a product, service, project or business, is all that matters. They focus on creating and working on their concepts without giving sufficient thought to articulating them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Make Your Message Relevant To Your Audience</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2022/08/23/2022-08-16-how_to_make_your_message_relevant_to_your_audience/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2022/08/23/2022-08-16-how_to_make_your_message_relevant_to_your_audience/</guid>
      <description>When Paul McCartney headlined Glastonbury in 2022 he played a long set which included lots of newer material, plus songs from his solo and Wings albums. Many people loved it. But he was criticised for not giving the audience what they wanted — which was the hits.&#xA;No doubt Sir Paul had his reasons. He doesn’t just want to play Beatles songs all evening. But even someone of his experience and talent can get it wrong sometimes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Power of Storytelling in Presentations</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2022/08/16/2022-07-26-the_power_of_storytelling_in_presentations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2022/08/16/2022-07-26-the_power_of_storytelling_in_presentations/</guid>
      <description>If you truly want to connect with an audience one of the most powerful strategies is to share stories and real life experiences. Facts and figures are hard to remember but we love hearing anecdotes.&#xA;Many business owners, leaders and professionals make the mistake of only sharing information in their presentations. They include abstract concepts, facts and figures. As a result, their presentations remain dry, factual and boring. You don’t want to be a boring presenter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Present A Clear Message To Any Audience: The Rule of Three</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2022/08/09/2022-08-09-how-to-present-a-clear-message-to-any-audience-the-rule-of-three/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2022/08/09/2022-08-09-how-to-present-a-clear-message-to-any-audience-the-rule-of-three/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever had this experience: it becomes increasingly obvious to you during a presentation that the structure isn’t clear enough? You’re losing the audience (which might be clients, colleagues, the board, partners or investors).&#xA;If so, you are not alone. Most business leaders and professionals struggle with this.&#xA;Fortunately, there is one simple yet powerful communication technique that will help you: the Rule of Three.&#xA;The Rule of Three Three is the most powerful number in communication.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three Ways To Simplify Your Presentations</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2022/08/02/2022-08-02-three-ways-to-simplify-your-presentations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2022/08/02/2022-08-02-three-ways-to-simplify-your-presentations/</guid>
      <description>Many business owners, leaders and professionals give presentations that are too complex. The consequence is that the audience fails to grasp the message and will not take the desired action.&#xA;I believe that the more you say, the less your audience will remember. So you need to keep your presentations short, simple and to the point.&#xA;Keeping it simple is one of the five key factors behind any powerful presentation. If you are interested in learning more about the others, I have written about them here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Five Key Principles For Powerful Presentations</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2022/07/26/2022-07-26-the-five-key-principles-for-powerful-presentations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2022/07/26/2022-07-26-the-five-key-principles-for-powerful-presentations/</guid>
      <description>Most business leaders fail to follow set principles for creating and delivering their presentations. In not doing so they are making a fundamental mistake.&#xA;Some think it’s primarily about creating slides on PowerPoint. They think if they get a decent deck together then they are good to go.&#xA;If you are one of those people who spend most of your preparation time working on PowerPoint slides (or any other presentation tool), you’ve missed the point.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Being Confident At Public Speaking: The Three Things You Need To Know</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2022/07/19/2022-07-19-being-confident-at-public-speaking-the-three-things-you-need-to-know/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2022/07/19/2022-07-19-being-confident-at-public-speaking-the-three-things-you-need-to-know/</guid>
      <description>Many business leaders and professionals wrongly believe that being confident at public speaking comes naturally to some people. Perhaps they are born with confidence?&#xA;Or they think that to become more confident at presenting they simply need to improve their delivery skills and work on things like eye contact, body language and vocal delivery. These things are all important but there is so much more to it.&#xA;As a result, most untrained business leaders don’t feel confident presenting at all.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hidden Cost Of Bad Presentations — How To Avoid Losing Business</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2022/06/28/2022-06-28-the-hidden-cost-of-bad-presentations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2022/06/28/2022-06-28-the-hidden-cost-of-bad-presentations/</guid>
      <description>A presentation is your opportunity to make a great first impression. It’s a bit like a first date — only the stakes are financial rather than romantic.&#xA;However, too many business leaders fail to consider the cost of delivering a bad presentation.&#xA;Many companies fall into the trap of making an invisible first impression. When presenting an idea for the first time — be it a product, a service or a project — the impression they make is invisible.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Public Speaking: A Proven Process to Build Your Confidence</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2022/06/09/2022-06-09-public-speaking-a-proven-process-to-build-your-confidence/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2022/06/09/2022-06-09-public-speaking-a-proven-process-to-build-your-confidence/</guid>
      <description>It’s easier than you think to improve your confidence when presenting or public speaking. The more prepared and structured your approach, the more confident you will be.&#xA;Most business leaders don’t follow any sort of organised process when preparing a presentation. Keen to get started, they launch into things and hope for the best. We’ve all seen the person who decides to wing it or who turns up with chaotic notes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why complex presentations don&#39;t work (and what to do instead)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2022/05/31/2022-05-31-why-complex-presentations-don-t-work-and-what-to-do-instead/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2022/05/31/2022-05-31-why-complex-presentations-don-t-work-and-what-to-do-instead/</guid>
      <description>The most successful messages are the simplest. The best writing gets to the point. The greatest speeches are concise and direct.&#xA;However, too many business leaders fall into the trap of giving presentations which are overly complex and technical. They navigate their audience down side roads and off on tangents. Their visuals mirror this and are often confusing and convoluted.&#xA;Why does this happen? It is all done for the right reasons.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
