<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Team-members on Ideas on Stage | Deliver amazing presentations</title>
    <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team-member/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Team-members on Ideas on Stage | Deliver amazing presentations</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© Ideas on Stage</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.ideasonstage.com/team-member/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Team</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/pierre-morsa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/pierre-morsa/</guid>
      <description>The best time to quit your consulting job and create a startup with zero Customers is when you are 40, at the top, with two young kids and a loan to reimburse for a Parisian apartment. Just close your eyes. Take a deep breath. Count to 10. And jump into the unknown.
Several years later, here I am, as the co-founding Partner and Creative Director of Ideas on Stage and enjoying every moment of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/phil-waknell/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/phil-waknell/</guid>
      <description>Phil Waknell is one of Europe’s leading experts in the new art of presenting, and speaks regularly at major corporations and conferences about better business communication. He teaches business presenting at HEC Paris Executive Education, Europe’s leading executive business school, and is the author of The Business Presentation Revolution.
Phil has helped hundreds of entrepreneurs and TED(x) speakers to prepare and deliver high-impact presentations, as well as coaching leaders at many of Europe’s top companies, delivering seminars and workshops around the world, and acting as Master of Ceremonies for major international events.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/michael-rickwood/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/michael-rickwood/</guid>
      <description>Initially a classically trained actor with 12 years of experience on stage and screen, Michael swapped his passion for acting in favour of business communication and design. Before joining Ideas on Stage, in parallel to his acting career, Michael spent many years creating and delivering original presentation training courses for some of France’s biggest companies.
Today, apart from training and coaching executives from all sectors and industries and helping them develop content, Michael also coaches speakers at hugely successful TEDx and WikiStage conferences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/marion-chapsal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/marion-chapsal/</guid>
      <description>Marion Chapsal coaches leaders in executive presence, presentation skills and gender-balanced leadership.
Her clients know her as fun, caring and remarkably creative. One may even say she&amp;rsquo;s the Mary Poppins of executive coaching; turning work into play while delivering high-quality results.
For Women on Stage, she has created the Heroines’ Journey. Partnered with Equine coach Evelyn McKelvie in Vancouver, the two have designed unique leadership retreats for women executives to find a voice of their own, craft their #TEDlike talks and own their presence on stage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/joe-ross/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/joe-ross/</guid>
      <description>Joe is a highly experienced writer, communicator, and campaign strategy designer; he has taught business writing and communication at Ecole Polytechnique as well in several business schools. Having a wealth of experience in the public sector and business, he has served in the capacity of Chief of Policy and Senior Advisor to prominent institutions, foundations, and governments including The Tallberg Foundation in Stockholm; PlaNet Finance in Paris; and the City of San Diego, California.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/vanessa-querville/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/vanessa-querville/</guid>
      <description>After graduating in History from Paris Sorbonne and Trinity College in Dublin, Vanessa Querville worked as a publisher and book designer before joining the startup world and running the Microsoft Accelerator in Paris. There, she was in charge of recruitment, operations, helping startups with their pitches, and acting as a bridge between startups and Microsoft clients. She joined Ideas on Stage in 2015 as Chief Pitch Officer, helping fast-growing companies with killer pitches, and helping established companies to pitch just as well as tech startups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/rose-bloomfield/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/rose-bloomfield/</guid>
      <description>Born in Los Angeles, California, Rose Bloomfield grew up performing on stage and in front of the camera. Her first big role was interviewing film creatives as a Disney host, talent like Jerry Bruckheimer, Anne Hathaway and Nicolas Cage, which paved the unexpected road to her next large project as a principle on the socio-cultural F.X. documentary series, “Black. White.”
Following the project and before earning a degree in Cultural Anthropology at the University of California, Santa Cruz, Rose had been a hired speaker at over a dozen colleges across the United States on the topic of empathy and intercultural communication.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/ricardo-bonis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/ricardo-bonis/</guid>
      <description>Ricardo is the founder and manager of Ideas on Stage Spain, located in Barcelona. Combining more than 15 years of experience in executive roles in the telco industry and his experience teaching at the Escuela Politécnica de Ingeniería of the University of Oviedo, Ricardo knows first hand the challenging business environment and the importance of great presentation skills to thrive in it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/laura-diaz-de-entresotos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/laura-diaz-de-entresotos/</guid>
      <description>Laura is an experienced coach and communicator. Before joining Ideas on Stage, she worked as psychology therapist for more than 13 years. She earned a PhD in Psychology from University of Oviedo and EuroPsy certification. Her experience on therapy and coaching, as well as her ability to connect, are her foundations to help other people feel comfortable, gain confidence and perform to their best on stage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/edoardo-sala/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/edoardo-sala/</guid>
      <description>After his diploma in classical studies Edoardo followed his passion for the arts and the theatre.
He graduated at the Drama Centre London, one of the most prestigious Academies of Dramatic Art in Great Britain and worked for many years as a professional actor.
He then brought his knowledge of verbal, non-verbal communication and public speaking skills to the corporate world.
After an extensive experience as a Sales and Marketing Manager in the International luxury market he completed the Executive MBA at the MIP school of management of the Politecnico of Milan, where he focused on General and Innovation Management, Luxury Marketing, Digital and Social Media Marketing finding a balance between his artistical background and his managerial experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/dirk-haun/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/dirk-haun/</guid>
      <description>Coming from a background in software development and technology, Dirk has made it his mission to help people express and present their ideas. He is the co-organizer and speaker liaison at TEDxStuttgart and the author of “Presenting for Geeks”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/patricia-lane/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/patricia-lane/</guid>
      <description>Patricia Lane, a dual French &amp;amp; American national, holds advanced degrees in Political Science targeting the US-Europe-Asia triangle.
An intercultural communications specialist, she leads the Franco-American Quill, which provides creative copywriting, executive training, and cross-cultural strategic consulting. She has worked for clients such as Airbus, Groupe Bel, Aventis, McDonald’s Europe, Dalkia and Linkfluence, has taught at INALCO, and is a member of the SFT, IABC and Communication et Entreprise. Passionate about photography, she is rarely seen without her Nikon slung over her shoulder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/roberto-lalli/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/roberto-lalli/</guid>
      <description>Specialising in value-based leadership and marketing through storytelling, and speaking fluent German, Italian and English, Roberto coaches and trains executives around Europe to broaden their charismatic leadership skills and their storytelling expertise.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>