<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Event on Ideas on Stage</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/event/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Event on Ideas on Stage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© Ideas on Stage</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/event/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Why should I hire an external event coordinator? An experienced event manager&#39;s point of view</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2020/02/25/2020-02-25-why-should-i-hire-an-external-event-coordinator-an-experienced-event-manager-s-point-of-view/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2020/02/25/2020-02-25-why-should-i-hire-an-external-event-coordinator-an-experienced-event-manager-s-point-of-view/</guid>
      <description>A lot of people think that organizing an event is within everyone’s reach. But is it really true? If you want to organize one for your company, a lot is at stake, including brand reputation as well as the satisfaction of your customers or guests. If you don’t want to take any chances and make a positive impression, it’s important to set up a team dedicated to your project.
If you are the organizer in the hot seat, you are likely asking yourself many questions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TEDx Saclay – Worth all the Applause</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2017/12/01/2017-12-01-tedxsaclay/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2017/12/01/2017-12-01-tedxsaclay/</guid>
      <description>For the third year running, Ideas on Stage was very happy to partner with the TEDx Saclay conference, which took place this November 30, 2017 in the brand-new CentraleSupélec amphitheater at the Plateau de Saclay on the powerful theme of “Serving the Living”.
TEDx Saclay Keeping standards typically high, this year’s event boasted a rich program of speakers including a few notably prestigious guests such as Cédric Villani &amp;ndash; renowned mathematician and member of the French National Assembly &amp;ndash; as well as artists, scientists, students, entrepreneurs and even a Guinness World Record gamer (Kayane).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taking Female Leadership by the Reins</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2017/09/04/2017-09-04-taking-female-leadership-by-the-reins/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2017/09/04/2017-09-04-taking-female-leadership-by-the-reins/</guid>
      <description>This September, something special will take place at Wisteria Acres in British Columbia, and it’s not just time with the horses. From Friday September 29th through Sunday evening on the 1st of October, Marion Chapsal and her co-facilitator Evelyn McKelvie will guide eight willing and ready women on a journey to find &amp;ndash; or fine-tune &amp;ndash; their public voice and take the stage alongside, you guessed it, horses. They call this workshop and retreat &amp;ldquo;The Heroine&amp;rsquo;s Journey&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can Women Pitch As Well As Men?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2017/09/01/2017-09-01-can-women-pitch-as-well-as-men/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2017/09/01/2017-09-01-can-women-pitch-as-well-as-men/</guid>
      <description>It’s a simple fact that most successful startups are run by men. Why? Firstly, there are more men than women who decide - or dare - to start companies. Secondly, men are more successful at raising funds than women, and even those women who do raise funds end up raising less, on average, than their male counterparts. Having spent two years playing in the Silicon Valley arena myself, I’ve seen this truth first hand both in California and now in France.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>