<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Team on Ideas on Stage</title>
    <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Team on Ideas on Stage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© Ideas on Stage 2015 - </copyright><atom:link href="https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/pierre-morsa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/pierre-morsa/</guid>
      <description>Pierre Morsa is the Co-founder of Ideas on Stage. He created the Ideas on Stage brand and concept in 2009. He works every day to create presentations with something extra special. He always looks for new ways to surprise and amaze your audience.
Pierre did projects for Yann Arthus-Bertrand, the UNESCO, the Positive Economy Forum, Havas, McCann, SNCF, Fresenius, Boston Scientific, EDF, RTE, Société Générale, Murex, l’Agence Française de Développement, Google, Microsoft, Vade Secure, Stormshield, several large luxury groups and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/phil-waknell/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/phil-waknell/</guid>
      <description>Phil Waknell is one of Europe’s leading experts in the new art of presenting, and speaks regularly at major corporations and conferences about better business communication. He teaches business presenting at HEC Paris Executive Education, Europe’s leading executive business school, and is the author of The Business Presentation Revolution.
Phil has helped hundreds of entrepreneurs and TED(x) speakers to prepare and deliver high-impact presentations, as well as coaching leaders at many of Europe’s top companies, delivering seminars and workshops around the world, and acting as Master of Ceremonies for major international events.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/michael-rickwood/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/michael-rickwood/</guid>
      <description>Initially a classically trained actor with 12 years of experience on stage and screen, Michael swapped his passion for acting in favour of business communication and design in 2011.
Today, apart from consulting, training and coaching executives from all sectors and industries all over the world including Engie South East Asia in Singapore, French Search Engine Qwant in Paris and the World Bank in Washington DC, Michael also coaches speakers at hugely successful TEDx and WikiStage conferences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/ricardo-bonis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/ricardo-bonis/</guid>
      <description>Ricardo is the founder and manager of Ideas on Stage Spain, located in Barcelona. Combining more than 15 years of experience in executive roles in the telco industry and his experience teaching at the Escuela Politécnica de Ingeniería of the University of Oviedo, Ricardo knows first hand the challenging business environment and the importance of great presentation skills to thrive in it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/laura-diaz-de-entresotos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/laura-diaz-de-entresotos/</guid>
      <description>Laura is an experienced coach and communicator. Before joining Ideas on Stage, she worked as psychology therapist for more than 13 years. She earned a PhD in Psychology from University of Oviedo and EuroPsy certification. Her experience on therapy and coaching, as well as her ability to connect, are her foundations to help other people feel comfortable, gain confidence and perform to their best on stage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/joe-ross/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/joe-ross/</guid>
      <description>Joe is a highly experienced writer, communicator, and campaign strategy designer; he has taught business writing and communication at Ecole Polytechnique as well in several business schools. Having a wealth of experience in the public sector and business, he has served in the capacity of Chief of Policy and Senior Advisor to prominent institutions, foundations, and governments including The Tallberg Foundation in Stockholm; PlaNet Finance in Paris; and the City of San Diego, California.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/vanessa-querville/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/vanessa-querville/</guid>
      <description>After graduating in History from Paris Sorbonne and Trinity College in Dublin, Vanessa Querville worked as a publisher and book designer before joining the startup world and running the Microsoft Accelerator in Paris. There, she was in charge of recruitment, operations, helping startups with their pitches, and acting as a bridge between startups and Microsoft clients. She joined Ideas on Stage in 2015 as Chief Pitch Officer, helping fast-growing companies with killer pitches, and helping established companies to pitch just as well as tech startups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/edoardo-sala/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/edoardo-sala/</guid>
      <description>After his diploma in classical studies Edoardo followed his passion for the arts and the theatre.
He graduated at the Drama Centre London, one of the most prestigious Academies of Dramatic Art in Great Britain and worked for many years as a professional actor.
He then brought his knowledge of verbal, non-verbal communication and public speaking skills to the corporate world.
After an extensive experience as a Sales and Marketing Manager in the International luxury market he completed the Executive MBA at the MIP school of management of the Politecnico of Milan, where he focused on General and Innovation Management, Luxury Marketing, Digital and Social Media Marketing finding a balance between his artistical background and his managerial experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/rose-bloomfield/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/rose-bloomfield/</guid>
      <description>Rose grew up in Los Angeles, California, where she became a natural Hollywood/Silicon Valley hybrid. After lead TV roles with Disney and FX, and with a degree in Cultural Anthropology from the University of California, Rose became a professional speaker on the topic of intercultural communication.
In 2014, she moved to San Francisco to join e-commerce startup Teespring as head of Culture, managing interior design, wellness, internal communication and an events calendar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/frederic-pascal-stein/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/frederic-pascal-stein/</guid>
      <description>Communication consultant, coach and writer, Frédéric-Pascal Stein specializes in verbal as well as non-verbal communication. As a dual French-American, he helps clients in both French and English.
Exposed from an early age to both artistic and scientific studies, Frédéric-Pascal’s initial training was directed toward engineering. He was later drawn to the theater as a professional actor and director, and to the teaching profession. He also has significant experience in mediation and group coaching.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/marine-benard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/marine-benard/</guid>
      <description>Marine is experienced in project management and the organization of events. She has many years of experience in organizing salons for professionals and for the general public, private events and TEDx conferences.
As Events Coordinator, Marine focuses her energy on producing fantastic events and conferences, making life easy for clients and ensuring smooth project management and coordination between client organizers, internal and external speakers, technical teams, and our team of coaches, designers and MCs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/andrea-pacini/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/andrea-pacini/</guid>
      <description>Andrea is our Presentation Director for the UK.
Since he joined Ideas on Stage, he has worked with many business leaders, including clients like General Assembly, Fiverr, ISTAO Business School, as well as TEDx speakers. Andrea is also the main voice of the Ideas on Stage Podcast.
He specialises in working with established business owners who want to grow their business and increase their influence through great presenting.
Andrea is on a mission to change the way people think about presenting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/ismael-salmeron/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/team/ismael-salmeron/</guid>
      <description>Ismael Salmerón has 20 years of experience in video editing and design. Before joining Ideas on Stage, he served customers such as Warner Bros., Dreamworks and Paramount Pictures as part of one of the largest video editing and postproduction companies in Spain. He has also worked for other well-known companies like El Corte Inglés and Canal Club.
Ismael’s design portfolio includes illustration work for Random House Mondadori; among his works are book covers for authors Ian Tregillis and Víctor del Árbol.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
