<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Events on Ideas on Stage</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/events/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Events on Ideas on Stage</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© Ideas on Stage 2010 - </copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/events/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How Personal Storytelling Can Transform Your Business, Boost Your Career and Drive Change</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2024/06/10/2024-06-10-how_personal_storytelling_can_transform_your_business_boost_your_career_and_drive_change_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2024/06/10/2024-06-10-how_personal_storytelling_can_transform_your_business_boost_your_career_and_drive_change_2/</guid>
      <description>In a recent web class we hosted, Mark Leruste, CEO of Storycast and a renowned storytelling expert, shared great insights on the power of personal storytelling. Here&amp;rsquo;s a summary of the key points from the session.&#xA;The Importance of Personal Storytelling&#xA;Mark emphasised the importance of personal storytelling in today&amp;rsquo;s world. With the constant noise and distractions in our digital age, stories have a unique ability to cut through the clutter and connect with people on a deep emotional level.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mastering the Art of Spontaneous Speaking </title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2024/04/10/2024-04-10-mastering_the_art_of_spontaneous_speaking/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2024/04/10/2024-04-10-mastering_the_art_of_spontaneous_speaking/</guid>
      <description>We recently hosted a special event with Matt Abrahams, a well-known Stanford lecturer and the author of ‘Think Faster, Talk Smarter,’ as our special guest. The focus was on spontaneous speaking, an essential skill for effective communication today. Over 180 people signed up for the event, getting a chance to ask Matt their questions directly.&#xA;Here&amp;rsquo;s a quick overview of the main topics we covered during our chat.&#xA;How did you get into spontaneous speaking?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Captivate Your Audience with Visual Storytelling</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2023/11/21/2023-11-21-captivate_your_audience_with_visual_storytelling/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2023/11/21/2023-11-21-captivate_your_audience_with_visual_storytelling/</guid>
      <description>In a world where we’re bombarded with information and sometimes overwhelming, effective communication becomes a precious skill. At our recent event with international best-selling author Dan Roam, participants had the chance to explore the secrets of mastering this skill through visual storytelling.&#xA;Blending art and science&#xA;Dan Roam explained the powerful combination of visual expression and scientific principles, showing how visual storytelling can revolutionise the way we convey our ideas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brain Rules for Effective Communication</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2023/06/13/2023-06-12-brain_rules_for_effective_communication/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2023/06/13/2023-06-12-brain_rules_for_effective_communication/</guid>
      <description>On June 6, 2023, we hosted a special event, Brain Rules for Effective Communication. The event featured the esteemed guest speaker, Dr. John Medina, renowned author of the New York Times bestseller Brain Rules. In this article, I highlight the key takeaways from Dr. Medina&amp;rsquo;s thought-provoking presentation.&#xA;Why it Matters&#xA;Attempting to be an effective communicator without understanding how our brain processes information is like shooting an arrow without a target.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zen and The Art of Presenting with Impact </title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2023/03/14/2023-03-14-zen_and_the_art_of_presenting_with_impact/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2023/03/14/2023-03-14-zen_and_the_art_of_presenting_with_impact/</guid>
      <description>On the 7th of March, more than 200 business leaders attended our virtual event, &amp;ldquo;Zen and the Art of Presenting with Impact&amp;rdquo;, featuring renowned speaker Garr Reynolds. Garr covered three key principles: Restraint Simplicity Naturalness Under the principle of Restraint in preparation, Garr emphasised the importance of planning presentations analogue and having the courage to remove unnecessary details in service of the audience. He also shared tips on creating a clear presentation structure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Communication Secrets that Power Amazon&#39;s Success</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2022/12/12/2022-12-12-communication_secrets_that_power_amazons_success/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2022/12/12/2022-12-12-communication_secrets_that_power_amazons_success/</guid>
      <description>Ideas don’t sell themselves. If you want to persuade others to act on your ideas, you need to be an effective communicator. We’ve recently hosted a special masterclass with the one and only Carmine Gallo as a guest speaker. Carmine Gallo is a communication coach for the world’s most admired brands. He’s a Harvard instructor, leadership advisor, and bestselling author whose books have been translated into more than 40 languages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leadership and Communication Tactics to Fuel Your Success</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2022/10/24/2022-10-19-leadership_and_communication_tactics_to_fuel_your_success/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2022/10/24/2022-10-19-leadership_and_communication_tactics_to_fuel_your_success/</guid>
      <description>Do others dismiss your ideas and proposals?&#xA;Do you struggle with creating and delivering simple, engaging, and persuasive presentations?&#xA;Have you heard about ‘storytelling’ but you’re not sure how to do it?&#xA;If so, this is the event you&amp;rsquo;ve been waiting for!&#xA;O﻿n 6th December 2022 I&amp;rsquo;m hosting a free, live web class in collaboration with the one and only Carmine Gallo, the bestselling author of Talk Like TED. You’ll learn strategies based on his new book, The Bezos Blueprint.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why should I hire an external event coordinator? An experienced event manager&#39;s point of view</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2020/02/25/2020-02-25-why-should-i-hire-an-external-event-coordinator-an-experienced-event-manager-s-point-of-view/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2020/02/25/2020-02-25-why-should-i-hire-an-external-event-coordinator-an-experienced-event-manager-s-point-of-view/</guid>
      <description>A lot of people think that organizing an event is within everyone’s reach. But is it really true? If you want to organize one for your company, a lot is at stake, including brand reputation as well as the satisfaction of your customers or guests. If you don’t want to take any chances and make a positive impression, it’s important to set up a team dedicated to your project.&#xA;If you are the organizer in the hot seat, you are likely asking yourself many questions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>12 Tips for an Amazing Event: Don’t Just Sit There, DO Something</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2019/09/24/2019-09-24-to-make-an-amazing-event-don-t-just-sit-there-do-something/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2019/09/24/2019-09-24-to-make-an-amazing-event-don-t-just-sit-there-do-something/</guid>
      <description>What is it about designing events that I love so much? Suddenly I think of cookie dough, the small crunchy granules of sugar blended with butter, the heavenly flavour of vanilla extract and the sublime melt of dark chocolate chips. Even before I bake the cookies, the main event in this case, the ingredients themselves have satisfied.&#xA;Designing events are similar because I love what goes into making them delicious–I mean, shine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Put your most nervous speakers early in the program</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2019/07/09/2019-07-09-put-your-most-nervous-speakers-early-in-the-program/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2019/07/09/2019-07-09-put-your-most-nervous-speakers-early-in-the-program/</guid>
      <description>One of the most stressful moments when speaking at an event is actually not during your presentation, but the hours before your presentation. To some speakers, the wait can be so stressful that they completely lose their presence. As mother nature didn&amp;rsquo;t give humans an appropriate instinctive response to face the stress of a presentation, they adopt one of the basic survival techniques for protection: they fight the public, they flee, or they &amp;ldquo;play dead&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A New Cure for Medical Conferences</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2019/05/16/2019-05-16-a-new-cure-for-medical-conferences/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2019/05/16/2019-05-16-a-new-cure-for-medical-conferences/</guid>
      <description>Most conferences are fairly boring. Even well-known tech conferences fail to engage their audiences all the time. But medical conferences can be among the worst. Check out this quick interview between Ideas on Stage, new partners with Doctors 2.0 &amp;amp; You, and Denise Silber to find out how to take medical (and other) events to the next level.&#xA;Our friend Ross Fisher, a paediatric surgeon based in the UK, has had enough of poor medical communication, and when he’s not operating, he spends time educating doctors about a better way to present.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Makes an Amazing, Culture-Shifting Event?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2019/05/15/2019-05-15-what-makes-an-amazing-culture-shifting-event/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2019/05/15/2019-05-15-what-makes-an-amazing-culture-shifting-event/</guid>
      <description>Case study of Mövenpick Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts’ 2018 General Managers conference in Regensdorf, Switzerland.&#xA;__&#xA;The Story It was a cool September morning in Paris when my colleague and I sat down in a stylish hotel dining room to meet a Mr. Olivier Chavy, President of Mövenpick Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts.&#xA;Before 8:00am we jumped right into business: Olivier’s vision and objectives for the spring 2018 general managers conference. “We want people to leave with the sensation ‘wow, I am really proud to work for this company’,” emphasized Chavy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our upcoming events in London</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2019/05/14/2019-05-10-london-calling/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2019/05/14/2019-05-10-london-calling/</guid>
      <description>A big part of the way many companies sell is to create a presentation that shows the complex benefits of the solution they are offering.&#xA;But even great businesses — which are very good at what they do — often lack the ability to clearly share their message to their target audience using presentations.&#xA;There are many reasons why people and companies want to improve their presentations but at the heart of it what they really want is to win more deals, get more customers and sell more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are you ready?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2018/10/08/2018-10-08-are-you-ready/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2018/10/08/2018-10-08-are-you-ready/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s already October and you know what that means&amp;hellip; Firming up plans for next year. Pitching projects. Assigning budgets. And ultimately getting creative about how to expire old, ineffective systems and implement a smarter and better approach. Look around and catch the shift. It&amp;rsquo;s not time for just another step forward. It&amp;rsquo;s time to leap.&#xA;At Ideas on Stage we coach, train and design for international clients and companies large and small, from CAC 40 enterprises to startups and incubators.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEDx Saclay – Worth all the Applause</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2017/12/01/2017-12-01-tedxsaclay/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2017/12/01/2017-12-01-tedxsaclay/</guid>
      <description>For the third year running, Ideas on Stage was very happy to partner with the TEDx Saclay conference, which took place this November 30, 2017 in the brand-new CentraleSupélec amphitheater at the Plateau de Saclay on the powerful theme of “Serving the Living”.&#xA;TEDx Saclay Keeping standards typically high, this year’s event boasted a rich program of speakers including a few notably prestigious guests such as Cédric Villani &amp;ndash; renowned mathematician and member of the French National Assembly &amp;ndash; as well as artists, scientists, students, entrepreneurs and even a Guinness World Record gamer (Kayane).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taking Female Leadership by the Reins</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2017/09/04/2017-09-04-taking-female-leadership-by-the-reins/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2017/09/04/2017-09-04-taking-female-leadership-by-the-reins/</guid>
      <description>This September, something special will take place at Wisteria Acres in British Columbia, and it’s not just time with the horses. From Friday September 29th through Sunday evening on the 1st of October, Marion Chapsal and her co-facilitator Evelyn McKelvie will guide eight willing and ready women on a journey to find &amp;ndash; or fine-tune &amp;ndash; their public voice and take the stage alongside, you guessed it, horses. They call this workshop and retreat &amp;ldquo;The Heroine&amp;rsquo;s Journey&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Women Pitch As Well As Men?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2017/09/01/2017-09-01-can-women-pitch-as-well-as-men/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2017/09/01/2017-09-01-can-women-pitch-as-well-as-men/</guid>
      <description>It’s a simple fact that most successful startups are run by men. Why? Firstly, there are more men than women who decide - or dare - to start companies. Secondly, men are more successful at raising funds than women, and even those women who do raise funds end up raising less, on average, than their male counterparts. Having spent two years playing in the Silicon Valley arena myself, I’ve seen this truth first hand both in California and now in France.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lost in Transition?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2017/08/31/2017-08-31-lost-in-transition/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2017/08/31/2017-08-31-lost-in-transition/</guid>
      <description>This summer Ideas on Stage partnered up with the fine people at Set’Event to help a handful of such thoughtful and committed citizens to give impactful keynote presentations at the 15th annual ACIDD event, which took place August 28-29 in Bordeaux. This year’s theme? “Lost in Transition: the time of possibilities”.&#xA;This annual event is dedicated to exploring the skills and solutions necessary to live well in our emerging digital age across all sectors, from sustainable energy to food and agriculture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEDX McGill 2016</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/project/tedx-mcgill-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/project/tedx-mcgill-2016/</guid>
      <description>Ideas on Stage, the global presentation specialists have been coaching TED speakers over the last six years with great results. This year we not only coached but also partnered with TedX McGill which occurred earlier this month.&#xA;The event theme was paradigm shift and took place at McGill University in Montreal. And as always the speakers were amazing and working on very different fields from gravitational waves to cyborg rights fondation or NGO activist.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
