<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Virtual Meeting Revolution on Ideas on Stage</title>
    <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/tags/virtual-meeting-revolution/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Virtual Meeting Revolution on Ideas on Stage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© Ideas on Stage 2015 - </copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.ideasonstage.com/tags/virtual-meeting-revolution/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Virtual Speaking Success: Effective communication in online meetings</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2020/04/06/2020-04-06-virtual_speaking_success_effective_communication_in_online_meetings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2020/04/06/2020-04-06-virtual_speaking_success_effective_communication_in_online_meetings/</guid>
      <description>As many of us are learning, it’s easy to arrange a virtual meeting, but not so easy to run one successfully. There is quite a steep learning curve.
One vital area to work on is speaking in virtual meetings. People often complain of video issues, microphone issues, poor vocal expression, monotonous speakers, and poor interactivity. Step 5 of our Virtual Meeting Revolution process is called Connection for a good reason: when speaking in an online meeting, you need to connect with the other participants, and you can’t connect if they are so bored they are not paying attention, or if they gave up trying to understand what you are saying.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 5 Virtual Meeting Revolutions</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2020/04/01/2020-04-01-the_5_virtual_meeting_revolutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/news/2020/04/01/2020-04-01-the_5_virtual_meeting_revolutions/</guid>
      <description>What are you going to do today? For many typical office workers, the answer is: too many meetings, and not enough time to work. It’s rare that meetings and productivity coincide.
At the time of writing, many of us are required to work from home, so physical meetings have become virtual meetings, and they’re not always an improvement. Online meetings present their own set of challenges, principally because unless everyone has their camera switched on, one participant won’t know whether another is paying attention, or is checking Instagram, or has gone to walk his dog, aiming to return at the end of the meeting in time to say goodbye and pick up as few actions as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
