<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Presentations on Ideas on Stage</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/presentations/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Presentations on Ideas on Stage</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© Ideas on Stage 2010 - </copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/presentations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>We&#39;re Finalists in the 2024 Learning Excellence Awards</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2023/12/07/2023-12-07-were_finalists_in_the_2024_learning_excellence_awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2023/12/07/2023-12-07-were_finalists_in_the_2024_learning_excellence_awards/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re over the moon to announce that Ideas on Stage has been selected as a finalist for the prestigious 2024 Learning Excellence Awards.&#xA;These awards spotlight the best in the business when it comes to training and development. Their goal is to recognise the most creative, effective and impactful learning initiatives out there. We&amp;rsquo;re thrilled to be on the list of finalists, standing with some of the industry’s brightest stars.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYU Selects &#39;Confident Presenter&#39; for Business Communications Courses</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2023/11/10/2023-11-10-nyu_selects_confident_presenter_for_business_communications_courses/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2023/11/10/2023-11-10-nyu_selects_confident_presenter_for_business_communications_courses/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled to share some great news about my book, &amp;lsquo;Confident Presenter.&amp;rsquo; It has been selected as a core resource for the Business Communications courses at the prestigious New York University (NYU). Recently, I also had the privilege of teaching a class to NYU&amp;rsquo;s Business Communications students. My hope is that these future leaders will use their communication skills to inspire their audiences, increase their influence, and make a positive impact in the world.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to facilitate virtual meetings</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2020/04/24/2020-04-24-how_to_facilitate_virtual_meetings/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2020/04/24/2020-04-24-how_to_facilitate_virtual_meetings/</guid>
      <description>A virtual meeting without a facilitator is like an orchestra without a conductor: the result is usually an unpleasant cacophony. Before, during and after the meeting, the facilitator’s role is key to ensure harmony, allow each participant to contribute, and achieve the meeting’s objectives.&#xA;The role will depend on the type of meeting. For a webinar, the facilitator will need to focus on sound quality, ensuring those not speaking have muted their microphones (or doing it for them), and handling the text chat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> The 3 Magic Ingredients of Great Presentations</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2020/01/29/2020-01-29-the_3_magic_ingredients_of_great_presentations/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2020/01/29/2020-01-29-the_3_magic_ingredients_of_great_presentations/</guid>
      <description>Is there a perfect recipe for a successful presentation? No. Partly it depends on the audience and the context: a boardroom presentation shouldn’t look like a TED talk, even if the subject is the same. And different presentations at the same event – a conference, a demo day, an Executive Committee meeting – should also look different from each other, because otherwise none of them will stand out.&#xA;So if there is no magic formula, are there at least some key ingredients we should always include?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Check If Your Presentation Remote Works Without Anyone Noticing</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2019/10/08/2019-10-08-how-to-check-if-your-presentation-remote-works-without-anyone-noticing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2019/10/08/2019-10-08-how-to-check-if-your-presentation-remote-works-without-anyone-noticing/</guid>
      <description>It’s your turn to present. You’ve launched your presentation and enter the stage. But how do you know if your presentation remote is working? If you start clicking back and forth between your first and second slide to see if it is working, everyone will notice what you’re doing, and you will not make a great first impression.&#xA;Luckily, someone shared a simple tip on twitter. Just duplicate your first slide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Game of Thrones and the importance of the storyline</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2019/05/21/2019-05-21-game-of-thrones-and-the-importance-of-the-storyline/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2019/05/21/2019-05-21-game-of-thrones-and-the-importance-of-the-storyline/</guid>
      <description>By now, the last episode of the cult show Game of Thrones has aired. I haven’t seen it, and I didn’t want to see it before writing this article. Whether it accurately follows the storyline of the books or not is a moot point, because said book hasn’t been written yet. And it shows. I won’t spoil anything, don’t worry. But everyone noticed that the screenwriting of the seasons that could rely on George R.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 7 deadly sins of slide design</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2019/04/23/2019-04-23-the-7-deadly-sins-of-slide-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2019/04/23/2019-04-23-the-7-deadly-sins-of-slide-design/</guid>
      <description>This is a quick list of seven common problems that we see with slides created by non specialists. However they are relatively easy to spot, and you don’t have to be a graphic designer to avoid them. Read on and your next slides will look much better!&#xA;Too much content. The goal is not to cover every single inch with content. It’s not because you have some space left at the bottom of the slide that you should put something there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to steal the show</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2019/01/29/2019-01-29-how-to-steal-the-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2019/01/29/2019-01-29-how-to-steal-the-show/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks ago, Ideas on Stage had the privilege of organizing a sales presentation training for Krauthammer at Dolce La Hulpe, close to Brussels in Belgium. For us, delivering a training for dozens of senior people at Krauthammer, one of the world’s most respected sales and management training companies, felt like designing something for Jonathan Ive, Apple’s legendary designer: a bit intimidating but incredibly exciting.&#xA;The training met with great success, and it was fantastic to work with such talented people, but what I will remember most are two presentations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I presented at CES and all I got was a bunch of ungrateful tweets</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2019/01/15/2019-01-14-i-presented-at-ces-and-all-i-got-was-a-bunch-of-ungrateful-tweets/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2019/01/15/2019-01-14-i-presented-at-ces-and-all-i-got-was-a-bunch-of-ungrateful-tweets/</guid>
      <description>My colleague Ricardo pointed me to a tweet from Rene Ritchie, who was attending the conferences at CES.&#xA;Dear almost everyone on stage at CES: Pay ungodly amounts of money — anything you have to — to get WWDC speaker training ASAP.&#xA;Or go to Juilliard or the Royal Shakespeare Company for a month. Whatever works for you.&#xA;&amp;mdash; Rene Ritchie (@reneritchie) January 8, 2019 This tweet says:&#xA;&amp;ldquo;Dear almost everyone on stage at CES: Pay ungodly amounts of money — anything you have to — to get WWDC speaker training ASAP.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What presentation lessons can we learn from Apple’s profit warning?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2019/01/08/2019-01-07-what-presentation-lessons-can-we-learn-from-apples-profit-warning/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2019/01/08/2019-01-07-what-presentation-lessons-can-we-learn-from-apples-profit-warning/</guid>
      <description>By now, you’ve probably heard that Apple was doomed. Last Wednesday they released a profit warning press release, followed by an interview with CEO Tim Cook.&#xA;I’m all too aware of Apple’s previous profit warning. Back in the nineties, after Steve Jobs returned to Apple and a Saudi prince (whose name I forget) bought a lot of Apple shares, I decided that I would be a smart investor and I bought Apple shares too.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Inform, Transform</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2019/01/07/2019-01-07-dont-inform-transform/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2019/01/07/2019-01-07-dont-inform-transform/</guid>
      <description>Too many presentations aim only to inform, yet this is one thing oral presentations are particularly bad at &amp;ndash; we forget most of what we hear within 30 seconds.&#xA;If you want people to remember information, give them a document and a coffee, and time to read. Then you can answer their questions, discuss, agree on the next steps, and leave.&#xA;This is what happens in meetings at companies like Amazon and LinkedIn, where not only do meetings never have slides - they never have presentations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Business Can Learn From TED</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2018/04/10/2018-04-10-what-business-can-learn-from-ted/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2018/04/10/2018-04-10-what-business-can-learn-from-ted/</guid>
      <description>Today marks the start of TED2018, the latest edition of the world&amp;rsquo;s best-known modern conference. Participants in Vancouver will be treated to high-quality talks from well-prepared speakers, and will leave feeling energized and inspired.&#xA;Back in the office, you and your colleagues will no doubt be subjected to low-quality presentations from poorly-prepared speakers, and you will leave feeling bored and uninspired.&#xA;Business presentations are not TED talks. A board meeting is not a stage with a round red carpet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 presentation lessons from The Darkest Hour</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/2018/02/16/2018-02-16-the-darkest-hour-presentation-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/2018/02/16/2018-02-16-the-darkest-hour-presentation-lessons/</guid>
      <description>Have you seen Gary Oldman in his interpretation of Churchill in the latest biopic by Joe Wright? If you have not, please go. It’s jaw-dropping. His outstanding performance may very soon win him an Oscar. You will enjoy some of the finest acting and also benefit from precious presentation lessons from the Master Orator.&#xA;Here are 3 takeaways from the movie, which you can immediately apply for your next keynote, sales meeting or investor pitch.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
