<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Public-speaking-coaching-services on Presentation Creation | Public Speaking Coaching and Training | Ideas on Stage</title>
    <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/public-speaking-coaching-services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Public-speaking-coaching-services on Presentation Creation | Public Speaking Coaching and Training | Ideas on Stage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© Ideas on Stage</copyright>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.ideasonstage.com/public-speaking-coaching-services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Executive Coaching</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/public-speaking-coaching/executive-coaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/public-speaking-coaching/executive-coaching/</guid>
      <description>Lead from the stage Our exclusive Senior Team dedicated to the coaching of C-Level Executives will help you build your communication skills and move to the next stage of your career.
We help many Senior Executives from leading companies to master the arts of leading from the stage, speaking to the media, and inspiring their organisations. Our role is to build competence, confidence and comfort, and make you enjoy the challenge of leadership communication in all situations, from the boardroom to the auditorium.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TEDx Coaching</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/public-speaking-coaching/tedx-coaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/public-speaking-coaching/tedx-coaching/</guid>
      <description>International TEDx expertise Producing a successful TEDx takes a lot of hard work in many different areas, but if everything is well-organised, what determines the success of the event is how well your speakers perform. It’s rarely the best-known speakers who deliver the stand-out talks: it’s the best-prepared speakers.
This is where Ideas on Stage comes in. Since we assisted photographer and environmentalist Yann Arthus-Bertrand with his memorable TED talk in 2009, we have helped over 300 TEDx speakers to create, prepare and deliver the talks of their lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Media Training</title>
      <link>https://www.ideasonstage.com/public-speaking-coaching/media-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ideasonstage.com/public-speaking-coaching/media-training/</guid>
      <description>Show the world the best version of yourself You come from make-up into a warm studio under hot lights, you take a seat opposite a journalist you hardly know, and after a brief greeting you are thrust via technology in front of a million pairs of eyes. Just as that thought hits your mind you’re being fired your first question, by someone who might not pull their punches. It suddenly feels even hotter under the lights.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>